<NotepadPlus>
    <UserLang name="Paradox Game Log" ext="log" udlVersion="2.1">
        <Settings>
            <Global caseIgnored="no" allowFoldOfComments="no" foldCompact="no" forcePureLC="0" decimalSeparator="0" />
            <Prefix Keywords1="no" Keywords2="no" Keywords3="no" Keywords4="no" Keywords5="no" Keywords6="no" Keywords7="no" Keywords8="no" />
        </Settings>
        <KeywordLists>
            <Keywords name="Comments">00merchant 00diplomat 01 02 03 04</Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Numbers, prefix1"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Numbers, prefix2"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Numbers, extras1"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Numbers, extras2"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Numbers, suffix1"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Numbers, suffix2"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Numbers, range"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Operators1"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Operators2"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Folders in code1, open"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Folders in code1, middle"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Folders in code1, close"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Folders in code2, open"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Folders in code2, middle"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Folders in code2, close"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Folders in comment, open"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Folders in comment, middle"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Folders in comment, close"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Keywords1">&quot;Aq Qoyunlu.&quot; &quot;United Central America.&quot; &quot;Rewa Kantha.&quot; &quot;Dai Viet.&quot; &quot;East Frisia.&quot; &quot;Great Britain.&quot; &quot;Golden Horde.&quot; &quot;Great Horde.&quot; &quot;Holy Roman Empire.&quot; &quot;Kara Del.&quot; &quot;Hisn Kayfa.&quot; &quot;Jan Mayen.&quot; &quot;Kanem Bornu.&quot; &quot;The Knights.&quot; &quot;La Plata.&quot; &quot;Livonian Order.&quot; &quot;Lan Na.&quot; &quot;The Isles.&quot; &quot;Luang Prabang.&quot; &quot;Lan Xang.&quot; &quot;Medri Bahri.&quot; &quot;Mong Kawng.&quot; &quot;Mong Mao.&quot; &quot;Mong Nai.&quot; &quot;Mong Pai.&quot; &quot;Muan Phuang.&quot; &quot;Mong Yang.&quot; &quot;Deva Bengal.&quot; &quot;Nizhny Novgorod.&quot; &quot;The Palatinate.&quot; &quot;The Papal State.&quot; &quot;Qara Qoyunlu.&quot; &quot;Roman Empire.&quot; &quot;Sarig Yogir.&quot; &quot;Teutonic Order.&quot; &quot;United States.&quot; &quot;Al Gharbia.&quot; &quot;Al Ghaydah.&quot; &quot;Al Jawf.&quot; &quot;Al Karak.&quot; &quot;Al Qadarif.&quot; &quot;Al Ula.&quot; &quot;Al Wajh.&quot; &quot;Altai Uriankhai.&quot; &quot;Ar Raqqa.&quot; &quot;Arica Bend.&quot; &quot;Arrial dos Couros.&quot; &quot;Ash Sharqiyah.&quot; &quot;Bab el Mandeb.&quot; &quot;Badiyat ash Sham.&quot; &quot;Bahama Banks.&quot; &quot;Baisi Rajya.&quot; &quot;Banda Oriental.&quot; &quot;Bandar Langeh.&quot; &quot;Bani Yas.&quot; &quot;Bayan Tumen.&quot; &quot;Bengal Delta.&quot; &quot;Blake Plateau.&quot; &quot;Bouvet Island.&quot; &quot;Campo Largo.&quot; &quot;Canary Approach.&quot; &quot;Canterbury Bight.&quot; &quot;Cao Bang.&quot; &quot;Castilla La Vieja.&quot; &quot;Central Africa.&quot; &quot;Central Australia.&quot; &quot;Central Caribbean.&quot; &quot;Central Doab.&quot; &quot;Central Sahara.&quot; &quot;Central Siberia.&quot; &quot;Chaco Austral.&quot; &quot;Chaco Boreal.&quot; &quot;Chaco Central.&quot; &quot;Chagos Archipelago.&quot; &quot;Chaubisi Rajya.&quot; &quot;Chiang Mai.&quot; &quot;Chiang Rai.&quot; &quot;Chott el-Jerid.&quot; &quot;Christmas Island.&quot; &quot;Clipperton Island.&quot; &quot;Cocos Island.&quot; &quot;Comorin Cape.&quot; &quot;Cook Inlet.&quot; &quot;Costa Rica.&quot; &quot;Costa Verde.&quot; &quot;Cote D\&apos;Argent.&quot; &quot;Cote D\&apos;Azur.&quot; &quot;Cuyo Archipelago.&quot; &quot;Dahlak Archipelago.&quot; &quot;Den Haag.&quot; &quot;Dogger Bank.&quot; &quot;Dong Kinh.&quot; &quot;Donji Kraji.&quot; &quot;East Berar.&quot; &quot;East Frisia.&quot; &quot;East March.&quot; &quot;East Sahara.&quot; &quot;East Timor.&quot; &quot;East Tunguska.&quot; &quot;East of Magellans.&quot; &quot;Easter Island.&quot; &quot;Eastern Amazonas.&quot; &quot;Eastern Caribbean.&quot; &quot;Eastern Gibbs Fracture.&quot; &quot;Eastern Siberia.&quot; &quot;Egyptian Desert.&quot; &quot;El Buur.&quot; &quot;El Djouf.&quot; &quot;El Obeid.&quot; &quot;Espirito Santo.&quot; &quot;Ewaso Ngiro.&quot; &quot;Fernando Po.&quot; &quot;Firth of Forth.&quot; &quot;Flint Island.&quot; &quot;Florida Blanca.&quot; &quot;Fuerte Borbon.&quot; &quot;Futa Jallon.&quot; &quot;Ganges Delta.&quot; &quot;Great Australian Bight.&quot; &quot;Great Barrier Reef.&quot; &quot;Great Karoo.&quot; &quot;Greenland Tip.&quot; &quot;Guugu Yimithirr.&quot; &quot;Ha Tinh.&quot; &quot;Hai Phong.&quot; &quot;Hatton Bank.&quot; &quot;Heard and McDonald.&quot; &quot;Helgoland Bight.&quot; &quot;Hetu Ala.&quot; &quot;High Atlas.&quot; &quot;Hisn Kayfa.&quot; &quot;Hkamti Long.&quot; &quot;Horn of Africa.&quot; &quot;Houtman Abrolhos.&quot; &quot;Iberian Shelf.&quot; &quot;Ih Huree.&quot; &quot;Ilan Hala.&quot; &quot;Inner Hebrides.&quot; &quot;Irrawady Delta.&quot; &quot;Jabal Shammar.&quot; &quot;Jabal Tubaiq.&quot; &quot;Ju Ud.&quot; &quot;Kangaroo Island.&quot; &quot;Khara Narin Ula.&quot; &quot;Khukhanor Surin.&quot; &quot;Koch Hajo.&quot; &quot;Kopet Dag.&quot; &quot;La Mancha.&quot; &quot;La Rioja.&quot; &quot;Las Khorey.&quot; &quot;Lehad Datu.&quot; &quot;Les Cayes.&quot; &quot;Lesser Antilles.&quot; &quot;Lesser Namaqualand.&quot; &quot;Lord Howe Island.&quot; &quot;Lower Doab.&quot; &quot;Lower Don.&quot; &quot;Lower Ishim.&quot; &quot;Lower Yik.&quot; &quot;Luang Namtha.&quot; &quot;Luang Prabang.&quot; &quot;Ma\&apos;din Sulaym.&quot; &quot;Macquarie Harbour.&quot; &quot;Madre de Dios.&quot; &quot;Marion Island.&quot; &quot;Mascarene Plateau.&quot; &quot;Midway Island.&quot; &quot;Minas Gerais.&quot; &quot;Miyoo Gasan.&quot; &quot;Mona Passage.&quot; &quot;Mong Kawng.&quot; &quot;Mong Kung.&quot; &quot;Mong Nai.&quot; &quot;Mong Pai.&quot; &quot;Mong Yang.&quot; &quot;Moray Firth.&quot; &quot;Mornington Abyssal Plain.&quot; &quot;Mrauk U.&quot; &quot;Naga Hills.&quot; &quot;Nakhon Si Thammarat.&quot; &quot;Nakhon Thung Yai.&quot; &quot;Naturaliste Plateau.&quot; &quot;New Caledonia.&quot; &quot;Nizhny Novgorod.&quot; &quot;Nong Khai.&quot; &quot;Nongbua Lamphu.&quot; &quot;North Kanara.&quot; &quot;Northwest Cape.&quot; &quot;Northwest Territories.&quot; &quot;Northwestern Caribbean.&quot; &quot;Northwestern Pacific.&quot; &quot;Norton Sound.&quot; &quot;Nowy Sacz.&quot; &quot;Onan Gol.&quot; &quot;Orinoco Delta.&quot; &quot;Outer Hebrides.&quot; &quot;Palawan Passage.&quot; &quot;Pastos Bons.&quot; &quot;Patos Lagoon.&quot; &quot;Pegaya Orda.&quot; &quot;Phnom Penh.&quot; &quot;Phra Bang.&quot; &quot;Porto Seguro.&quot; &quot;Povos das Missoes.&quot; &quot;Prek Russey.&quot; &quot;Prey Nokor.&quot; &quot;Puerto Carreno.&quot; &quot;Puerto Deseado.&quot; &quot;Puna de Atacama.&quot; &quot;Qasr Ibrim.&quot; &quot;Ras Gharib.&quot; &quot;Rio Branco.&quot; &quot;Rio Contas.&quot; &quot;Rio Das Mortes.&quot; &quot;Rio Grande do Sul.&quot; &quot;Rio Grande.&quot; &quot;Rio Negro.&quot; &quot;Rio de Janeiro.&quot; &quot;Rio de la Plata.&quot; &quot;Romanche Gap.&quot; &quot;Rub\&apos; al Khali.&quot; &quot;Sable Island Bank.&quot; &quot;Sahra an.&quot; N&#x00FC;byah &quot;Saint Helena Island.&quot; &quot;San Antonio.&quot; &quot;San Joaquin.&quot; &quot;San Juan.&quot; &quot;San Luis.&quot; &quot;Santa Catalina.&quot; &quot;Santa Catarina.&quot; &quot;Santa Cruz de la Sierra.&quot; &quot;Santa Fe.&quot; &quot;Santa Tecla.&quot; &quot;Santiago del Estero.&quot; &quot;Santo Amaro.&quot; &quot;Santo Antonio da Manga.&quot; &quot;Sao Joao del Rei.&quot; &quot;Sao Tome.&quot; &quot;Sao Vicente.&quot; &quot;Savanh Nakhone.&quot; &quot;Sierra Leone.&quot; &quot;Sol Galitskaya.&quot; &quot;Song La.&quot; &quot;South Georgia.&quot; &quot;South Kanara.&quot; &quot;South Pacific Raging Fifties.&quot; &quot;South Pacific Roaring Forties.&quot; &quot;South Pacific.&quot; &quot;Southeast Pacific.&quot; &quot;St Gallen.&quot; &quot;St. Helena.&quot; &quot;St. Kitts.&quot; &quot;St. Lucia.&quot; &quot;St. Martin.&quot; &quot;St. Thomas.&quot; &quot;St. Vincent.&quot; &quot;Stung Treng.&quot; &quot;Suleiman Range.&quot; &quot;Suntar Khayata.&quot; &quot;Takla Makan.&quot; &quot;Tannu Uriankhai.&quot; &quot;Tay Nguyen.&quot; &quot;Teuk Khmao.&quot; &quot;Thanh Hoa.&quot; &quot;Tharp Fault.&quot; &quot;The Alps.&quot; &quot;The Andamans.&quot; &quot;The Azores.&quot; &quot;The Baleares.&quot; &quot;The Canarias.&quot; &quot;The Carpathians.&quot; &quot;The Caucasus.&quot; &quot;The Kurils.&quot; &quot;The Mascareignes.&quot; &quot;The Pyrenees.&quot; &quot;The Scandes.&quot; &quot;The Seychelles.&quot; &quot;Tian Shan.&quot; &quot;Tierra del Fuego.&quot; &quot;Tsuu Tina.&quot; &quot;Ulakhan Fault.&quot; &quot;Upper Doab.&quot; &quot;Upper Guelders.&quot; &quot;Vila Bela.&quot; &quot;Vila Boa.&quot; &quot;Vila Rica.&quot; &quot;Vistula Lagoon.&quot; &quot;Vyshny Volochyok.&quot; &quot;Wadi Halfa.&quot; &quot;Wake Island.&quot; &quot;Wallaby Plateau.&quot; &quot;West March.&quot; &quot;West Timor.&quot; &quot;West Tunguska.&quot; &quot;West of Magellans.&quot; &quot;Western Amazonas.&quot; &quot;Western Approaches.&quot; &quot;Western Australia.&quot; &quot;Western Gibbs Fracture.&quot; &quot;Western Mediterranean.&quot; &quot;Western Pacific.&quot; &quot;Western Siberia.&quot; &quot;White Karelia.&quot; &quot;Xilin Gol.&quot; &quot;Yang Tse Delta.&quot; &quot;Yangi Hissar.&quot; &quot;Yos Sudarso.&quot; &quot;Zenith Plateau.&quot; &quot;Aq Qoyunlu&quot; &quot;United Central America&quot; &quot;Rewa Kantha&quot; &quot;Dai Viet&quot; &quot;East Frisia&quot; &quot;Great Britain&quot; &quot;Golden Horde&quot; &quot;Great Horde&quot; &quot;Holy Roman Empire&quot; &quot;Kara Del&quot; &quot;Hisn Kayfa&quot; &quot;Jan Mayen&quot; &quot;Kanem Bornu&quot; &quot;The Knights&quot; &quot;La Plata&quot; &quot;Livonian Order&quot; &quot;Lan Na&quot; &quot;The Isles&quot; &quot;Luang Prabang&quot; &quot;Lan Xang&quot; &quot;Medri Bahri&quot; &quot;Mong Kawng&quot; &quot;Mong Mao&quot; &quot;Mong Nai&quot; &quot;Mong Pai&quot; &quot;Muan Phuang&quot; &quot;Mong Yang&quot; &quot;Deva Bengal&quot; &quot;Nizhny Novgorod&quot; &quot;The Palatinate&quot; &quot;The Papal State&quot; &quot;Qara Qoyunlu&quot; &quot;Roman Empire&quot; &quot;Sarig Yogir&quot; &quot;Teutonic Order&quot; &quot;United States&quot; &quot;Al Gharbia&quot; &quot;Al Ghaydah&quot; &quot;Al Jawf&quot; &quot;Al Karak&quot; &quot;Al Qadarif&quot; &quot;Al Ula&quot; &quot;Al Wajh&quot; &quot;Altai Uriankhai&quot; &quot;Ar Raqqa&quot; &quot;Arica Bend&quot; &quot;Arrial dos Couros&quot; &quot;Ash Sharqiyah&quot; &quot;Bab el Mandeb&quot; &quot;Badiyat ash Sham&quot; &quot;Bahama Banks&quot; &quot;Baisi Rajya&quot; &quot;Banda Oriental&quot; &quot;Bandar Langeh&quot; &quot;Bani Yas&quot; &quot;Bayan Tumen&quot; &quot;Bengal Delta&quot; &quot;Blake Plateau&quot; &quot;Bouvet Island&quot; &quot;Campo Largo&quot; &quot;Canary Approach&quot; &quot;Canterbury Bight&quot; &quot;Cao Bang&quot; &quot;Castilla La Vieja&quot; &quot;Central Africa&quot; &quot;Central Australia&quot; &quot;Central Caribbean&quot; &quot;Central Doab&quot; &quot;Central Sahara&quot; &quot;Central Siberia&quot; &quot;Chaco Austral&quot; &quot;Chaco Boreal&quot; &quot;Chaco Central&quot; &quot;Chagos Archipelago&quot; &quot;Chaubisi Rajya&quot; &quot;Chiang Mai&quot; &quot;Chiang Rai&quot; &quot;Chott el-Jerid&quot; &quot;Christmas Island&quot; &quot;Clipperton Island&quot; &quot;Cocos Island&quot; &quot;Comorin Cape&quot; &quot;Cook Inlet&quot; &quot;Costa Rica&quot; &quot;Costa Verde&quot; &quot;Cote D\&apos;Argent&quot; &quot;Cote D\&apos;Azur&quot; &quot;Cuyo Archipelago&quot; &quot;Dahlak Archipelago&quot; &quot;Den Haag&quot; &quot;Dogger Bank&quot; &quot;Dong Kinh&quot; &quot;Donji Kraji&quot; &quot;East Berar&quot; &quot;East Frisia&quot; &quot;East March&quot; &quot;East Sahara&quot; &quot;East Timor&quot; &quot;East Tunguska&quot; &quot;East of Magellans&quot; &quot;Easter Island&quot; &quot;Eastern Amazonas&quot; &quot;Eastern Caribbean&quot; &quot;Eastern Gibbs Fracture&quot; &quot;Eastern Siberia&quot; &quot;Egyptian Desert&quot; &quot;El Buur&quot; &quot;El Djouf&quot; &quot;El Obeid&quot; &quot;Espirito Santo&quot; &quot;Ewaso Ngiro&quot; &quot;Fernando Po&quot; &quot;Firth of Forth&quot; &quot;Flint Island&quot; &quot;Florida Blanca&quot; &quot;Fuerte Borbon&quot; &quot;Futa Jallon&quot; &quot;Ganges Delta&quot; &quot;Great Australian Bight&quot; &quot;Great Barrier Reef&quot; &quot;Great Karoo&quot; &quot;Greenland Tip&quot; &quot;Guugu Yimithirr&quot; &quot;Ha Tinh&quot; &quot;Hai Phong&quot; &quot;Hatton Bank&quot; &quot;Heard and McDonald&quot; &quot;Helgoland Bight&quot; &quot;Hetu Ala&quot; &quot;High Atlas&quot; &quot;Hisn Kayfa&quot; &quot;Hkamti Long&quot; &quot;Horn of Africa&quot; &quot;Houtman Abrolhos&quot; &quot;Iberian Shelf&quot; &quot;Ih Huree&quot; &quot;Ilan Hala&quot; &quot;Inner Hebrides&quot; &quot;Irrawady Delta&quot; &quot;Jabal Shammar&quot; &quot;Jabal Tubaiq&quot; &quot;Ju Ud&quot; &quot;Kangaroo Island&quot; &quot;Khara Narin Ula&quot; &quot;Khukhanor Surin&quot; &quot;Koch Hajo&quot; &quot;Kopet Dag&quot; &quot;La Mancha&quot; &quot;La Rioja&quot; &quot;Las Khorey&quot; &quot;Lehad Datu&quot; &quot;Les Cayes&quot; &quot;Lesser Antilles&quot; &quot;Lesser Namaqualand&quot; &quot;Lord Howe Island&quot; &quot;Lower Doab&quot; &quot;Lower Don&quot; &quot;Lower Ishim&quot; &quot;Lower Yik&quot; &quot;Luang Namtha&quot; &quot;Luang Prabang&quot; &quot;Ma\&apos;din Sulaym&quot; &quot;Macquarie Harbour&quot; &quot;Madre de Dios&quot; &quot;Marion Island&quot; &quot;Mascarene Plateau&quot; &quot;Midway Island&quot; &quot;Minas Gerais&quot; &quot;Miyoo Gasan&quot; &quot;Mona Passage&quot; &quot;Mong Kawng&quot; &quot;Mong Kung&quot; &quot;Mong Nai&quot; &quot;Mong Pai&quot; &quot;Mong Yang&quot; &quot;Moray Firth&quot; &quot;Mornington Abyssal Plain&quot; &quot;Mrauk U&quot; &quot;Naga Hills&quot; &quot;Nakhon Si Thammarat&quot; &quot;Nakhon Thung Yai&quot; &quot;Naturaliste Plateau&quot; &quot;New Caledonia&quot; &quot;Nizhny Novgorod&quot; &quot;Nong Khai&quot; &quot;Nongbua Lamphu&quot; &quot;North Kanara&quot; &quot;Northwest Cape&quot; &quot;Northwest Territories&quot; &quot;Northwestern Caribbean&quot; &quot;Northwestern Pacific&quot; &quot;Norton Sound&quot; &quot;Nowy Sacz&quot; &quot;Onan Gol&quot; &quot;Orinoco Delta&quot; &quot;Outer Hebrides&quot; &quot;Palawan Passage&quot; &quot;Pastos Bons&quot; &quot;Patos Lagoon&quot; &quot;Pegaya Orda&quot; &quot;Phnom Penh&quot; &quot;Phra Bang&quot; &quot;Porto Seguro&quot; &quot;Povos das Missoes&quot; &quot;Prek Russey&quot; &quot;Prey Nokor&quot; &quot;Puerto Carreno&quot; &quot;Puerto Deseado&quot; &quot;Puna de Atacama&quot; &quot;Qasr Ibrim&quot; &quot;Ras Gharib&quot; &quot;Rio Branco&quot; &quot;Rio Contas&quot; &quot;Rio Das Mortes&quot; &quot;Rio Grande do Sul&quot; &quot;Rio Grande&quot; &quot;Rio Negro&quot; &quot;Rio de Janeiro&quot; &quot;Rio de la Plata&quot; &quot;Romanche Gap&quot; &quot;Rub\&apos; al Khali&quot; &quot;Sable Island Bank&quot; &quot;Sahra an&quot; N&#x00FC;byah &quot;Saint Helena Island&quot; &quot;San Antonio&quot; &quot;San Joaquin&quot; &quot;San Juan&quot; &quot;San Luis&quot; &quot;Santa Catalina&quot; &quot;Santa Catarina&quot; &quot;Santa Cruz de la Sierra&quot; &quot;Santa Fe&quot; &quot;Santa Tecla&quot; &quot;Santiago del Estero&quot; &quot;Santo Amaro&quot; &quot;Santo Antonio da Manga&quot; &quot;Sao Joao del Rei&quot; &quot;Sao Tome&quot; &quot;Sao Vicente&quot; &quot;Savanh Nakhone&quot; &quot;Sierra Leone&quot; &quot;Sol Galitskaya&quot; &quot;Song La&quot; &quot;South Georgia&quot; &quot;South Kanara&quot; &quot;South Pacific Raging Fifties&quot; &quot;South Pacific Roaring Forties&quot; &quot;South Pacific&quot; &quot;Southeast Pacific&quot; &quot;St Gallen&quot; &quot;St. Helena&quot; &quot;St. Kitts&quot; &quot;St. Lucia&quot; &quot;St. Martin&quot; &quot;St. Thomas&quot; &quot;St. Vincent&quot; &quot;Stung Treng&quot; &quot;Suleiman Range&quot; &quot;Suntar Khayata&quot; &quot;Takla Makan&quot; &quot;Tannu Uriankhai&quot; &quot;Tay Nguyen&quot; &quot;Teuk Khmao&quot; &quot;Thanh Hoa&quot; &quot;Tharp Fault&quot; &quot;The Alps&quot; &quot;The Andamans&quot; &quot;The Azores&quot; &quot;The Baleares&quot; &quot;The Canarias&quot; &quot;The Carpathians&quot; &quot;The Caucasus&quot; &quot;The Kurils&quot; &quot;The Mascareignes&quot; &quot;The Pyrenees&quot; &quot;The Scandes&quot; &quot;The Seychelles&quot; &quot;Tian Shan&quot; &quot;Tierra del Fuego&quot; &quot;Tsuu Tina&quot; &quot;Ulakhan Fault&quot; &quot;Upper Doab&quot; &quot;Upper Guelders&quot; &quot;Vila Bela&quot; &quot;Vila Boa&quot; &quot;Vila Rica&quot; &quot;Vistula Lagoon&quot; &quot;Vyshny Volochyok&quot; &quot;Wadi Halfa&quot; &quot;Wake Island&quot; &quot;Wallaby Plateau&quot; &quot;West March&quot; &quot;West Timor&quot; &quot;West Tunguska&quot; &quot;West of Magellans&quot; &quot;Western Amazonas&quot; &quot;Western Approaches&quot; &quot;Western Australia&quot; &quot;Western Gibbs Fracture&quot; &quot;Western Mediterranean&quot; &quot;Western Pacific&quot; &quot;Western Siberia&quot; &quot;White Karelia&quot; &quot;Xilin Gol&quot; &quot;Yang Tse Delta&quot; &quot;Yangi Hissar&quot; &quot;Yos Sudarso&quot; &quot;Zenith Plateau&quot; &#x00CE;le Bourbon Aachen Abancay Abarquh Abda Aberdeen Abitibi Abkhazia Abomey Abruzzi Achaea Acoma Adai Adana Adanki Adavani Aden Ader Adirondack Adyghe Afder Afgooye Aflaj Agadir Agan Agdesiden Agew Agyidel Ah Canul Ahmadabad Ahmadnagar Ahuriri Ahvaz Aigun Air Ais Ajlun Ajmer Akershus Aki Aksaray Aksary Aksu Aksum Akureyri Al-Arid Al-Junaynah Al-Kariatan Al-Qatif Al-Yamamah Alabama Alagoas Alakol Alania Alaska Alatyr Albenga Alborz Alcantara Alchuka Aldan Alen&#x00E7;on Aleppo Aleut Alexandria Algarve Algonquin Alicante Alimuly Allegheny Almaty Almer&#x00ED;a Altagracia Altmark Alty-Kuduk Altyn Alxa Amapa Amasya Ambon Amol Amsterdam Ancona Anding Andong Androscoggin Angara Angkor Angoche Angostura Angot Angoumois Anhalt Anjou Ankara Ankober Annaba Anqing Ansbach Antankara Antanosy Antemoro Anticosti Antigua Antioch Antioqu&#x00ED;a Antofagasta Antsalova Antwerpen Anziku Apache Apalachee Apatzingan Aps&#x00E1;alooke Apure Aqabah Aqenganggyai Aquitaine Ar-Chally Arapaho Araraquara Araxas Arbil Arcot Ardabil Ardakan Ardalan Arequipa Arezzo Arguin Argyll Argyn Aribanda Arica Arikara Arkansas Armagnac Armor Aroostook Arsi Arsigantegok Artois Aru Arunachal Ashshipite Asinaan Asmat Asosa Assab Assam Astara Astrakhan Asturias Asuncion Aswan Atabapo Atakapa Atakent Atakora Atfih Athabasca Athens Atikaki Atikamekw Atrakwaye Attawapiskat Augsburg Aures Ausa Auvergne Auxerrois Ava Avignon Awa Awngthim Ayaviri Aydin Ayntab Ayrshire Aysen Ayutthaya Azaraba Azawad Azawagh Azbin Azov Azraq Baachinena Bacs Badajoz Badakhshan Baden Baffin Bafuriru Bagamoyo Baganaly Baghdad Baghelkhand Baghena Bagirmi Baglana Bagoe Bahamas Bahawalpur Bahia Bahiriya Bahmut Bahrain Bahreich Baiali Balasore Bali Balikul Balkh Baltistan Bam Bamberg Bambuk Bamyan Bandogarh Bangka Banjar Bannock Bannu Banten Baoding Bara Baracoa Barahonas Baraimi Barawa Barbados Barcelona Barcelos Bardera Bardiyah Bareily Barguzin Bari Barinas Barito Barmer Barnaul Baroda Barra Barrois Barunggam Bas-Poitou Bashgird Bashkortostan Basra Bastar Batak Batinah Battambang Bauchi Bayamo Bayazid Baykha Bayougoula Bayuda Bayuly Beafada Bechbaliq Bedde Beihan Beijing Beira Beja Bela Beledweyne Belem Belgrade Belitung Belize Beljamen Beloozero Belz Bemba Bender Bendugu Benghazi Bengkulu Benguela Benin Beothuk Berau Berber Berbera Berezov Berg Bergenhus Bergslagen Berlin Bermuda Bern Berry Besalampy Bessarabia Betsileo Bezhetsk Bhagalpur Bhakkar Bharatpur Bharuch Bhatnair Bhattiana Bhera Bhilsa Bhilwara Bidar Bihar Bijapur Bikol Bilanga Biloxi Bintan Biram Birija Birjand Bishah Bishnupur Biskra Bitlis Bizen Bizerte Blambangan Blekinge Boduna Bogota Bohogue Bohori Bohusl&#x00E4;n Bojnord Bolgar Bolu Bonny Bonoman Borborema Borgu Borik&#x00E9;n Borisoglebsk Borneo Bornholm Borno Borrado Bosaso Bosnia Bourbonnais Bozhou Bozok Bragan&#x00E7;a Brakna Branicevo Braslaw Bratsberg Bratslav Breda Breisgau Bremen Brescia Breslau Brest Brno Brunei Brunswick Brussels Bryansk Budejovice Buganda Buglas Buhaira Buhera Bukhara Bulungan Bundi Bundjalung Bungi Bungo Bunyoro Buraydah Bure Burgas Burgos Burhanpur Buru Bushubi Busoga Bust Butana Buteha Buton Butua Butuan Buyogoma Buzau Buzinza Buzuluk B&#x00E9;arn B&#x00E9;k&#x00E9;s Cacaxtes Caceres Cachar Caddo Cadiz Caen Caffa Cagayan Cagliari Cahokia Cahuilla Cairo Cajamarca Calabar Calabria Calais Calama Calicut Calusa Camaguey Camana Cambray Cambridge Cameroon Campeche Campinas Canari Candelaria Canelos Canik Cannanore Cantabria Canton Cape Capitanata Caqueta Caracas Caraga Carmarthen Carmen Cartagena Castro Catamarca Catawba Cauca Caux Cayenne Cayor Cayuga Ceara Cebu Ceram Cerejeiras Ceuta Chabahar Chachapoyas Chacujal Chagai Chahar Chaiya Chaiyaphum Chakhansur Chakla Champaran Champasak Champutun Chanar Chanchan Chanda Chanderi Chandragiri Changsha Changtang Chaochow Chara Charcas Charjuy Charolais Chartres Chatot Chaul Chehalis Chelmno Chelyaba Chengde Chengdu Cheongju Chepes Cheraw Cherdyn Cherkasy Chernigov Cherokee Chesapeake Chester Chiapas Chichas Chickamauga Chickasaw Chicora Chikuzen Chillicothe Chiloe Chimbote Chinook Chios Chipewyan Chiquitos Chiquiyami Chiricahua Chisca Chisedec Chitimacha Chitradurg Chittagong Chittor Choco Choctaw Chokwe Cholistan Cholula Chongqing Choquechaca Chorotega Chortli Chubut Chuguchak Chulym Chumash Chuna Chungju Chuquiabo Churu Chuy Cicigar Cihuatlan Circassia Cirebon Cisasipi Coahuila Coahuilteco Cochabamba Cochimi Coimbra Coixtlahuacan Colima Colonia Columbia Comoros Conceicao Concepcion Concho Connaught Connecticut Conoy Constantine Constantinople Coosa Copiapo Coquimbo Corfu Cork Cornwall Coro Corrientes Corsica Corumba Cosenza Cotentin Cotoname Coventry Coweta Coxim Coyolapan Crato Cree Cremona Crete Crimea Cuddalore Cuenca Cuetlaxtlan Cuiaba Cuitzeo Cumana Cumbria Cuneo Curacao Curitiba Cusabo Cuttack Cutzamala Cuzco Cyprus C&#x00F3;rdoba Dabhol Dagbon Dagestan Dagon Dahra Dakelh Dal Dalaskogen Dali Dallol Dalmatia Damagaram Daman Damascus Damietta Damin Daming Damot Damxung Danezaa Dang Danzig Darab Darfur Darien Darnah Darrang Daru Dashtistan Datong Daulatabad Dauphin&#x00E9; Daura Dawa Dawaro Dawasir Dazhou Dege Degehabur Dehong Delaware Delhi Deli Demak Dembiya Demerara Dendi Denizli Denkyira Derajat Derby Deren Desmond Devarakonda Devon Dhaka Dhamar Dharangaon Dhofar Dhundar Diamantina Diamantino Dijonnais Dindigul Dipalpur Dithmarschen Diu Divrigi Diyarbakir Djado Djerba Do Doaba Doeg Dominica Donegal Dongola Dongting Dornogovi Dorpat Dorset Doti Draa Dresden Dukkala Dundgovi Durr&#x00EB;s Dzhaman-Kuduk Ecab Echigo Echizen Edirne Eeelalapito Eger Eiriksfjord Ejin Elfsborg Elsass Enare Enderta Eora Epekwitk Epirus Ereen Erie Erz Erzincan Erzurum Eskikewakik Esmeraldas Espachomy Essequibo Essex Etawah Etchemins Etchu Etkara Euboea Extremadura Eyak Eyeish Ezorongondo Fak-Fak Falklands Farafreh Fasa Fathabad Fayyum Fazughli Fej&#x00E9;r Fengxiang Fengyang Ferah Ferrara Feyzabad Fez Fezzan Figuig Fiherana Fiji Finist&#x00E8;re Finnmark Firenze Flores Forcalquier Franche-Comt&#x00E9; Frankfurt Friesland Friuli Fudali Furdan Fuyang Fuzhou Fyn F&#x00E4;r&#x00F6;arna Gabon Gabu Gafsa Gaizhou Galam Galich Galicia Galkayo Gambela Ganggye Gangneung Ganja Ganjam Ganzhou Gao Garhwal Garoowe Garze Gauda Gayo Gaza Gazni Gedo Gelre Genoa Gezira Ghadames Gharb Ghazipur Ghent Ghor Ghuriyan Gibraltar Gingee Gird Girga Girin Girnar Girona Gizhiga Glamorgan Glogau Gloucester Goa Gobir Gogo Gohilvad Goias Gojjam Golconda Goldingen Golestan Gonder Goraghat Gorakhpur Gorontalo Gorwar Goshute Gotland Govi Graaff-Reinet Grajau Granada Grane Graub&#x00FC;nden Graz Greenland Greifswald Griqualand Grodno Groningen Guachichil Guadelupe Guajira Guale Guam Guamares Guangnan Guantanamo Guapore Guasipati Guatemala Guaviare Guayaquil Guaycura Guayra Guilin Guinea Guiyang Gulbarga Gunditjmara Gurganj Guria Gurma Gutti Guyana Gwadar Gwiriko Gwynedd Gyaaman Gyegu Gyeongju Gyeongseong Gyirong G&#x00F6;inge G&#x00F6;rz Haaninin Haayre Haditha Hadiya Hadoti Haeju Hafar Hafun Haha Haibatnagar Haida Haiilanboo Hainaut Haizhou Hajipur Halaib Halar Halicz Halland Halmahera Hama Hamadan Hamasien Hamburg Hamheung Hami Hamid Hampshire Handia Hangzhou Hanover Hanseong Hanuabada Hanzhong Harer Hargeisa Harima Hasinai Haut-Poitou Havana Hawaii Hebina Hefei Hehe Heidelberg Heiltsuk Hejian Hemba Hengyang Herat Hessen Hetao Hidatsa Highveld Higo Himalaya Hinggan Hinonoeino Hitachi Hitchiti Hizen Hj&#x00E4;lmaren Hoboksar Hobyo Hochelaga Hodh Hodna Hofuf Hohhot Hollhavai Holstein Hombori Homs Honduras Honnavara Honniasont Hont Hopi Hormuz Hotan Hoveyzeh Hoya Hradecko Hsenwi Hsipaw Huai\&apos;an Huaiqing Hualapai Huancavelica Huangzhou Huanuco Huaraz Huastec Hue Huichol Huillimapu Huizhou Hulan Hull Hulunbuir Hum Huncun Hunyad Huron Hwangju Hyuga H&#x00E4;lsingland H&#x00E5;logaland H&#x00FC;davendigar Ibo Iboina Ibra Idah Ife Ifni Ifugao Iglino Ijebu Ilam Ilheus Ili Illichpur Illinois Illubabor Ilocos Iman Imatong Imereti Indragiri Indrapura Ingermanland Ingil Ingolstadt Inhambane Inhambupe Innu Inverness Iowa Ipora Iquique Iquitos Irkutsk Irtesh Ise Isfahan Ishindi Isna Issyk-Kul Istria Itap&#x00FA;a Itesan Itscheabine Iwami Iximch&#x00E9; Iyo Izhkar Izumo I&#x00E7;el Jaffa Jaisalmer Jalalabad Jamaica Jambi Jammu Jangladesh Janjiro Jask Jauja Jaunpur Jazan Ja&#x00E9;n Jeddah Jeju Jenne Jeonju Jeremoabo Jerusalem Jesselton Jeypore Jhalavad Jhansi Jharkhand Ji\&apos;an Jianchang Jianning Jianzhou Jiazhou Jicarilla Jinan Jingzhou Jinhua Jinju Jirem Johor Jokkmokk Joma Jufra Jugjur Jujuy Juketau Jumano Juniata Junir J&#x00E4;mtland Kabardia Kabul Kabylia Kaffa Kagyrgyn Kai Kaifeng Kainuu Kakheti Kala Kalahandi Kalahari Kalapa Kalapuya Kalar Kalat Kale Kalingandhra Kalinjar Kalisz Kalmar Kalonga Kalpi Kaluga Kalundwe Kamchatka Kamikawa Kamilaroi Kan Kanadey Kanawha Kanchipuram Kandahar Kandy Kanem Kangiri Kangra Kanker Kannauj Kano Kanongesha Kansas Kantor Kaonde Karabara Karagwe Karahisar Karakum Karalveyem Karaman Karamegdan Karanja Karankawa Karasi Karbala Karelia Kargopol Karor Karou Kars Karta Kartli Kasanje Kasdir Kashan Kashgar Kashin Kashmir Kasimov Kaskaskia Kaskinampo Kassel Kastamonu Kastoria Katapang Katehar Katha Kathiri Katmandu Katsekera Katsina Kattegat Kaurna Kauthara Kawali Kawar Kawesqar Kayseri Kazan Kazerun Kebbi Kedah Kediri Kef Kelang Kelantan Kenai Kendal Kendari Kengtung Kennebec Kent Kentucky Kerema Kerey Kerman Kesagami Kespek Kespukwitk Kesyehotinne Ket Ketu Kexholm Khairabad Khairpur Khamammet Khambhat Kharan Kharga Kharkov Kharya Kherlen Khiagt Khiva Kholm Kholmogory Khorat Khorramabad Khoy Khujand Khundzia Khurda Kichesipi Kiev Kii Kikuyu Kilatika Kildare Kilwa Kinga Kingchow Kinougeoulini Kiowa Kirenga Kiribati Kirikiriroa Kirkuk Kirmanshah Kirshehir Kir&#x00E1;lyf&#x00F6;ld Kish Kismayo Kitkehaki Kivu Kizil-Su Klamath Kleves Kobbe Kobdo Koblenz Kocaeli Koch Kochin Kochkor Kodiak Kokand Kola Kolberg Kolding Kolhapur Kolomna Kolyma Komi Konaseema Kondavidu Kong Kongu Konjikala Konya Kora Korla Kosovo Kosti Kostroma Kotoko Kotte Kovno Kozuke Krain Krakow Kratie Ktunaxa Kuba Kuban Kuccuntikka Kuching Kudymkar Kulob Kuma Kumaon Kumari Kumasi Kumbana Kumeyaay Kunduz Kungirot Kuqa Kurgan Kuria Kurnool Kursk Kuru Kusu Kutai Kutch Kuznetsk Kwakiutl Kyoto Kypshak Kyzyl-Yar Kyzylkum K&#x00E4;rnten K&#x00F6;ln K&#x00F6;nigsberg K&#x00FC;tahya Labourd Ladakh Ladoga Lae Laghouat Laguna Laguneros Lahijan Lahore Laizhou Lakhnor Lakia Lakota Lala Lamba Lamu Lamuri Lanao Lancashire Landshut Langfjella Lango Langzhong Lanzhou Lappland Larestan Lasta Latgalia Lauenburg Leczyca Lega Leicester Leichow Leinster Leipzig Lenape Lenca Lenje Leyte Lezh&#x00EB; Le&#x00F3;n Lhasa Liangzhou Liegnitz Lienz Lijiang Lika Lima Limbuwan Limchow Limerick Limousin Limpopo Lincolnshire Lindi Lingga Lingyun Linz Lipan Lipiyanes Liptako Lisboa Liuzhou Livland Liwa Li&#x00E8;ge Llanos Loango Lobi Logone Lolland Lolo Lombok Lomwe London Loon Lothian Lothringen Loup Lu\&apos;an Lualaba Luanda Luangwa Luapula Luba Lublin Lucania Lucca Lucknow Luki Lund Lundu Luoyang Luxemburg Luzhou Luziana Lwena Lwow Lyonnais L&#x00FC;beck L&#x00FC;neburg Maan Macau Macaya Macedonia Madanda Madang Madawaska Madeira Madrid Madura Madurai Magdalena Magdeburg Magua Maguana Maguindanao Mahadeo Mahafaly Mahakoshal Mahe Mahican Mahikantha Mahmikiwiniyak Mahoba Mahur Maidu Maine Mainz Maisouna Majar Makassar Makonde Makoua Makua Makwanpur Malacca Malamir Malatya Maldives Malem Malenadu Malgana Malindi Maliseet Malta Manado Managua Manahoac Manaus Mandan Mandara Mandla Mandsaur Mandu Manfalut Manga Mangazea Mangyshlak Manhattan Mani Manicouagan Manidurg Manikya Manila Manipur Manitoba Mann Manokwari Mansur Mansura Mantua Manych Maracaibo Maragheh Maraj&#x00F3; Maralbexi Maramaros Maranhao Marash Mardin Margalla Marghi Marib Marienburg Mariquita Markam Maroantsetra Maros Marrakech Martaban Martinique Marwar Mascouten Mashhad Masirah Massachusetts Massapa Massawa Massina Matamba Matara Matrega Matsolo Mauritius Mawkmai Maya Mayaimi Maymana Mayumba Mayurbhanj Mazyr Mbamba Mbata Mbwila Mdewakanton Mecca Medina Medwa Meghalaya Meknes Melikates Melilla Melodia Mema Memel Memmingen Menabe Mendefera Mendoza Mengkonkia Menominee Mentawai Mentese Meppen Merca Meregh Mergen Mergui Merida Merina Merrimack Merta Merv Mescalero Mesquakie Messina Meta Metz Metztitlan Mewar Mewat Mexico Mezen Miami Mianeh Michigamea Michigan Micronesia Middag Midlands Midnapore Midway Mikawa Mikmaq Milan Minang Mindoro Mingan Mino Minsin Minsk Minya Misiones Missisage Missisquoi Missouri Mitau Mitidja Miwok Mixe Mixtec Mobile Mocama Modena Mogadishu Mogilev Mogostan Mohawk Moingwena Mokha Moldavia Mologa Mombasa Monacan Monghyr Monongahela Montevideo Montferrat Montgomery Montpellier Mora Morang Morasanadu Moratok Morea Moron Moshi Moskva Mosoni Mosquito Mosul Moulmein Moxos Moyobamba Mozambique Mozhaisk Mpangu Mpasu Mpemba Mstislav Mtetwa Mudgal Muhambwe Mukalla Mukhtuya Muko-Muko Multan Munene Muniyo Munsee Murcia Murom Musashi Muscat Mush Muskegon Muskogee Mutsu Muturu Mweru Mysore Mzab Mzizima M&#x00E4;laren M&#x00FC;nchen M&#x00FC;nster Nadia Nadym Naga Nagaur Nagchu Naisha Najran Naju Nakhchivan Nakipa Namibia Namning Namur Nan Nanchang Nander Nanjing Nantais Nanticoke Nanyang Napochi Napoli Narayanpur Narbada Narbonne Narim Narraganset Narva Narym Nasik Nasirabad Nasirpur Naskapi Nassau Natal Natchez Natchitoches Natividad Nauru Navajo Navarra Naxos Nazca Ndongo Nduga Nedong Negapatam Nehiyawewin Neiva Nellore Nemours Nenets Neumark Neva Ngaichow Ngari Ngchow Ngindo Ngonde Ngoyo Niagara Nias Nicaragua Nice Nicoya Niederlausitz Nihithawak Niitsitapi Nimiipu Ningbo Ningguo Ningguta Ningwu Ningxia Ningyuan Nipigon Nipissing Nipmuc Nis Nisga\&apos;a Nishapur Nivernais Nizwa Nkoma Nkore Nogay Nootka Noquet Nordjylland Norfolk Northumberland Notec Novara Novgorod Nsenga Nukhtui Nukunu Nunavut Nunu Nupe Nyatura Nyeongbyeon Nyingchi Nyland N&#x00E4;rke N&#x00FC;rnberg Obdorsk Oberlausitz Oberpfalz Oberschwaben Odawa Odishi Oeiras Ofaie Ogaden Oglala Ohio Oiapoque Ojibwa Oka Okanagan Okhotsk Okinawa Okouara Olancho Olavarria Oldenburg Olomouc Olonets Oltenia Oltu Omaha Omolon Omushkego Ondo Onega Oneida Onondaga Ontario Opplanda Oran Orda Ordos Orkney Orleanais Ormond Ortelsburg Oruro Oshima Osnabr&#x00FC;ck Osterode Ostmarch Ostrov Ostyaki Ouargla Ouarsenis Ouarzazate Oudong Oujda Ouluj&#x00E4;rvi Outoulibi Oversticht Owari Owrucz Oxford Oyo Paderborn Pagan Pagarruyung Pahang Pahatsi Paithre Paiute Pajang Pakuan Palau Palawan Pale Palembang Palermo Palopo Palpa Palu Palus Pambu Pamir Pamlico Panama Panay Panduranga Pangasinan Panipat Papua Para Paraiba Paramaribo Paratinga Paredarerme Pariaman Paris Parlakhimedi Parma Parnagua Parnaiba Pasai Passamaquoddy Pataliputra Patan Pate Pathein Patna Pattani Patzcuaro Pawnee Pegu Pehuenmapu Pelym Pennacook Penobscott Pensacola Penukonda Penza Penzhina Perak Peremyshl Pereyaslav Perm Pernambuco Perth Pest Pet&#x00E9;n Peureulak Pfalz Phangwa Phetchaburi Phitsanulok Piankeshaw Picardie Picunmapu Piedmont Piegan Piekouagami Pijin Pima Pindinga Pingliang Pingyang Pinsk Pipil Pirara Pirineo Pirkanmaa Piro Pisa Piscatang Pisqupampa Piwra Placentia Plock Plovdiv Plzen Pocumtuk Podlasie Podolia Polotsk Poltava Pomo Pontal Pontianak Popayan Porbandar Pore Porto Poso Potawatomi Potomac Potosi Potsdam Powhatan Poya Poyang Poznan Pozsony Prague Prome Pronsk Provence Pskov Pu\&apos;er Pubungo Pueblo Puelches Punakha Pune Puno Purang Purnia Pyeongyang P&#x00E9;rigord Qakilik Qamdo Qaraqalpak Qaraqorum Qardho Qarqan Qarshi Qatar Qawasim Qazaniya Qazvin Qikirmiut Qilian Qingzhou Qishn Qom Quanzhou Quapaw Quelimane Quennebigon Querandi Quercy Querecho Quero Queseer Quetta Quhistan Quijos Quileute Quillacas Quinnipiac Quisquisacate Quito Qumis Qunfudhah Qurqara-usu Qus Rabaul Rafsanjan Ragusa Rahba Raichur Raipur Rajapur Rajkot Rangpur Rano Ranthambore Rapanui Raritan Rasht Raska Ratanpur Ratchaburi Ratibor Rebgong Regensburg Reims Rennais Rethel Reval Rewakantha Reykjavik Rhodes Riga Rikuzen Rioja Roanoke Rockall Roggeveld Roh Rohtasgarh Rokan Roma Romagna Romsdal Rosario Rosetta Rostock Rostov Rouergue Roussillon Rovaniemi Rowne Ruguru Ruhunu Rukwa Rund Runing Ruppin Rutanzige Rutog Ryazan Ryn Rzhev Sabzevar Sadiya Sagaing Sagami Sah Sahda Saidabad Saimaa Saintonge Sakam Sakha Sakhalin Sakya Salamanca Salavata Salem Salento Salerno Salin Salinan Salish Salto Saluda Salzburg Samana Samar Samara Samarinda Samarkand Samawat Sambalpur Sambhal Samoa Samogitia Sampit Sana\&apos;a Sanaag Sandomierz Sandoway Sangju Santarem Santee Santiago Saoura Sarai Sarakhs Saran Saratov Sari Sartu Saruhan Saskatchewan Sassari Satara Satgaon Satsuma Satuskhdin Sauce Saugor Sauk Savah Savanur Savoie Savolax Sayan Sayultecas Scarborough Secwepemc Seganka Segu Sehwan Sekani Selangor Semien Semnan Sena Seneca Sennar Senqu Sergipe Seri Seringapatam Serro Setsen Settsu Severia Sevilla Sfax Shaga Shaggami Shaki Shamakhi Shamba Shangqiu Shangwe Shaoxin Sharqiya Shasta Shatt Shatteras Shegendyk Shekhawati Shekty Shenandoah Shendy Shenkursk Shenyang Shetland Shewa Shigatse Shihr Shimotsuke Shimousa Shinano Shinje Shiraz Shiribeshi Shirvan Shiuhing Shiukwan Sholhapur Shorkot Shrewsbury Shushtar Shymkent Siak Sialkot Sibir Sibiridugu Sibsongbanna Sibu Sidamo Sidon Siena Sieradz Siine Sikhottabong Sikkim Siknikt Siksikawa Sikumiut Silhet Silistria Simbirsk Sinai Sinaloa Sinjar Sinop Sipeknekatik Sipiwininiwak Sira Siraf Sirhind Sirmur Sirt Sisseton Sitka Siuslaw Sivas Siwi Sj&#x00E6;lland Skagerrak Skaraborg Skardu Skiri Skopje Slavonia Slesvig Sligo Smederevo Smolensk Sm&#x00E5;lenene Soba Socotra Sofala Sofia Sokoki Solikamsk Soltanieh Solvychegodsk Somerset Somogy Sonargaon Songo Songqu Songye Sonpur Sopron Soria Soroka Soto Sotuta Soumelpur Sousse Soyo Sozak Spi&#x0161; Spokane Squamish Srikakulam Stadacona Stade Stanovoy Starodub Stavanger Steiermark Sternberg Stettin Stockholm Stolp Storavan Storsj&#x00F6;n Stralsund Straubing Suakin Sucre Sudayr Suez Sugla Sukhothai Sula Sulimaniyeh Sultan&#x00F6;n&#x00FC; Sulu Suma Sumba Sumbawa Sunderbans Sundgau Suo Surabaya Surat Surguja Surgut Suriname Suruga Sus Susquehanna Sussex Sutherland Suwayda Suwon Suzdal Suzhou Swellendam Syghnak Syracuse Syrmia Szabolcs Szolnok S&#x00F3;\&apos;taeo\&apos;o Tabas Tabayin Tabriz Tabuk Tabwa Tachi Tachienlu Tadla Tadmekka Tadmor Tadoussac Tafilalt Tagant Tagloc Taif Taining Taiyuan Taiz Tajhari Tajima Tajura Talas Tamanthi Tamaroa Tamaulipas Tambov Tana Tandil Tanga Tangiers Tango Tanjore Taozhou Taqamkuk Tarabulus Tarakan Taranaki Taraz Tarija Tarki Tarnovo Tarnow Tarragona Tarrana Tashkent Tataouine Taudeni Tauisk Taungoo Tauranga Tavastland Taveta Tavoy Taytay Tbilisi Tegali Teheran Tehuantepec Tehuelmapu Tekke Tekrur Teloloapan Temes Tenere Tenkodogo Tennessee Tepeacac Tepehuan Terek Terengganu Termes Termez Ternate Teruel Tete Tetyushi Teush Teyas Thalang Thalner Thana Thatta Thaungdut Theodoro Thessaly Thimpu Thubaqt Th&#x00FC;ringen Tiahuanaco Tianshui Tidore Tikhvin Tikrit Timaru Timbuktu Timiskaming Timon Timucua Tingzhou Tioh&#x00E4;rad Tionontate Tirhut Tirol Tiruchirappalli Tirunelveli Titteri Tiwi Tizapan Tkaronto Tlapanec Tlaxcala Tlemcen Tlingit Toboso Tobykty Tochtepec Togdheer Tohancapan Tohome Tokachi Tokat Toledo Tomsk Tondainadu Tondo Tonga Tongren Tonkawa Toront&#x00E1;l Toropets Tortkara Tortuga Torzhok Tosa Totma Totorames Touggourt Toulouse Touraine Trakai Tranqebar Trarza Travunia Trebizond Trencin Trent Treviso Trier Trincomale Trinidad Tripoli Tripura Troyes Trubchevsk Tr&#x00F8;ndelag Tsaidam Tsetserleg Tsilhoqotin Tsimihety Tsimshian Tsisistas Tsurphu Tuat Tuchola Tucuman Tucume Tucurui Tuintsund&#x00E9; Tula Tulangbewang Tullucan Tumbes Tumbuka Tun Tunis Tunja Tura Turda Turkana Turkestan Turov Turpan Turrbal Turubah Turukhan Tuscarora Tuskegee Tutelo Tuvalu Tuwan Tver Tyn Tyne Tyrone Tyumen Tziccoac T&#x00EE;rgoviste Uaymil Ucayali Uchamin Uckermark Udayagiri Ude Udi Udmurtia Ugo Ujjain Ukek Ula Ulaangom Ulch Uliastai Ulm Ulster Uluas Umarkot Umatilla Umbria Umung Unamakik Unami Ungava Upemba Urbino Urfa Urgell Urgench Urgoma Urkan Urmia Uruguay Urumqi Urzhar Ust-Kut Ust-Sysolsk Ust-Vym Ustyug Ustyurt Ustyuzhna Utrecht Utsetha Utva Uyapari Uzen Uzkend Vagad Vah Valois Val&#x00E8;ncia Van Vannetais Vanni Vanuatu Varanasi Varasd Vatomandry Vaud Veda-Suvar Velanadu Velsk Venad Venezia Veraguas Verkhoyansk Verona Vestbygden Vestjylland Vetluga Viatka Viborg Vidin Vientiane Vijaya Vijayanagar Vilna Visoki Vitebsk Vivarais Vizcaya Vlaanderen Vladimir Vlor&#x00EB; Vogtland Volhynia Vologda Voronezh Vyazma V&#x00E4;nern V&#x00E4;rmland V&#x00E4;sterbotten V&#x00E4;ttern Wabash Waccamaw Waco Waddai Wadjuk Wagadu Wagadugu Wahpekute Wahpeton Waichow Waihopai Waitaha Wake Waldst&#x00E4;tte Wallis Wampanoag Wankapampa Wappus Warangal Warmia Warri Warsheikh Warszawa Washim Wasit Waxhaw Wayao Wea Weagamow Welayta Wenden Wenzhou Werder Wergaia Westfalen Whangarei Whydah Wichita Wien Winnebago Winnipeg Wiradjuri Wismar Wittenberg Wizna Wollo Wolof Wolystoq Wonju Wuchang Wuding Wukari Wulgurukaba Wuling Wurundjeri Wusta Wyandot W&#x00FC;rttemberg W&#x00FC;rzburg Xhosa Xi\&apos;an Xiangyang Xiankhouang Xicallanco Xining Xocnochco Xuanhua Xuzhou Yabrin Yadkin Yaik Yaka Yakima Yakut Yakutat Yamal Yamasee Yamato Yamdena Yamethin Yan\&apos;an Yanbu Yangzhou Yankton Yanktonai Yanzhou Yao Yaqui Yaran Yareyu Yarkand Yarmanka</Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Keywords2">AAC ABB ABE ACH ADA ADE ADU AFA AFG AHM AIR AJU AKK AKM AKT ALB ALE ALG ALH ALO ALS AMA AMG ANH ANN ANS ANT ANU ANZ APA APU AQU ARA ARB ARD ARK ARL ARM ARP ART ARW ASA ASH ASI ASK ASS AST ATH ATJ AUG AUS AUV AVA AVI AVR AYD AYU AZT Aachen Abenaki Aceh Achaea Adal Aden Afghanistan Ahmadnagar Ahmednagar Ainu Air Ajam Ajuuraan Akamatsu Albania Alen&#x00E7;on Algiers Alodia Alsace Amago Andalusia Andhra Ando Anhalt Anizah Annam Ansbach Antemoro Apache Apu Aquileia Arabia Aragon Arakan Arapaho Arawak Ardabil Ardalan Armagnac Armenia Artillery Asakura Ashanti Ashikaga Assam Assiniboine Astrakhan Athens Augsburg Aussa Australia Austria Auvergne Ava Avaria Avignon Aydin Ayutthaya Aztec BAD BAH BAL BAN BAR BAS BAV BDA BEI BEJ BEN BER BEY BGA BGL BHA BHT BHU BIJ BLA BLI BLM BLO BND BNG BNJ BNY BOH BON BOS BOU BPI BPR BRA BRB BRE BRI BRR BRT BRU BRZ BSG BSH BSR BST BTI BTL BTN BTS BTU BUG BUK BUL BUR BUU BYZ Baden Baghelkhand Baglana Bahmanis Bali Baluchistan Banjar Banten Bar Baroda Bashkiria Basra Bastar Bavaria Beja Beloozero Bengal Benin Berar Berry Betsimisaraka Bey Bharat Bhutan Biapas Bijapur Bishnupur Bitlis Blackfoot Blambangan Bohemia Bonoman Bosnia Bourbonnais Brabant Brandenburg Brazil Bremen Brittany Brunei Brunswick Buganda Buha Bukhara Bulgaria Bundelkhand Bunyoro Burgundy Burundi Buryatia Busoga Buton Butua Butuan Byzantium CAB CAD CAH CAM CAN CAR CAS CAT CAV CBA CCQ CDL CEB CEP CEY CGS CHA CHC CHD CHE CHG CHH CHI CHK CHL CHM CHO CHP CHR CHU CHV CHY CIR CJA CKW CLA CLM CMI CMP CND CNK CNN COC COL COM COR CRA CRB CRE CRI CRN CRO CRT CSH CSK CSU CUA CXI CYA CYI CYP CZH Caddo Cah Cajamarca Calchaqui Calicut Canada Candar Car Carib Carnatic Castile Catalonia Cavalry Cebu Chachapoya Chagatai Chahar Champa Champagne Champasak Chanda Changsheng Charca Charrua Chavchuveny Chernigov Cherokee Cheyenne Chiba Chickasaw Chile Chimu Chinook Choctaw Chokwe Chosokabe Chu Chukchi Circassia Cirebon Clanricarde Cleves Cocomes Colima Colla Cologne Colombia Comanche Commonwealth Corfu Cornwall Corsica Cree Creek Crete Crimea Croatia Cusco Cyprus DAH DAI DAM DAN DAR DAU DAW DEC DGB DGL DHU DLH DMK DMS DNG DNZ DTE DTI DTT DUL DUR Dagbon Dahomey Dali Damot Dang Danzig Darfur Date Dauphine Dawasir Deccan Delhi Demak Denmark Desmond Dhundhar Dithmarschen Djerid Dongola Doti Dulkadir Durrani EFR EGY ENA ENG EPI ERE EST ETH ETR Egypt England Ennarea Epirus Eretna Estonia Ethiopia Etruria FAD FEO FER FEZ FIN FLA FLY FOI FOX FRA FRI FRN FRS FUJ FUL FZA Fadl Fars Ferghana Ferrara Fez Fezzan Finland Flanders Florence Foix Fox France Frankfurt Friesland Fujiwara Fulo Funj GAL GAZ GBR GDW GEL GEN GEO GER GHD GHR GLE GLH GNG GOC GOL GOT GRA GRE GRJ GRK GRM GUA GUG GUJ GUY GWA Gaeldom Galicia Galicia&#x2013;Volhynia Garha Garhwal Garjat Gascony Gazikumukh Geledi Gelre Genoa Georgia Germany Germiyan Gilan Gingee Golkonda Gorkha Gotland Granada Greece Guarani Guge Gujarat Gwalior HAB HAD HAI HAM HAN HAR HAS HAT HAU HDA HDR HDY HED HES HIN HJA HJO HLR HMI HOB HOD HOL HSA HSC HSE HSI HSK HSN HTK HUA HUN HUR Haasa Habsan Hadiya Hadoti Hadramut Haida Hainaut Haiti Haixi Hamburg Hanover Harar Has Hatakeyama Hausa Hejaz Hesse Hindustan Hobyo Hojo Holland Holstein Hormuz Hosokawa Hsenwi Hsipaw Huai Hungary Huron Huyla ICE ICM IDR IKE ILL IME IMG INC INF IRE IRO IRQ ISF ISK ITA ITO ITZ Iceland Ichma Idar Ikeda Illiniwek Imagawa Imereti Imerina Inca Infantry Iraq Ireland Iroquois Isfahan Isshiki Italy Ito Itza JAI JAJ JAM JAN JAP JFN JGD JIM JIN JJI JLV JML JMN JNN JNP JOH JOL JPR JSL Jaffna Jaisalmer Jam Jangladesh Janjiro Japan Jaunpur Jenn&#x00E9; Jerusalem Jeypore Jhalavad Jharkhand Jianzhou Jimma Jin Johor Jolof Jumla Junagarh KAC KAF KAL KAM KAN KAR KAS KAT KAZ KBA KBO KBU KED KGR KHA KHD KHI KHM KHO KIC KID KIE KIK KIO KJH KKC KLD KLE KLH KLK KLN KLP KLT KMC KMN KMT KND KNG KNI KNO KOC KOI KOJ KOK KOL KON KOR KRA KRC KRK KRL KRM KRW KRY KSD KSH KSJ KTB KTS KTU KUB KUR KUT KZB KZH Kaabu Kabylia Kachar Kaffa Kalahandi Kale Kalinjar Kalpi Kalundwe Kamchadals Kandy Kangra Kano Karagwe Karaman Karelia Kasanje Kashmir Kathmandu Katsina Kazakh Kazan Kazembe Kedah Keladi Keonhjar Kerman Khalkha Kham Khandesh Kharabakh Khiva Khmer Khodynt Khorasan Khoshuud Kiche Kiev Kikondja Kikuchi Kildare Kilwa Kiowa Kitabatake Koch Kochin Kolathunad Kong Kongo Kono Korchin Korea Kotte Krakow Kuba Kumaon Kurland Kutai Kutch LAN LAP LAU LDK LDU LEB LEI LEN LFA LIE LIG LIT LIV LNA LND LNG LNO LOA LOI LON LOR LOU LRI LUA LUB LUC LUN LUW LUX LVA LWA LXA Ladakh Lanao Lanfang Lebanon Leinster Lenape Le&#x00F3;n Liang Liege Ligor Limbuwan Lithuania Livonia Loango Lorraine Louisiana Luba Lucca Lunda Lundu Luristan Luwu Luxembourg L&#x00FC;beck L&#x00FC;neburg MAB MAD MAE MAG MAH MAI MAJ MAK MAL MAM MAN MAR MAS MAW MAY MAZ MBA MBL MCA MCH MCM MDA MDI MED MEI MEM MEN MER MEW MEX MFA MFL MFY MGD MGR MHR MHX MIK MIN MIR MIX MJE MJZ MKA MKL MKP MKS MKU MLB MLC MLI MLK MLO MLW MMA MMI MNA MNG MNI MNS MOD MOE MOL MON MOR MOS MPA MPC MPH MRA MRE MRI MSA MSI MSY MTH MTR MUG MUL MUN MUR MVA MYA MYR MYS MZB Macina Madurai Madyas Maeda Magdeburg Maguindanao Mahafaly Mahican Mahra Mainz Majapahit Majeerteen Makassar Makua Makuria Makwanpur Malacca Malaya Maldives Mali Malindi Malta Malwa Mamluks Manchu Manipur Mann Mantua Mapuche Marathas Maravi Maregheh Marehan Marwar Mataram Maya Maynila Mazandaran Mazovia Meath Mecklenburg Medina Meissen Memmingen Mentese Mewar Mewat Mexico Miami Miao Mikhlaf Mikmaq Milan Min Ming Mixtec Modena Mogadishu Moldavia Mombasa Mongolia Montenegro Montferrat Moravia Morea Mori Morocco Mossi Mughals Muisca Multan Munster Murom Muscovy Mushasha Mutapa Mysore Mzab M&#x00FC;nster NAG NAH NAJ NAP NAT NAV NAX NDO NED NEV NGA NGP NIZ NJR NKO NNG NOG NOL NOR NOV NPL NRM NSA NUB NUM NUP NVR NZH Nagaur Nagpur Najd Najran Nanbu Naples Nassau Natives Navajo Navanagar Navarra Naxos Ndongo Nepal Netherlands Nevers Ning Nitra Nkore Nogai Normandy Northumberland Norway Novgorod Nupe Nuremberg ODA ODH OGS OIR OJI OKA OLD OMA ORD ORI ORL ORM OSA OTM OTT OUC OYO Oda Odoyev Offaly Ogasawara Oirat Ojibwe Oldenburg Oman Orissa Orleans Ormond Osage Otomo Ottawa Ottomans Ouchi Oudh Oyo PAL PAN PAP PAR PAT PAW PCJ PEG PEQ PER PEU PGR PGS PHA PIC PIM PIR PIS PLB PLC PLT POL POM POR POT POW PRB PRD PRG PRK PRM PRO PRU PSA PSK PTA PTE PTG PTI PTL PTT PUE PUN Pacajes Pagarruyung Palembang Palitana Pangasinan Paraguay Parlakhimidi Parma Pasai Pate Patiala Patna Pattani Pawnee Pegu Pequot Perak Perm Persia Peru Picardy Pima Pirates Pisa Poland Polotsk Pomerania Porbandar Portugal Potawatomi Potiguara Powhatan Prome Provence Prussia Pskov Pueblo Punjab QAR QAS QIC QIN QNG QOM QTO QUE Qasim Qi Qin Qing Quebec Quito RAG RAJ RAM RAS REB REX RFR RIG RJK RJP RMN RMP ROM RSO RTT RUM RUS RVA RWA RYA RYU RZW Ragusa Rajkot Rajputana Ramazan Rassids Ratanpur Ravensburg Rebels Rex Riga Rohilkhand Romania Rostov Russia Ruthenia Rwanda Ryazan Ryukyu R&#x00FB;m SAK SAL SAR SAV SAX SBA SBP SCA SCO SDY SER SFA SHA SHL SHM SHN SHO SHR SHU SHY SIB SIC SIE SIL SIO SIS SKA SKK SLN SLO SLZ SME SMI SMO SMZ SND SOA SOF SOK SON SOS SPA SPI SRG SRH SRM SRU SRV SST STK STY SUK SUL SUN SUS SWE SWI SYG SYO SYR Sadiya Sakalava Salish Salzburg Sambalpur Samtskhe Sapmi Sardinia Sardinia-Piedmont Saruhan Satake Savoy Saxe-Lauenburg Saxony Scandinavia Scotland Segu Semien Serbia Shammar Shan Sharjah Shawnee Shewa Shiba Shimazu Shirvan Shoni Shoshone Shu Shun Siak Sibir Sicily Siena Sikkim Silesia Sindh Sioux Sirhind Sirmur Sistan Sligo Smolensk Sofala Sokoto Songhai Soran Soyo Spain Styria Sukhothai Sulu Sunda Surguja Sus Susquehannock Sweden Switzerland Syria TAB TAC TAI TAR TAU TBK TBR TDO TER TEU TFL TGT THU TIB TID TIM TIR TKD TKG TKI TLA TLC TLG TLX TMB TNG TNJ TOK TOT TOU TPA TPQ TPR TRA TRE TRI TRP TRS TRT TRV TRY TTI TUA TUN TUR TUS TVE TYO TYR Tabriz Tachibana Tafilalt Taira Takeda Tang Tanjore Tapuia Tarascan Taungu Telingana Ternate Theodoro Thomond Thuringia Tibet Tidore Timbuktu Timurids Tirhut Tirol Tlapanec Tlaxcala Tlemcen Toki Tokugawa Tondo Tonkin Totonac Touggourt Toulouse Transoxiana Transylvania Travanacore Trebizond Trier Tripoli Tripura Tsang Tsutsui Tumbuka Tunis Tupinamba Tupiniquim Tuscany Tver Tyo Tyrconnell Tyrone U UBH UES UKR ULM ULS URB USA UTN UTR UTS Uesugi Ulm Ulster Urbino Utrecht Utsunomiya Uzbek VEN VER VIE VIJ VLA VND VNZ VOL Venad Venezuela Venice Verden Vientiane Vijayanagar Vladimir WAL WAR WBG WCR WES WIC WKA WLS WLY WUR WUU Wales Wallachia Wanka Warsangali Welayta Westphalia Wichita Wu Wurttemberg Wurzburg XIA XIU Xi Xia Xiu YAK YAN YAO YAR YAS YAT YEM YMN YOR YUA YUE YZD Yaka Yamana Yan Yao Yarkand Yaroslavl Yas Yashilkul Yasuj Yatenga Yavapai Yawnghwe Yawuri Yazd Yazoo Yedisan Yedishkul Yehe Yelets Yemen Yeren Yerevan Yi Yichang Yokuts Yola Yolngu Yongping Yopitzinco York Yscani Yuan Yuanling Yuchi Yue Yugan Yuin Yuki Yukjin Yumen Yunnan Yuriev Yurimaguas Yustaga ZAF ZAN ZAP ZAZ ZEN ZIM ZUN ZZZ Zabid Zacatecas Zacatula Zagreb Zagros Zamboanga Zamfara Zanjan Zanzibar Zaporozhia Zaporozhie Zapotec Zaragoza Zaranj Zaraza Zarmaganda Zasagt Zaysan Zazzau Zeeland Zeila Zempl&#x00E9;n Zen Zeta Zhangye Zhending Zhenjiang Zhenyuan Zhetyru Zhou Zhytomyr Zigua Zimbabwe Zubtsov Zufra Zumbo Zunghar Zuni Zuwarah Z&#x00FC;rich &#x00C5;bo &#x00C5;land &#x00C9;vora &#x00D6;resund &#x00D6;sel &#x00D6;sterbotten &#x00D6;sterg&#x00F6;tland &#x00D8;stjylland</Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Keywords3"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Keywords4"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Keywords5"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Keywords6"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Keywords7"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Keywords8"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Delimiters">00(( Event: Decision: )) 01 02((EOL)) 03. 04 05(( EOL )) 06[messagehandler 07 08] 09EVE: 10 11(( EOL )) 12Error 13 14(( &gt;&gt; )) 15 16 17 18 19 20 21 22 23</Keywords>
        </KeywordLists>
        <Styles>
            <WordsStyle name="DEFAULT" fgColor="000000" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="0" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="COMMENTS" fgColor="000000" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="0" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="LINE COMMENTS" fgColor="6A6A6A" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="0" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="NUMBERS" fgColor="000000" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="0" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="KEYWORDS1" fgColor="004080" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="1" fontSize="9" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="KEYWORDS2" fgColor="004080" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="1" fontSize="9" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="KEYWORDS3" fgColor="000000" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="0" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="KEYWORDS4" fgColor="000000" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="0" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="KEYWORDS5" fgColor="000000" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="0" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="KEYWORDS6" fgColor="000000" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="0" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="KEYWORDS7" fgColor="000000" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="0" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="KEYWORDS8" fgColor="000000" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="0" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="OPERATORS" fgColor="000000" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="0" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="FOLDER IN CODE1" fgColor="000000" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="0" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="FOLDER IN CODE2" fgColor="000000" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="0" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="FOLDER IN COMMENT" fgColor="000000" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="0" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="DELIMITERS1" fgColor="005900" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="0" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="DELIMITERS2" fgColor="000000" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="0" nesting="117702655" />
            <WordsStyle name="DELIMITERS3" fgColor="000000" bgColor="DDDDDD" fontName="" fontStyle="0" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="DELIMITERS4" fgColor="CA00CA" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="0" fontSize="10" nesting="261136" />
            <WordsStyle name="DELIMITERS5" fgColor="FF0000" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="0" nesting="32" />
            <WordsStyle name="DELIMITERS6" fgColor="000000" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="0" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="DELIMITERS7" fgColor="000000" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="0" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="DELIMITERS8" fgColor="000000" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="0" nesting="0" />
        </Styles>
    </UserLang>
</NotepadPlus>
