<NotepadPlus>
    <UserLang name="Paradox Log" ext="" udlVersion="2.1">
        <Settings>
            <Global caseIgnored="yes" allowFoldOfComments="no" foldCompact="no" forcePureLC="0" decimalSeparator="0" />
            <Prefix Keywords1="no" Keywords2="no" Keywords3="no" Keywords4="no" Keywords5="no" Keywords6="no" Keywords7="no" Keywords8="no" />
        </Settings>
        <KeywordLists>
            <Keywords name="Comments">00merchant 00diplomat 01 02 03 04</Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Numbers, prefix1"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Numbers, prefix2"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Numbers, extras1"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Numbers, extras2"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Numbers, suffix1"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Numbers, suffix2"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Numbers, range"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Operators1"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Operators2">&quot;Military Alliance&quot; &quot;Royal Marriage&quot;</Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Folders in code1, open"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Folders in code1, middle"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Folders in code1, close"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Folders in code2, open"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Folders in code2, middle"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Folders in code2, close"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Folders in comment, open"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Folders in comment, middle"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Folders in comment, close"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Keywords1">&quot;East Frisia&quot; &quot;East Frisian&quot; &quot;Nizhny Novgorod&quot; &quot;Nizhny Novgorodian&quot; &quot;United Central America&quot; &quot;Livonian Order&quot; &quot;Central American&quot; &quot;Holy Roman Empire&quot; &quot;Aq Qoyunlu&quot; &quot;Dai Viet&quot; &quot;Great Britain&quot; &quot;Great Horde&quot; &quot;Kanem Bornu&quot; &quot;The Knights&quot; &quot;La Plata&quot; &quot;Lan Na&quot; &quot;Luang Prabang&quot; &quot;Lan Xang&quot; &quot;The Palatinate&quot; &quot;The Papal State&quot; &quot;Qara Qoyunlu&quot; &quot;Teutonic Order&quot; &quot;United States&quot; &quot;Deva Bengal&quot; &quot;Aq Qoyunlu&quot; &quot;Chagatai Khanate&quot; &quot;Dai Vietan&quot; &quot;Great Horde&quot; &quot;Kanem Bornuan&quot; &quot;La Platan&quot; &quot;Lan Nan&quot; &quot;Luang Prabangi&quot; &quot;Lan Xangi&quot; &quot;Qara Qoyunlu&quot; &quot;Rebel Alliance&quot; &quot;Deva Bengali&quot; &quot;Rewa Kantha&quot; &quot;Rewa Kanthi&quot; &quot;Kara Del&quot; &quot;Sarig Yogir&quot; &quot;Muan Phuang&quot; &quot;Mong Yang&quot; &quot;Beta Israel&quot; &quot;Roman Empire&quot; &quot;Golden Horde&quot; &quot;Hisn Kayfa&quot; &quot;Hisn Kayfan&quot; &quot;The Isles&quot; &#x000D;&#x000A;&#x000D;&#x000A;&quot;East Frisia.&quot; &quot;East Frisian.&quot; &quot;Nizhny Novgorod.&quot; &quot;Nizhny Novgorodian.&quot; &quot;United Central America.&quot; &quot;Livonian Order.&quot; &quot;Central American.&quot; &quot;Holy Roman Empire.&quot; &quot;Aq Qoyunlu.&quot; &quot;Dai Viet.&quot; &quot;Great Britain.&quot; &quot;Great Horde.&quot; &quot;Kanem Bornu.&quot; &quot;The Knights.&quot; &quot;La Plata.&quot; &quot;Lan Na.&quot; &quot;Luang Prabang.&quot; &quot;Lan Xang.&quot; &quot;The Palatinate.&quot; &quot;The Papal State.&quot; &quot;Qara Qoyunlu.&quot; &quot;Teutonic Order.&quot; &quot;United States.&quot; &quot;Deva Bengal.&quot; &quot;Aq Qoyunlu.&quot; &quot;Chagatai Khanate.&quot; &quot;Dai Vietan.&quot; &quot;Great Horde.&quot; &quot;Kanem Bornuan.&quot; &quot;La Platan.&quot; &quot;Lan Nan.&quot; &quot;Luang Prabangi.&quot; &quot;Lan Xangi.&quot; &quot;Qara Qoyunlu.&quot; &quot;Rebel Alliance.&quot; &quot;Deva Bengali.&quot; &quot;Rewa Kantha.&quot; &quot;Rewa Kanthi.&quot; &quot;Kara Del.&quot; &quot;Sarig Yogir.&quot; &quot;Muan Phuang.&quot; &quot;Mong Yang.&quot; &quot;Beta Israel.&quot; &quot;Roman Empire.&quot; &quot;Golden Horde.&quot; &quot;Hisn Kayfa.&quot; &quot;Hisn Kayfan.&quot; &quot;The Isles.&quot;</Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Keywords2">BAR Bar Barroise HSA L&#x00FC;beck L&#x00FC;beckian SMO Smolensk Smolenskian MUR Murom Muromian NZH VLA Vladimir Vladimiran LAU Saxe-Lauenburg Lauenburgian AAC Aachen Aachener ALE Alen&#x00E7;on AUG Augsburg Augsburgian ULM Ulm Ulmer Tairan Fuijiwaran Tachibanan MSA Malaya Malayan HIN Hindustan Hindustani BHA Bharat Bharathi CAM DNZ Danzig ETR Etruria FRN Frankfurt HAT Haiti IRQ Iraq KHO Khorasan KRA Krakow LIV NAP Naples PRG Paraguay QIN Qin RFR Nanbu SOK Sokoto SPI Sardinia-Piedmont SYR Syria VNZ Venezuela WES Westphalia WUU Wu XIA Xia Danzigian Etrurian Frankfurtian Haitian Iraqi Khorasani Krakowian Livonian Neapolitan Paraguayan Qin Nanbuan Sokototian Sardinian Syrian Venezuelan Westfalian Wun Xian RMN Romania Romanian AYD Aydin AQU Aquileia BYZ Byzantium MAJ Majapahit MEI Meissen SUK Sukhothai Aydin Aquileian Byzantine Majapahit Meissen Sukhothai GAL Galicia Galician PLT Polotsk Polotskian SCA Scandinavia Scandinavian ACH Achaea Achaean KOJ Jerusalem Jerusalemite BER Berry Berrian HLR SRU Saruhan Saruhani MEN Mentese RAM Ramazan Ramazani EPI Epirus Epirote ADE Aden AKK ALB Albania ALG Algiers ALH Haasa ALS Alsace AMG Armagnac ANH Anhalt ANN Annam ANS Ansbach ARA Aragon ARK Arakan ARM Armenia ASH Ashanti ASS Assam AST Astrakhan ATH Athens ATJ Aceh AUV Auvergne AVI Avignon AYU Ayutthaya AZT Aztec BAD Baden BLI Bali BAN Banten BAL Baluchistan BAV Bavaria BEI Brunei BEN Benin BHU Bhutan BIJ Bijapur BND Bundelkhand BNG Bengal BOH Bohemia BOS Bosnia BOU Bourbonnais BRA Brandenburg BRB Brabant BRE Bremen BRI Brittany BRR Berar BRU Brunswick BRZ Brazil BUL Bulgaria BUR Burgundy CAN Canada CAS Castile CAT Catalonia CEP Corfu CHA Champa CHE Cherokee CHG Chagatai CHK Champasak CHL Chile CHM Chimu CHP Champagne CND Candar COL Colombia CNN Clanricarde COR Corsica CRE Creek CRI Crimea CRN Cornwall CRO Croatia CRT Crete CYP Cyprus DAI DAN Denmark DAU Dauphine DLH Delhi DUL Dulkadir DUR Durrani ENG England ETH Ethiopia FER Ferrara FEZ Fez FIN Finland FLA Flanders FOI Foix FRA France FRI Friesland GBR GDW Gondwana GEL Gelre GEN Genoa GEO Georgia GER Germany GOL GOT Gotland GRA Granada GRE Greece GUJ Gujarat GUY Gascony HAB Austria HAI Hainaut HAM Hamburg HAN Hanover HAU Hausa HED Hejaz HES Hesse HOL Holland HUN Hungary HUR Huron INC Inca IRE Ireland IRO Iroquois ITA Italy JAP Japan KAR Karaman KAZ Kazan KBO KHA Mongolia KHD Khandesh KHI Khiva KHM Khmer KLE Cleves KNI KOK Ferghana KOL Cologne KON Kongo KOR Korea KRK Carnatic KSH Kashmir KUR Kurland KZH Kazakh LAN Florence LAP LEI Leinster LIE Liege LIT Lithuania LNA LOA Loango LOR Lorraine LOU Louisiana LUA LUN L&#x00FC;neburg LUX Luxembourg LXA MAD Madurai MAG Magdeburg MAI Mainz MAL Mali MAM Mamluks MAN Mantua MAY Maya MAZ Mazovia MCH Manchu MEX Mexico MKL Mecklenburg MKS Makassar MLC Malacca MLO Milan MLW Malwa MNG Ming MNS Thomond MOD Modena MOE Morea MOL Moldavia MON Montenegro MOR Morocco MOS Muscovy MTR Mataram MUG Mughals MUN M&#x00FC;nster MYS Mysore NAJ Najd NAV Navarra NAX Naxos NED Netherlands NEV Nevers NOG Nogai NOL Northumberland NOR Norway NOV Novgorod NPL Nepal NRM Normandy NUB Funj ODH Oudh OIR Oirat OLD Oldenburg OMA Oman ORI Orissa ORL Orleans OYO Oyo PAL PAP PAR Parma PAT Pattani PEG Pegu PER Persia PEU Peru PIC Picardy PIS Pisa POL Poland POM Pomerania POR Portugal PRO Provence PRU Prussia PSK Pskov PUN Punjab QAR QAS Qasim QUE Quebec RAG Ragusa RAJ Rajputana REB Rebels RIG Riga RUS Russia RYA Ryazan RYU Ryukyu SAR Sardinia SAV Savoy SAX Saxony SCO Scotland SER Serbia SHA Shawnee SHL Holstein SHR Sharjah SHY Uzbek SIB Sibir SIC Sicily SIE Siena SIL Silesia SLZ Salzburg SND Sind SOF Segu SON Songhai SPA Spain SST Shan STY Styria SUL Sulu SWE Sweden SWI Switzerland TAU Taungu TEU THU Thuringia TIB Tibet TIM Timurids TIR Tirol TOK Tonkin TOU Toulouse TRA Transylvania TRE Trebizond TRI Trier TRP Tripoli TRV Travanacore TUN Tunis TUR Ottomans TUS Tuscany TVE Tver TYR Tyrone UKR Ruthenia URB Urbino USA UTR Utrecht WAL Wallachia WBG Wurzburg VEN Venice VIE Vientiane VIJ Vijayanagar WLS Wales WUR Wurttemberg YAR Yaroslavl YOR Andhra ZAP Zapotec ZAZ Zaporozhie ZIM Mutapa NIZ BAS Ahmadnagar NAT Natives PIR Pirates Piratic Native Adalan Adeni Albanian Algerian Haasalese Alsatian Armagnac Anhaltian Annamese Ansbachian Aragonese Arakani Armenian Ashanti Assamese Astrakhani Athenian Atjehan Auvergnese Avignonese Ayutthayan Aztec Badenese Balinese Banteni Baluchistani Bavarian Bruneian Beninese Bhutanese Bijapuri Bundelkhandi Bengalese Bohemian Bosnian Bourbonnean Brandenburgian Brabantian Bremian Breton Berari Brunswickian Brazilian Bulgarian Burgundian Canadian Castilian Catalonian Corfuan Champani Cherokee Champassaki Chilean Chimu Champagnian Candari Colombian Clanricarde Corsican Creek Crimean Cornish Croatian Cretan Cypriot Danish Dauphinese Delhian Dulkadiri Durrani English Ethiopian Ferraranese Fezian Finnish Flemish Foixian French Frisian British Gondwanese Gelren Genoese Georgian German Gotlander Granadan Greek Gujarati Gascon Austrian Hainautian Hamburgian Hanoverian Hausan Hejazi Hessian Dutch Hungarian Huron Incan Irish Iroquois Italian Japanese Karamanese Kazani Mongol Khandeshi Khivan Cambodian Clevian Knights Ferghanan Colognian Kongolese Korean Carnatic Kashmiri Kurlandian Kazakhi Florentine Leinster Liegian Lithuanian Loangoni Lorrainian Louisianan Luneburgian Luxembourgian Madurain Magdeburgian Mainzian Malian Mamlukean Mantuan Mayan Mazovian Manchurian Mexican Mecklenburgian Makassari Malaccan Milanese Malwani Ming Thomondian Modenan Morean Moldavian Montenegrin Moroccan Muscovite Matarami Mughal M&#x00FC;nster Mysorian Najdi Navarran Naxosian Dutch Neveriase Nogai Northumbrian Norwegian Novgorodian Nepalese Norman Funj Oudh Oirat Oldenburgian Omani Orissi Orleanaise Oyo Palatine Papal Parman Pattani Pegu Persian Peruvian Picardian Pisan Polish Pomeranian Portuguese Provencal Prussian Pskovian Punjabi Qasim Quebec Ragusan Rajputni Rigan Russian Ryazanian Ryukyuan Sardinian Savoyard Saxon Scottish Serbian Shawnee Holsteinian Sharjahi Uzbek Sibirian Sicilian Sienese Silesian Salzburgian Sindi Seguian Songhain Spanish Shan Styrian Sulu Swedish Swiss Taunguan Teutonic Thuringian Tibetan Timurid Tyrolean Tonkini Toulousian Transylvanian Trebizondian Trierian Tripolitanian Travanacori Tunisian Ottoman Tuscan Tverian Tyrone Ruthenian Urbinese American Utrechtian Wallachian Wurzburgian Venetian Vientianese Vijaynagari Welsh Wurttembergian Yaroslavlian Andhran Zapotec Zaporozhian Mutapan Ahmadnagari AMA Amago ASA Asakura CSK Chosokabe DTE Date HJO Hojo HSK Hosokawa HTK Hatakeyama IKE Ikeda IMG Imagawa MAE Maeda MRI Mori ODA Oda OTM Otomo OUC Ouchi SBA Shiba SMZ Shimazu TKD Takeda TKG Tokugawa UES Uesugi YMN Yamana Amago Asakura Chosokabe Date Hojo Hosokawa Hatakeyama Ikeda Imagawa Maeda Mori Oda Otomo Ouchi Shiba Shimazu Takeda Tokugawa Uesugi Yamana JNP Jaunpur MAW Marwar MER Mewar MUL Multan JAN Jangladesh GRJ Garjat GWA Gwalior DHU Dhundhar KLN Keladi MAB Malabar MEW Mewat BST Bastar JSL Jaisalmer KAC Kachar KMT Koch KGR Kangra KAT Kathiawar KOC Kochin AHM Ahmednagar BAH Bahmanis NAG Nagpur BDA Baroda GOC Golkonda MAR Marathas VND Venad DEC Deccan CZH Zhou CSH Shun CXI Xi JOL Jolof Jolofian Jaunpuri Marwari Mewari Multani Jangladeshi Garjati Gwaliori Dhundhari Keladi Malabari Mewati Bastari Jaisalmer Kachari Kochi Kangri Kathiawar Kochi Ahmednagari Bahmani Nagpuri Barodan Golkondan Maratha Venadi Deccani Zhou Shun Xi PLC Commonwealth PRM Perm Permian CEY Ceylon Ceylonese AFG Afghanistan Afghan QNG Qing ABE Abenaki APA Apache ASI Assiniboine BLA Blackfoot CAD Caddo CHI Chickasaw CHO Choctaw CHY Cheyenne COM Comanche FOX Fox ILL Illiniwek LEN Lenape MIK Mikmaq MMI Miami MAH Mahican NAH Navajo OJI Ojibwe OSA Osage OTT Ottawa PAW Pawnee PEQ Pequot PIM Pima POT Potawatomi POW Powhatan PUE Pueblo SIO Sioux SHO Shoshone SUS Susquehannock WCR Cree Abenaki Apache Assiniboine Blackfoot Caddoan Chickasaw Choctaw Cheyenne Comanche Fox Illiniwek Lenape Mikmaq Miami Mahican Navajo Ojibwe Osage Ottawa Pawnee Pequot Piman Potawatomi Powhatan Pueblo Sioux Shoshone Susquehannock Cree ZAN Kilwa Kilwan AJU Ajuuraan MBA Mombasa Mombasan MDI Mogadishu Mogadishan MLI Malindi Malindian SFA Sofala Sofalan EGY Egypt Egyptian BUK Bukhara Bukharan BGA Baglana Baglani BGL Bagelkhand Bagelkhandi CHD Chanda Chandi CMP GHR Garhwal Garhwali HAD Hadoti JAJ Habsan Habsani JFN Jaffna LDK Ladakh Ladakhi MLB Manipur Manipuri NGA Nagaur Nagauri NGP Jharkhand Jharkhandi PTA Patiala Patialan RMP Rohilkhand Rohilla SDY Sadiya Sadiyan TPR Tripura Tripuran TRT Tirhut Tirhuti CIR Circassia Circassian GAZ Gazikumukh Gazikumukhan IME Imereti Imeretian TAB Mazandaran Mazandarani MYR Yeren MHX Haixi KRC Korchin KLK Khalkha DGL Maldives Maldivian HMI ZUN Zunghar KAS Yarkand KSD Khoshuud SYG UTS U-tsang KAM Kham GUG Guge Gugi TMB Timbuktu Timbuktuan AIR Air MSI Mossi KTS Katsina Katsinan KAN Kano FUL Fulo Fulani BON Bonoman DAH Dahomey Dahomeyan DGB Dagbon Dagbani JNN Jenn&#x00E9; Jenn&#x00E9;an KBU Kaabu KNG Kong NUP Nupe YAO Yao YAT Yatenga ZAF Macina ZZZ Zazzau Zazzauan ARD Ardalan BHT Soran Sorani ERE Eretna Eretnid LEB Lebanon Lebanese MAK Makuria Makurian SHM Shammar Shammari ARB Arabia Arabian GRM Germiyan Germiyanid MPH LIG Ligor Ligori JOH Johor Johori KED Kedah PRK Perak Perakian HSE Hsenwi MYA AVA Ava Avan FEO Theodoro Theodorian VOL Galicia&#x2013;Volhynia Volhynian KIE Kiev Kievian CHR Chernigov Chernihiv CHU Chukchi Chukchian HOD Khodynt Khodyntian CHV Chavchuveny Chavchuvenian KMC Kamchadals Kamchadese BRT Buryatia Buriat BSH Bashkiria Bashkirian TLC Tlemcen Tlemceni MZB Mzab Mozabite TGT Touggourt Touggourtian GHD Djerid Djeridi FZA Fezzan Fezzani KBA Kabylia Kabyle SOS Sus Susian TFL Tafilalt Tafilalti ARP Arapaho Arapahoan CNK Chinook Chinookan COC Cocomes XIU Xiu HDA Haida ITZ Itza KIC Kiche KIO Kiowa MIX Mixtec Mixtecan SAL Salish Salishan TAR Tarascan Tzintzuntzani TLA Tlapanec Tlapanecan TLX Tlaxcala Tlaxcalan TOT Totonac WIC Wichita CLM Colima BLM Blambangan CRB Cirebon Cirebonese DMK Demak Demakan PGR Pagarruyung Pagarruyungan PLB Palembang Palembangan PSA Pasai SAK Siak Siakian SUN Sunda Sundanese MJZ Jianzhou SRV Shirvan Shirvani MIN Min YUE Yue SHU Shu NNG Ning CHC Chu TNG Tang QIC Qi YAN Yan JIN Jin LNG Liang HUA Huai CGS Changsheng CAB Carib Cariban LON Le&#x00F3;n Leonese ICM Ichma Ichman NUM Nuremberg Nuremberger AUS Australia Australian BTI Semien MTH Meath Meathian ADU Andalusia Andalusian MEM Memmingen Memminger VER Verden Verdner NSA Nassau RVA Ravensburg Ravensburger MFA Montferrat Montferratian LUC Lucca Luccan LVA Livonia Livonian EST Estonia Estonian SMI Sapmi Sami ORM Hormuz Hormuzi KRL Karelia Karelian JAI Malta Maltese KUB Kuba Kuban KLD Kalundwe YAK Yaka Yakan KZB Kazembe Kazemban KIK Kikondja CKW Chokwe Chokwan LND Lunda Lundan LUB Luba Luban KSJ Kasanje Kasanjean SYO Soyo Soyan TYO Tyo Tyoan BSG Busoga Busogan BNY Bunyoro Bunyoroan KRW Karagwe Karagwan BUG Buganda Bugandan RWA Rwanda Rwandan NKO Nkore Nkorian BUU Burundi Burundian UBH Buha Buhan MRA Maravi Maravian LDU Lundu Lundian TBK Tumbuka Tumbukan MKU Makua Makuan RZW Butua Butuan MIR Imerina Imerinan ANT Antemoro Antemorian SKA Sakalava Sakalavan MFY Mahafaly BTS Betsimisaraka Betsimisarakan ULS Ulster Ulstrian DMS Desmond ORD Ormond KID Kildare Kildarean MCM Munster FLY Offaly TRY Tyrconnell SLN Sligo Sligonian OKA Odoyev Odoyevan ICE Iceland Icelandic SLO Nitra Nitran HSC Gaeldom Gaelic ROM Roman DTT Dithmarschen Dithmarscher GLH BEJ Beja Bejan JIM Jimma Jimman WLY Welayta Welaytan DAM Damot Damotian HDY Hadiya Hadiyan SOA Shewa Shewan JJI Janjiro Janjiroan ENA Ennarea Ennarean ABB Dongola Dongolan AKM Akamatsu AKT Ando CBA Chiba ISK Isshiki ITO Ito KKC Kikuchi KNO Kono OGS Ogasawara SHN Shoni STK Satake TKI Toki UTN Utsunomiya TTI Tsutsui Akamatsu Ando Chiba Isshiki Ito Kikuchi Kono Ogasawara Shoni Satake Toki Utsunomiya Tsutsui ASK Ashikaga MVA Moravia Moravian YUA Yuan BLO Beloozero Beloozeroan RSO Rostov Rostovian MHR Mahra Mahri HDR Hadramut Hadramhi MDA Medina Medinan ANZ Anizah FAD Fadl Fadli YAS Yas Yasi RAS Rassids Rassid YEM Yemen Yemeni DAW Dawasir Dawasiri MFL Mikhlaf Mikhlafi NJR Najran Najrani HSN BTL Bitlis Bitlisi AVR Avaria Avarian MLK Kharabakh Kharabakhi SME Samtskhe Samtskhean ARL Ardabil Ardabili MSY Mushasha Mushashan RUM R&#x00FB;m R&#x00FB;mi KRY Gilan Gilani LRI Luristan Luristani SIS Sistan Sistani BPI Biapas Biapasi FRS Fars Farsi KRM Kerman Kermani YZD Yazd Yazdi ISF Isfahan Isfahani TBR Tabriz Tabrizi BSR Basra Basran MGR Maregheh Mareghehi QOM Ajam Ajami TRS Transoxiana Transoxianian MAS Madyas PGS Pangasinan TDO Tondo Tondoan MNA Maynila Maynilan CEB Cebu Cebuan BTU Butuan KTB Kitabatake KOI Mann Manx LOI EFR Hebridean &#x000D;&#x000A;&#x000D;&#x000A;BAR. Bar. Barroise. HSA. L&#x00FC;beck. L&#x00FC;beckian. SMO. Smolensk. Smolenskian. MUR. Murom. Muromian. NZH. VLA. Vladimir. Vladimiran. LAU. Saxe-Lauenburg. Lauenburgian. AAC. Aachen. Aachener. ALE. Alen&#x00E7;on. AUG. Augsburg. Augsburgian. ULM. Ulm. Ulmer. Tairan. Fuijiwaran. Tachibanan. MSA. Malaya. Malayan. HIN. Hindustan. Hindustani. BHA. Bharat. Bharathi. CAM. DNZ. Danzig. ETR. Etruria. FRN. Frankfurt. HAT. Haiti. IRQ. Iraq. KHO. Khorasan. KRA. Krakow. LIV. NAP. Naples. PRG. Paraguay. QIN. Qin. RFR. Nanbu. SOK. Sokoto. SPI. Sardinia-Piedmont. SYR. Syria. VNZ. Venezuela. WES. Westphalia. WUU. Wu. XIA. Xia. Danzigian. Etrurian. Frankfurtian. Haitian. Iraqi. Khorasani. Krakowian. Livonian. Neapolitan. Paraguayan. Qin. Nanbuan. Sokototian. Sardinian. Syrian. Venezuelan. Westfalian. Wun. Xian. RMN. Romania. Romanian. AYD. Aydin. AQU. Aquileia. BYZ. Byzantium. MAJ. Majapahit. MEI. Meissen. SUK. Sukhothai. Aydin. Aquileian. Byzantine. Majapahit. Meissen. Sukhothai. GAL. Galicia. Galician. PLT. Polotsk. Polotskian. SCA. Scandinavia. Scandinavian. ACH. Achaea. Achaean. KOJ. Jerusalem. Jerusalemite. BER. Berry. Berrian. HLR. SRU. Saruhan. Saruhani. MEN. Mentese. RAM. Ramazan. Ramazani. EPI. Epirus. Epirote. ADE. Aden. AKK. ALB. Albania. ALG. Algiers. ALH. Haasa. ALS. Alsace. AMG. Armagnac. ANH. Anhalt. ANN. Annam. ANS. Ansbach. ARA. Aragon. ARK. Arakan. ARM. Armenia. ASH. Ashanti. ASS. Assam. AST. Astrakhan. ATH. Athens. ATJ. Aceh. AUV. Auvergne. AVI. Avignon. AYU. Ayutthaya. AZT. Aztec. BAD. Baden. BLI. Bali. BAN. Banten. BAL. Baluchistan. BAV. Bavaria. BEI. Brunei. BEN. Benin. BHU. Bhutan. BIJ. Bijapur. BND. Bundelkhand. BNG. Bengal. BOH. Bohemia. BOS. Bosnia. BOU. Bourbonnais. BRA. Brandenburg. BRB. Brabant. BRE. Bremen. BRI. Brittany. BRR. Berar. BRU. Brunswick. BRZ. Brazil. BUL. Bulgaria. BUR. Burgundy. CAN. Canada. CAS. Castile. CAT. Catalonia. CEP. Corfu. CHA. Champa. CHE. Cherokee. CHG. Chagatai. CHK. Champasak. CHL. Chile. CHM. Chimu. CHP. Champagne. CND. Candar. COL. Colombia. CNN. Clanricarde. COR. Corsica. CRE. Creek. CRI. Crimea. CRN. Cornwall. CRO. Croatia. CRT. Crete. CYP. Cyprus. DAI. DAN. Denmark. DAU. Dauphine. DLH. Delhi. DUL. Dulkadir. DUR. Durrani. ENG. England. ETH. Ethiopia. FER. Ferrara. FEZ. Fez. FIN. Finland. FLA. Flanders. FOI. Foix. FRA. France. FRI. Friesland. GBR. GDW. Gondwana. GEL. Gelre. GEN. Genoa. GEO. Georgia. GER. Germany. GOL. GOT. Gotland. GRA. Granada. GRE. Greece. GUJ. Gujarat. GUY. Gascony. HAB. Austria. HAI. Hainaut. HAM. Hamburg. HAN. Hanover. HAU. Hausa. HED. Hejaz. HES. Hesse. HOL. Holland. HUN. Hungary. HUR. Huron. INC. Inca. IRE. Ireland. IRO. Iroquois. ITA. Italy. JAP. Japan. KAR. Karaman. KAZ. Kazan. KBO. KHA. Mongolia. KHD. Khandesh. KHI. Khiva. KHM. Khmer. KLE. Cleves. KNI. KOK. Ferghana. KOL. Cologne. KON. Kongo. KOR. Korea. KRK. Carnatic. KSH. Kashmir. KUR. Kurland. KZH. Kazakh. LAN. Florence. LAP. LEI. Leinster. LIE. Liege. LIT. Lithuania. LNA. LOA. Loango. LOR. Lorraine. LOU. Louisiana. LUA. LUN. L&#x00FC;neburg. LUX. Luxembourg. LXA. MAD. Madurai. MAG. Magdeburg. MAI. Mainz. MAL. Mali. MAM. Mamluks. MAN. Mantua. MAY. Maya. MAZ. Mazovia. MCH. Manchu. MEX. Mexico. MKL. Mecklenburg. MKS. Makassar. MLC. Malacca. MLO. Milan. MLW. Malwa. MNG. Ming. MNS. Thomond. MOD. Modena. MOE. Morea. MOL. Moldavia. MON. Montenegro. MOR. Morocco. MOS. Muscovy. MTR. Mataram. MUG. Mughals. MUN. M&#x00FC;nster. MYS. Mysore. NAJ. Najd. NAV. Navarra. NAX. Naxos. NED. Netherlands. NEV. Nevers. NOG. Nogai. NOL. Northumberland. NOR. Norway. NOV. Novgorod. NPL. Nepal. NRM. Normandy. NUB. Funj. ODH. Oudh. OIR. Oirat. OLD. Oldenburg. OMA. Oman. ORI. Orissa. ORL. Orleans. OYO. Oyo. PAL. PAP. PAR. Parma. PAT. Pattani. PEG. Pegu. PER. Persia. PEU. Peru. PIC. Picardy. PIS. Pisa. POL. Poland. POM. Pomerania. POR. Portugal. PRO. Provence. PRU. Prussia. PSK. Pskov. PUN. Punjab. QAR. QAS. Qasim. QUE. Quebec. RAG. Ragusa. RAJ. Rajputana. REB. Rebels. RIG. Riga. RUS. Russia. RYA. Ryazan. RYU. Ryukyu. SAR. Sardinia. SAV. Savoy. SAX. Saxony. SCO. Scotland. SER. Serbia. SHA. Shawnee. SHL. Holstein. SHR. Sharjah. SHY. Uzbek. SIB. Sibir. SIC. Sicily. SIE. Siena. SIL. Silesia. SLZ. Salzburg. SND. Sind. SOF. Segu. SON. Songhai. SPA. Spain. SST. Shan. STY. Styria. SUL. Sulu. SWE. Sweden. SWI. Switzerland. TAU. Taungu. TEU. THU. Thuringia. TIB. Tibet. TIM. Timurids. TIR. Tirol. TOK. Tonkin. TOU. Toulouse. TRA. Transylvania. TRE. Trebizond. TRI. Trier. TRP. Tripoli. TRV. Travanacore. TUN. Tunis. TUR. Ottomans. TUS. Tuscany. TVE. Tver. TYR. Tyrone. UKR. Ruthenia. URB. Urbino. USA. UTR. Utrecht. WAL. Wallachia. WBG. Wurzburg. VEN. Venice. VIE. Vientiane. VIJ. Vijayanagar. WLS. Wales. WUR. Wurttemberg. YAR. Yaroslavl. YOR. Andhra. ZAP. Zapotec. ZAZ. Zaporozhie. ZIM. Mutapa. NIZ. BAS. Ahmadnagar. NAT. Natives. PIR. Pirates. Piratic. Native. Adalan. Adeni. Albanian. Algerian. Haasalese. Alsatian. Armagnac. Anhaltian. Annamese. Ansbachian. Aragonese. Arakani. Armenian. Ashanti. Assamese. Astrakhani. Athenian. Atjehan. Auvergnese. Avignonese. Ayutthayan. Aztec. Badenese. Balinese. Banteni. Baluchistani. Bavarian. Bruneian. Beninese. Bhutanese. Bijapuri. Bundelkhandi. Bengalese. Bohemian. Bosnian. Bourbonnean. Brandenburgian. Brabantian. Bremian. Breton. Berari. Brunswickian. Brazilian. Bulgarian. Burgundian. Canadian. Castilian. Catalonian. Corfuan. Champani. Cherokee. Champassaki. Chilean. Chimu. Champagnian. Candari. Colombian. Clanricarde. Corsican. Creek. Crimean. Cornish. Croatian. Cretan. Cypriot. Danish. Dauphinese. Delhian. Dulkadiri. Durrani. English. Ethiopian. Ferraranese. Fezian. Finnish. Flemish. Foixian. French. Frisian. British. Gondwanese. Gelren. Genoese. Georgian. German. Gotlander. Granadan. Greek. Gujarati. Gascon. Austrian. Hainautian. Hamburgian. Hanoverian. Hausan. Hejazi. Hessian. Dutch. Hungarian. Huron. Incan. Irish. Iroquois. Italian. Japanese. Karamanese. Kazani. Mongol. Khandeshi. Khivan. Cambodian. Clevian. Knights. Ferghanan. Colognian. Kongolese. Korean. Carnatic. Kashmiri. Kurlandian. Kazakhi. Florentine. Leinster. Liegian. Lithuanian. Loangoni. Lorrainian. Louisianan. Luneburgian. Luxembourgian. Madurain. Magdeburgian. Mainzian. Malian. Mamlukean. Mantuan. Mayan. Mazovian. Manchurian. Mexican. Mecklenburgian. Makassari. Malaccan. Milanese. Malwani. Ming. Thomondian. Modenan. Morean. Moldavian. Montenegrin. Moroccan. Muscovite. Matarami. Mughal. M&#x00FC;nster. Mysorian. Najdi. Navarran. Naxosian. Dutch. Neveriase. Nogai. Northumbrian. Norwegian. Novgorodian. Nepalese. Norman. Funj. Oudh. Oirat. Oldenburgian. Omani. Orissi. Orleanaise. Oyo. Palatine. Papal. Parman. Pattani. Pegu. Persian. Peruvian. Picardian. Pisan. Polish. Pomeranian. Portuguese. Provencal. Prussian. Pskovian. Punjabi. Qasim. Quebec. Ragusan. Rajputni. Rigan. Russian. Ryazanian. Ryukyuan. Sardinian. Savoyard. Saxon. Scottish. Serbian. Shawnee. Holsteinian. Sharjahi. Uzbek. Sibirian. Sicilian. Sienese. Silesian. Salzburgian. Sindi. Seguian. Songhain. Spanish. Shan. Styrian. Sulu. Swedish. Swiss. Taunguan. Teutonic. Thuringian. Tibetan. Timurid. Tyrolean. Tonkini. Toulousian. Transylvanian. Trebizondian. Trierian. Tripolitanian. Travanacori. Tunisian. Ottoman. Tuscan. Tverian. Tyrone. Ruthenian. Urbinese. American. Utrechtian. Wallachian. Wurzburgian. Venetian. Vientianese. Vijaynagari. Welsh. Wurttembergian. Yaroslavlian. Andhran. Zapotec. Zaporozhian. Mutapan. Ahmadnagari. AMA. Amago. ASA. Asakura. CSK. Chosokabe. DTE. Date. HJO. Hojo. HSK. Hosokawa. HTK. Hatakeyama. IKE. Ikeda. IMG. Imagawa. MAE. Maeda. MRI. Mori. ODA. Oda. OTM. Otomo. OUC. Ouchi. SBA. Shiba. SMZ. Shimazu. TKD. Takeda. TKG. Tokugawa. UES. Uesugi. YMN. Yamana. Amago. Asakura. Chosokabe. Date. Hojo. Hosokawa. Hatakeyama. Ikeda. Imagawa. Maeda. Mori. Oda. Otomo. Ouchi. Shiba. Shimazu. Takeda. Tokugawa. Uesugi. Yamana. JNP. Jaunpur. MAW. Marwar. MER. Mewar. MUL. Multan. JAN. Jangladesh. GRJ. Garjat. GWA. Gwalior. DHU. Dhundhar. KLN. Keladi. MAB. Malabar. MEW. Mewat. BST. Bastar. JSL. Jaisalmer. KAC. Kachar. KMT. Koch. KGR. Kangra. KAT. Kathiawar. KOC. Kochin. AHM. Ahmednagar. BAH. Bahmanis. NAG. Nagpur. BDA. Baroda. GOC. Golkonda. MAR. Marathas. VND. Venad. DEC. Deccan. CZH. Zhou. CSH. Shun. CXI. Xi. JOL. Jolof. Jolofian. Jaunpuri. Marwari. Mewari. Multani. Jangladeshi. Garjati. Gwaliori. Dhundhari. Keladi. Malabari. Mewati. Bastari. Jaisalmer. Kachari. Kochi. Kangri. Kathiawar. Kochi. Ahmednagari. Bahmani. Nagpuri. Barodan. Golkondan. Maratha. Venadi. Deccani. Zhou. Shun. Xi. PLC. Commonwealth. PRM. Perm. Permian. CEY. Ceylon. Ceylonese. AFG. Afghanistan. Afghan. QNG. Qing. ABE. Abenaki. APA. Apache. ASI. Assiniboine. BLA. Blackfoot. CAD. Caddo. CHI. Chickasaw. CHO. Choctaw. CHY. Cheyenne. COM. Comanche. FOX. Fox. ILL. Illiniwek. LEN. Lenape. MIK. Mikmaq. MMI. Miami. MAH. Mahican. NAH. Navajo. OJI. Ojibwe. OSA. Osage. OTT. Ottawa. PAW. Pawnee. PEQ. Pequot. PIM. Pima. POT. Potawatomi. POW. Powhatan. PUE. Pueblo. SIO. Sioux. SHO. Shoshone. SUS. Susquehannock. WCR. Cree. Abenaki. Apache. Assiniboine. Blackfoot. Caddoan. Chickasaw. Choctaw. Cheyenne. Comanche. Fox. Illiniwek. Lenape. Mikmaq. Miami. Mahican. Navajo. Ojibwe. Osage. Ottawa. Pawnee. Pequot. Piman. Potawatomi. Powhatan. Pueblo. Sioux. Shoshone. Susquehannock. Cree. ZAN. Kilwa. Kilwan. AJU. Ajuuraan. MBA. Mombasa. Mombasan. MDI. Mogadishu. Mogadishan. MLI. Malindi. Malindian. SFA. Sofala. Sofalan. EGY. Egypt. Egyptian. BUK. Bukhara. Bukharan. BGA. Baglana. Baglani. BGL. Bagelkhand. Bagelkhandi. CHD. Chanda. Chandi. CMP. GHR. Garhwal. Garhwali. HAD. Hadoti. JAJ. Habsan. Habsani. JFN. Jaffna. LDK. Ladakh. Ladakhi. MLB. Manipur. Manipuri. NGA. Nagaur. Nagauri. NGP. Jharkhand. Jharkhandi. PTA. Patiala. Patialan. RMP. Rohilkhand. Rohilla. SDY. Sadiya. Sadiyan. TPR. Tripura. Tripuran. TRT. Tirhut. Tirhuti. CIR. Circassia. Circassian. GAZ. Gazikumukh. Gazikumukhan. IME. Imereti. Imeretian. TAB. Mazandaran. Mazandarani. MYR. Yeren. MHX. Haixi. KRC. Korchin. KLK. Khalkha. DGL. Maldives. Maldivian. HMI. ZUN. Zunghar. KAS. Yarkand. KSD. Khoshuud. SYG. UTS. U-tsang. KAM. Kham. GUG. Guge. Gugi. TMB. Timbuktu. Timbuktuan. AIR. Air. MSI. Mossi. KTS. Katsina. Katsinan. KAN. Kano. FUL. Fulo. Fulani. BON. Bonoman. DAH. Dahomey. Dahomeyan. DGB. Dagbon. Dagbani. JNN. Jenn&#x00E9;. Jenn&#x00E9;an. KBU. Kaabu. KNG. Kong. NUP. Nupe. YAO. Yao. YAT. Yatenga. ZAF. Macina. ZZZ. Zazzau. Zazzauan. ARD. Ardalan. BHT. Soran. Sorani. ERE. Eretna. Eretnid. LEB. Lebanon. Lebanese. MAK. Makuria. Makurian. SHM. Shammar. Shammari. ARB. Arabia. Arabian. GRM. Germiyan. Germiyanid. MPH. LIG. Ligor. Ligori. JOH. Johor. Johori. KED. Kedah. PRK. Perak. Perakian. HSE. Hsenwi. MYA. AVA. Ava. Avan. FEO. Theodoro. Theodorian. VOL. Galicia&#x2013;Volhynia. Volhynian. KIE. Kiev. Kievian. CHR. Chernigov. Chernihiv. CHU. Chukchi. Chukchian. HOD. Khodynt. Khodyntian. CHV. Chavchuveny. Chavchuvenian. KMC. Kamchadals. Kamchadese. BRT. Buryatia. Buriat. BSH. Bashkiria. Bashkirian. TLC. Tlemcen. Tlemceni. MZB. Mzab. Mozabite. TGT. Touggourt. Touggourtian. GHD. Djerid. Djeridi. FZA. Fezzan. Fezzani. KBA. Kabylia. Kabyle. SOS. Sus. Susian. TFL. Tafilalt. Tafilalti. ARP. Arapaho. Arapahoan. CNK. Chinook. Chinookan. COC. Cocomes. XIU. Xiu. HDA. Haida. ITZ. Itza. KIC. Kiche. KIO. Kiowa. MIX. Mixtec. Mixtecan. SAL. Salish. Salishan. TAR. Tarascan. Tzintzuntzani. TLA. Tlapanec. Tlapanecan. TLX. Tlaxcala. Tlaxcalan. TOT. Totonac. WIC. Wichita. CLM. Colima. BLM. Blambangan. CRB. Cirebon. Cirebonese. DMK. Demak. Demakan. PGR. Pagarruyung. Pagarruyungan. PLB. Palembang. Palembangan. PSA. Pasai. SAK. Siak. Siakian. SUN. Sunda. Sundanese. MJZ. Jianzhou. SRV. Shirvan. Shirvani. MIN. Min. YUE. Yue. SHU. Shu. NNG. Ning. CHC. Chu. TNG. Tang. QIC. Qi. YAN. Yan. JIN. Jin. LNG. Liang. HUA. Huai. CGS. Changsheng. CAB. Carib. Cariban. LON. Le&#x00F3;n. Leonese. ICM. Ichma. Ichman. NUM. Nuremberg. Nuremberger. AUS. Australia. Australian. BTI. Semien. MTH. Meath. Meathian. ADU. Andalusia. Andalusian. MEM. Memmingen. Memminger. VER. Verden. Verdner. NSA. Nassau. RVA. Ravensburg. Ravensburger. MFA. Montferrat. Montferratian. LUC. Lucca. Luccan. LVA. Livonia. Livonian. EST. Estonia. Estonian. SMI. Sapmi. Sami. ORM. Hormuz. Hormuzi. KRL. Karelia. Karelian. JAI. Malta. Maltese. KUB. Kuba. Kuban. KLD. Kalundwe. YAK. Yaka. Yakan. KZB. Kazembe. Kazemban. KIK. Kikondja. CKW. Chokwe. Chokwan. LND. Lunda. Lundan. LUB. Luba. Luban. KSJ. Kasanje. Kasanjean. SYO. Soyo. Soyan. TYO. Tyo. Tyoan. BSG. Busoga. Busogan. BNY. Bunyoro. Bunyoroan. KRW. Karagwe. Karagwan. BUG. Buganda. Bugandan. RWA. Rwanda. Rwandan. NKO. Nkore. Nkorian. BUU. Burundi. Burundian. UBH. Buha. Buhan. MRA. Maravi. Maravian. LDU. Lundu. Lundian. TBK. Tumbuka. Tumbukan. MKU. Makua. Makuan. RZW. Butua. Butuan. MIR. Imerina. Imerinan. ANT. Antemoro. Antemorian. SKA. Sakalava. Sakalavan. MFY. Mahafaly. BTS. Betsimisaraka. Betsimisarakan. ULS. Ulster. Ulstrian. DMS. Desmond. ORD. Ormond. KID. Kildare. Kildarean. MCM. Munster. FLY. Offaly. TRY. Tyrconnell. SLN. Sligo. Sligonian. OKA. Odoyev. Odoyevan. ICE. Iceland. Icelandic. SLO. Nitra. Nitran. HSC. Gaeldom. Gaelic. ROM. Roman. DTT. Dithmarschen. Dithmarscher. GLH. BEJ. Beja. Bejan. JIM. Jimma. Jimman. WLY. Welayta. Welaytan. DAM. Damot. Damotian. HDY. Hadiya. Hadiyan. SOA. Shewa. Shewan. JJI. Janjiro. Janjiroan. ENA. Ennarea. Ennarean. ABB. Dongola. Dongolan. AKM. Akamatsu. AKT. Ando. CBA. Chiba. ISK. Isshiki. ITO. Ito. KKC. Kikuchi. KNO. Kono. OGS. Ogasawara. SHN. Shoni. STK. Satake. TKI. Toki. UTN. Utsunomiya. TTI. Tsutsui. Akamatsu. Ando. Chiba. Isshiki. Ito. Kikuchi. Kono. Ogasawara. Shoni. Satake. Toki. Utsunomiya. Tsutsui. ASK. Ashikaga. MVA. Moravia. Moravian. YUA. Yuan. BLO. Beloozero. Beloozeroan. RSO. Rostov. Rostovian. MHR. Mahra. Mahri. HDR. Hadramut. Hadramhi. MDA. Medina. Medinan. ANZ. Anizah. FAD. Fadl. Fadli. YAS. Yas. Yasi. RAS. Rassids. Rassid. YEM. Yemen. Yemeni. DAW. Dawasir. Dawasiri. MFL. Mikhlaf. Mikhlafi. NJR. Najran. Najrani. HSN. BTL. Bitlis. Bitlisi. AVR. Avaria. Avarian. MLK. Kharabakh. Kharabakhi. SME. Samtskhe. Samtskhean. ARL. Ardabil. Ardabili. MSY. Mushasha. Mushashan. RUM. R&#x00FB;m. R&#x00FB;mi. KRY. Gilan. Gilani. LRI. Luristan. Luristani. SIS. Sistan. Sistani. BPI. Biapas. Biapasi. FRS. Fars. Farsi. KRM. Kerman. Kermani. YZD. Yazd. Yazdi. ISF. Isfahan. Isfahani. TBR. Tabriz. Tabrizi. BSR. Basra. Basran. MGR. Maregheh. Mareghehi. QOM. Ajam. Ajami. TRS. Transoxiana. Transoxianian. MAS. Madyas. PGS. Pangasinan. TDO. Tondo. Tondoan. MNA. Maynila. Maynilan. CEB. Cebu. Cebuan. BTU. Butuan. KTB. Kitabatake. KOI. Mann. Manx. LOI. EFR. Hebridean.</Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Keywords3">&quot;Colonial Alaska&quot; &quot;Colonial Canada&quot; &quot;Eastern America&quot; &quot;Colonial Eastern America&quot; &quot;Colonial Louisiana&quot; &quot;Colonial California&quot; &quot;Colonial Mexico&quot; &quot;Colonial Caribbean&quot; &quot;Colonial Colombia&quot; &quot;Colonial Peru&quot; &quot;La Plata&quot; &quot;Colonial La Plata&quot; &quot;Colonial Brazil&quot; &quot;Colonial Guyana&quot; &quot;Colonial Australia&quot; &quot;Pacifico Norte&quot; &quot;Pacifico Nortean&quot; &quot;Nova Scotia&quot; &quot;Nova Scotian&quot; &quot;Nova Hollandia&quot; &quot;Nova Hollandian&quot; &quot;Hudson Bay&quot; &quot;Rupert&apos;s Land&quot; &quot;Thirteen Colonies&quot; &quot;Thirteen Colonial&quot; &quot;New Albion&quot; &quot;New Albionian&quot; &quot;New Spain&quot; &quot;New Spanish&quot; &quot;New Castile&quot; &quot;New Castilian&quot; &quot;Isla Juana&quot; &quot;Isla Juanan&quot; &quot;West Indies&quot; &quot;West Indian&quot; &quot;West Indies&quot; &quot;West Indian&quot; &quot;The Caribbean&quot; &quot;New Granada&quot; &quot;New Granadan&quot; &quot;Rio da Prata&quot; &quot;Rio da Pratan&quot; &quot;La Plata&quot; &quot;La Platan&quot; &quot;Terra de Vera Cruz&quot; &quot;Terra de Vera Cruzian&quot; &quot;Granada Al-Jadida&quot; &quot;Jadida Granadian&quot; &quot;Las Guayanas&quot; &quot;Las Guayanan&quot; &quot;Tierra Austral&quot; &quot;Tierra Australian&quot; &quot;Terre Australe&quot; &quot;Terre Australian&quot; &quot;New Holland&quot; &quot;New Hollandian&quot; &quot;Terra Australis&quot; &quot;Terra Australian&quot;&#x000D;&#x000A;&#x000D;&#x000A;&quot;Colonial Alaska.&quot; &quot;Colonial Canada.&quot; &quot;Eastern America.&quot; &quot;Colonial Eastern America.&quot; &quot;Colonial Louisiana.&quot; &quot;Colonial California.&quot; &quot;Colonial Mexico.&quot; &quot;Colonial Caribbean.&quot; &quot;Colonial Colombia.&quot; &quot;Colonial Peru.&quot; &quot;La Plata.&quot; &quot;Colonial La Plata.&quot; &quot;Colonial Brazil.&quot; &quot;Colonial Guyana.&quot; &quot;Colonial Australia.&quot; &quot;Pacifico Norte.&quot; &quot;Pacifico Nortean.&quot; &quot;Nova Scotia.&quot; &quot;Nova Scotian.&quot; &quot;Nova Hollandia.&quot; &quot;Nova Hollandian.&quot; &quot;Hudson Bay.&quot; &quot;Rupert&apos;s Land.&quot; &quot;Thirteen Colonies.&quot; &quot;Thirteen Colonial.&quot; &quot;New Albion.&quot; &quot;New Albionian.&quot; &quot;New Spain.&quot; &quot;New Spanish.&quot; &quot;New Castile.&quot; &quot;New Castilian.&quot; &quot;Isla Juana.&quot; &quot;Isla Juanan.&quot; &quot;West Indies.&quot; &quot;West Indian.&quot; &quot;West Indies.&quot; &quot;West Indian.&quot; &quot;The Caribbean.&quot; &quot;New Granada.&quot; &quot;New Granadan.&quot; &quot;Rio da Prata.&quot; &quot;Rio da Pratan.&quot; &quot;La Plata.&quot; &quot;La Platan.&quot; &quot;Terra de Vera Cruz.&quot; &quot;Terra de Vera Cruzian.&quot; &quot;Granada Al-Jadida.&quot; &quot;Jadida Granadian.&quot; &quot;Las Guayanas.&quot; &quot;Las Guayanan.&quot; &quot;Tierra Austral.&quot; &quot;Tierra Australian.&quot; &quot;Terre Australe.&quot; &quot;Terre Australian.&quot; &quot;New Holland.&quot; &quot;New Hollandian.&quot; &quot;Terra Australis.&quot; &quot;Terra Australian.&quot;</Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Keywords4">Alaska Canada Louisiana California Mexico Caribbean Colombia Peru Brazil Guyana Australia Alyeska Alyeskan Alaska Alaskan Aleutia Aleutian Canada Canadian Acadia Acadian Nouvelle-&#x00C9;cosse Nouvelle-&#x00C9;cossean Newfoundland Newfoundlandian Quebec Quebecian Laurentia Laurentian Borealia Borealian Lavrador Lavradorian Kanata Kanatan Vinland Vinlandian Canada Canadian Labrador Labradorian Nouvelle-Flandre Nouvelle-Flandrean Floride Floridean Florida Floridan Virginia Virginian Louisiana Louisianan Louisiana Louisianan Mississippi Mississippian Manitounie Manitounien Arkansas Arkansan Wisconsin Wisconsinite Nebraska Nebraskan Columbia Columbian California Californian Oregon Cascadia Cascadian Mexico Mexican Yucatan Guatemala Guatemalan Texas Texan Hispaniola Hispaniolan Antilles Antillean Cuba Cuban Caraibas Antilhas Colombia Colombian Peru Peruvian Argentine Transplatina Transplatinan Paraguay Paraguayan Chile Chilean Argentina Argentinan Brazil Brazilian Guyane Guiana Guianan Suriname Surinamese Guyana Guyanan Guyana Guyanan Australia Australian Australia Australian&#x000D;&#x000A;&#x000D;&#x000A;Alaska. Canada. Louisiana. California. Mexico. Caribbean. Colombia. Peru. Brazil. Guyana. Australia. Alyeska. Alyeskan. Alaska. Alaskan. Aleutia. Aleutian. Canada. Canadian. Acadia. Acadian. Nouvelle-&#x00C9;cosse. Nouvelle-&#x00C9;cossean. Newfoundland. Newfoundlandian. Quebec. Quebecian. Laurentia. Laurentian. Borealia. Borealian. Lavrador. Lavradorian. Kanata. Kanatan. Vinland. Vinlandian. Canada. Canadian. Labrador. Labradorian. Nouvelle-Flandre. Nouvelle-Flandrean. Floride. Floridean. Florida. Floridan. Virginia. Virginian. Louisiana. Louisianan. Louisiana. Louisianan. Mississippi. Mississippian. Manitounie. Manitounien. Arkansas. Arkansan. Wisconsin. Wisconsinite. Nebraska. Nebraskan. Columbia. Columbian. California. Californian. Oregon. Cascadia. Cascadian. Mexico. Mexican. Yucatan. Guatemala. Guatemalan. Texas. Texan. Hispaniola. Hispaniolan. Antilles. Antillean. Cuba. Cuban. Caraibas. Antilhas. Colombia. Colombian. Peru. Peruvian. Argentine. Transplatina. Transplatinan. Paraguay. Paraguayan. Chile. Chilean. Argentina. Argentinan. Brazil. Brazilian. Guyane. Guiana. Guianan. Suriname. Surinamese. Guyana. Guyanan. Guyana. Guyanan. Australia. Australian. Australia. Australian.</Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Keywords5">&quot;Stockholm&quot; &quot;&#x00D6;sterg&#x00F6;tland&quot; &quot;Kalmar&quot; &quot;Bergslagen&quot; &quot;V&#x00E4;rmland&quot; &quot;Lund&quot; &quot;Skaraborg&quot; &quot;Dalaskogen&quot; &quot;H&#x00E4;lsingland&quot; &quot;J&#x00E4;mtland&quot; &quot;V&#x00E4;sterbotten&quot; &quot;Sj&#x00E6;lland&quot; &quot;Slesvig&quot; &quot;Fyn&quot; &quot;Vestjylland&quot; &quot;Bohusl&#x00E4;n&quot; &quot;Akershus&quot; &quot;Lappland&quot; &quot;&#x00D6;sterbotten&quot; &quot;Tr&#x00F8;ndelag&quot; &quot;H&#x00E5;logaland&quot; &quot;Opplanda&quot; &quot;Bergenhus&quot; &quot;Stavanger&quot; &quot;Gotland&quot; &quot;Halland&quot; &quot;&#x00C5;bo&quot; &quot;Nyland&quot; &quot;Tavastland&quot; &quot;Viborg&quot; &quot;Savolax&quot; &quot;Kexholm&quot; &quot;Neva&quot; &quot;Ingermanland&quot; &quot;&#x00D6;sel&quot; &quot;Reval&quot; &quot;Livland&quot; &quot;Riga&quot; &quot;Goldingen&quot; &quot;Memel&quot; &quot;K&#x00F6;nigsberg&quot; &quot;Warmia&quot; &quot;Danzig&quot; &quot;Hamburg&quot; &quot;L&#x00FC;beck&quot; &quot;Rostock&quot; &quot;Stralsund&quot; &quot;Kolberg&quot; &quot;Neumark&quot; &quot;Berlin&quot; &quot;Ruppin&quot; &quot;Magdeburg&quot; &quot;L&#x00FC;neburg&quot; &quot;Stade&quot; &quot;Oldenburg&quot; &quot;Osnabr&#x00FC;ck&quot; &quot;Brunswick&quot; &quot;Anhalt&quot; &quot;Wittenberg&quot; &quot;Oberlausitz&quot; &quot;Dresden&quot; &quot;Leipzig&quot; &quot;Th&#x00FC;ringen&quot; &quot;Landshut&quot; &quot;M&#x00FC;nchen&quot; &quot;Bamberg&quot; &quot;N&#x00FC;rnberg&quot; &quot;Memmingen&quot; &quot;Oberschwaben&quot; &quot;W&#x00FC;rttemberg&quot; &quot;Ansbach&quot; &quot;Breisgau&quot; &quot;Tirol&quot; &quot;Baden&quot; &quot;Elsass&quot; &quot;Salzburg&quot; &quot;Heidelberg&quot; &quot;Mainz&quot; &quot;W&#x00FC;rzburg&quot; &quot;Trier&quot; &quot;Hessen&quot; &quot;Westfalen&quot; &quot;Nassau&quot; &quot;Berg&quot; &quot;K&#x00F6;ln&quot; &quot;M&#x00FC;nster&quot; &quot;Calais&quot; &quot;Artois&quot; &quot;Picardie&quot; &quot;Vlaanderen&quot; &quot;Hainaut&quot; &quot;Brussels&quot; &quot;Li&#x00E8;ge&quot; &quot;Luxemburg&quot; &quot;Breda&quot; &quot;Zeeland&quot; &quot;Amsterdam&quot; &quot;Utrecht&quot; &quot;Gelre&quot; &quot;Friesland&quot; &quot;Genoa&quot; &quot;Nice&quot; &quot;Piedmont&quot; &quot;Milan&quot; &quot;Parma&quot; &quot;Modena&quot; &quot;Brescia&quot; &quot;Verona&quot; &quot;Mantua&quot; &quot;Trent&quot; &quot;Friuli&quot; &quot;Venezia&quot; &quot;Ferrara&quot; &quot;Romagna&quot; &quot;Pisa&quot; &quot;Firenze&quot; &quot;Siena&quot; &quot;Roma&quot; &quot;Ancona&quot; &quot;Abruzzi&quot; &quot;Napoli&quot; &quot;Salento&quot; &quot;Calabria&quot; &quot;Messina&quot; &quot;Palermo&quot; &quot;Malta&quot; &quot;Sassari&quot; &quot;K&#x00E4;rnten&quot; &quot;Krain&quot; &quot;Istria&quot; &quot;Zagreb&quot; &quot;Steiermark&quot; &quot;Linz&quot; &quot;Wien&quot; &quot;Sopron&quot; &quot;Dalmatia&quot; &quot;Ragusa&quot; &quot;Zeta&quot; &quot;Hum&quot; &quot;Bosnia&quot; &quot;Smederevo&quot; &quot;Corfu&quot; &quot;Vlor&#x00EB;&quot; &quot;Epirus&quot; &quot;Morea&quot; &quot;Athens&quot; &quot;Thessaly&quot; &quot;Macedonia&quot; &quot;Edirne&quot; &quot;Tarnovo&quot; &quot;Constantinople&quot; &quot;Varasd&quot; &quot;Pest&quot; &quot;Hont&quot; &quot;B&#x00E9;k&#x00E9;s&quot; &quot;Temes&quot; &quot;Bihar&quot; &quot;Maros&quot; &quot;Silistria&quot; &quot;Oltenia&quot; &quot;T&#x00EE;rgoviste&quot; &quot;Zempl&#x00E9;n&quot; &quot;Crete&quot; &quot;Naxos&quot; &quot;Bern&quot; &quot;Waldst&#x00E4;tte&quot; &quot;Caux&quot; &quot;Caen&quot; &quot;Armor&quot; &quot;Finist&#x00E8;re&quot; &quot;Vannetais&quot; &quot;Nantais&quot; &quot;Labourd&quot; &quot;Aquitaine&quot; &quot;Armagnac&quot; &quot;B&#x00E9;arn&quot; &quot;Maine&quot; &quot;Anjou&quot; &quot;Berry&quot; &quot;Haut-Poitou&quot; &quot;Rethel&quot; &quot;Valois&quot; &quot;Paris&quot; &quot;Orleanais&quot; &quot;Nemours&quot; &quot;Reims&quot; &quot;Barrois&quot; &quot;Metz&quot; &quot;Lothringen&quot; &quot;Bourbonnais&quot; &quot;Nivernais&quot; &quot;Dijonnais&quot; &quot;Franche-Comt&#x00E9;&quot; &quot;P&#x00E9;rigord&quot; &quot;Limousin&quot; &quot;Toulouse&quot; &quot;Roussillon&quot; &quot;Rouergue&quot; &quot;Auvergne&quot; &quot;Montpellier&quot; &quot;Provence&quot; &quot;Avignon&quot; &quot;Lyonnais&quot; &quot;Dauphin&#x00E9;&quot; &quot;Savoie&quot; &quot;Galicia&quot; &quot;Asturias&quot; &quot;Le&#x00F3;n&quot; &quot;Vizcaya&quot; &quot;Navarra&quot; &quot;Pirineo&quot; &quot;Girona&quot; &quot;Barcelona&quot; &quot;Zaragoza&quot; &quot;Castilla La Vieja&quot; &quot;Salamanca&quot; &quot;Madrid&quot; &quot;Badajoz&quot; &quot;Toledo&quot; &quot;Val&#x00E8;ncia&quot; &quot;Murcia&quot; &quot;Almer&#x00ED;a&quot; &quot;Granada&quot; &quot;Sevilla&quot; &quot;C&#x00F3;rdoba&quot; &quot;Gibraltar&quot; &quot;Lisboa&quot; &quot;Beira&quot; &quot;Beja&quot; &quot;Algarve&quot; &quot;Porto&quot; &quot;Bragan&#x00E7;a&quot; &quot;Cornwall&quot; &quot;Hampshire&quot; &quot;Kent&quot; &quot;London&quot; &quot;Oxford&quot; &quot;Essex&quot; &quot;Gloucester&quot; &quot;Shrewsbury&quot; &quot;Glamorgan&quot; &quot;Gwynedd&quot; &quot;Lincolnshire&quot; &quot;Lancashire&quot; &quot;York&quot; &quot;Northumberland&quot; &quot;Cumbria&quot; &quot;Lothian&quot; &quot;Ayrshire&quot; &quot;Perth&quot; &quot;Aberdeen&quot; &quot;Inverness&quot; &quot;Outer Hebrides&quot; &quot;Poznan&quot; &quot;Kalisz&quot; &quot;Plock&quot; &quot;Warszawa&quot; &quot;Sieradz&quot; &quot;Sandomierz&quot; &quot;Lublin&quot; &quot;Halicz&quot; &quot;Krakow&quot; &quot;Ratibor&quot; &quot;Breslau&quot; &quot;Brno&quot; &quot;Prague&quot; &quot;Plzen&quot; &quot;Moldavia&quot; &quot;Podlasie&quot; &quot;Trakai&quot; &quot;Samogitia&quot; &quot;Vilna&quot; &quot;Latgalia&quot; &quot;Pskov&quot; &quot;Polotsk&quot; &quot;Minsk&quot; &quot;Brest&quot; &quot;Pinsk&quot; &quot;Volhynia&quot; &quot;Kiev&quot; &quot;Podolia&quot; &quot;Yedisan&quot; &quot;Zaporozhia&quot; &quot;Crimea&quot; &quot;Caffa&quot; &quot;Azov&quot; &quot;Kuban&quot; &quot;Lower Don&quot; &quot;Chernigov&quot; &quot;Poltava&quot; &quot;Kharkov&quot; &quot;Mogilev&quot; &quot;Smolensk&quot; &quot;Tver&quot; &quot;Moskva&quot; &quot;Kaluga&quot; &quot;Bryansk&quot; &quot;Kursk&quot; &quot;Voronezh&quot; &quot;Tula&quot; &quot;Ryazan&quot; &quot;Tambov&quot; &quot;Saratov&quot; &quot;Penza&quot; &quot;Perm&quot; &quot;Nizhny Novgorod&quot; &quot;Vladimir&quot; &quot;Yaroslavl&quot; &quot;Olonets&quot; &quot;Novgorod&quot; &quot;Kholm&quot; &quot;Beloozero&quot; &quot;Soroka&quot; &quot;Vologda&quot; &quot;Finnmark&quot; &quot;Kocaeli&quot; &quot;H&#x00FC;davendigar&quot; &quot;Sugla&quot; &quot;Mentese&quot; &quot;Rhodes&quot; &quot;Cyprus&quot; &quot;K&#x00FC;tahya&quot; &quot;Konya&quot; &quot;Karaman&quot; &quot;Kastamonu&quot; &quot;Ankara&quot; &quot;Adana&quot; &quot;Sinop&quot; &quot;Sivas&quot; &quot;Trebizond&quot; &quot;Erzurum&quot; &quot;Marash&quot; &quot;The Baleares&quot; &quot;Tangiers&quot; &quot;Melilla&quot; &quot;Tlemcen&quot; &quot;Oran&quot; &quot;Mitidja&quot; &quot;Kabylia&quot; &quot;Constantine&quot; &quot;Tunis&quot; &quot;Gharb&quot; &quot;Fez&quot; &quot;Marrakech&quot; &quot;Abda&quot; &quot;Tafilalt&quot; &quot;Ifni&quot; &quot;Sus&quot; &quot;Figuig&quot; &quot;Laghouat&quot; &quot;Biskra&quot; &quot;Gafsa&quot; &quot;Tataouine&quot; &quot;Tripoli&quot; &quot;Sirt&quot; &quot;Benghazi&quot; &quot;Darnah&quot; &quot;Alexandria&quot; &quot;Fayyum&quot; &quot;Qus&quot; &quot;Cairo&quot; &quot;Rosetta&quot; &quot;Damietta&quot; &quot;Gaza&quot; &quot;Sinai&quot; &quot;The Canarias&quot; &quot;The Azores&quot; &quot;Madeira&quot; &quot;Orkney&quot; &quot;Reykjavik&quot; &quot;Akureyri&quot; &quot;Tyrone&quot; &quot;Pale&quot; &quot;Leinster&quot; &quot;Limerick&quot; &quot;Connaught&quot; &quot;Aleppo&quot; &quot;Tarabulus&quot; &quot;Jerusalem&quot; &quot;Al Karak&quot; &quot;Ajlun&quot; &quot;Damascus&quot; &quot;Tabuk&quot; &quot;Medina&quot; &quot;Mecca&quot; &quot;Bishah&quot; &quot;Mokha&quot; &quot;Aden&quot; &quot;Mukalla&quot; &quot;Sana\&apos;a&quot; &quot;Najran&quot; &quot;Al-Arid&quot; &quot;Jabal Shammar&quot; &quot;Al-Qatif&quot; &quot;Qatar&quot; &quot;Bahrain&quot; &quot;Bani Yas&quot; &quot;Qawasim&quot; &quot;Batinah&quot; &quot;Muscat&quot; &quot;Dhofar&quot; &quot;Qishn&quot; &quot;Nizwa&quot; &quot;Liwa&quot; &quot;Tadmor&quot; &quot;Haditha&quot; &quot;Ar Raqqa&quot; &quot;Basra&quot; &quot;Karbala&quot; &quot;Baghdad&quot; &quot;Mosul&quot; &quot;Ahvaz&quot; &quot;Khorramabad&quot; &quot;Hamadan&quot; &quot;Kirkuk&quot; &quot;Tabriz&quot; &quot;Lahijan&quot; &quot;Diyarbakir&quot; &quot;Yerevan&quot; &quot;Ganja&quot; &quot;Shirvan&quot; &quot;Imereti&quot; &quot;Tbilisi&quot; &quot;Ardabil&quot; &quot;Dagestan&quot; &quot;Amol&quot; &quot;Qumis&quot; &quot;Teheran&quot; &quot;Isfahan&quot; &quot;Dashtistan&quot; &quot;Mogostan&quot; &quot;Kerman&quot; &quot;Yazd&quot; &quot;Quhistan&quot; &quot;Zaranj&quot; &quot;Birjand&quot; &quot;Kopet Dag&quot; &quot;Karakum&quot; &quot;Mangyshlak&quot; &quot;Qaraqalpak&quot; &quot;Khiva&quot; &quot;Bukhara&quot; &quot;Ustyurt&quot; &quot;Charjuy&quot; &quot;Merv&quot; &quot;Herat&quot; &quot;Kandahar&quot; &quot;Gazni&quot; &quot;Ghor&quot; &quot;Balkh&quot; &quot;Kabul&quot; &quot;Badakhshan&quot; &quot;Qarshi&quot; &quot;Samarkand&quot; &quot;Kyzylkum&quot; &quot;Turkestan&quot; &quot;Tashkent&quot; &quot;Kokand&quot; &quot;Taraz&quot; &quot;Uzkend&quot; &quot;Almaty&quot; &quot;Odishi&quot; &quot;Circassia&quot; &quot;Astrakhan&quot; &quot;Nogay&quot; &quot;Sarai&quot; &quot;Borisoglebsk&quot; &quot;Manych&quot; &quot;Ryn&quot; &quot;Bayuly&quot; &quot;Alimuly&quot; &quot;Zhetyru&quot; &quot;Samara&quot; &quot;Yaik&quot; &quot;Bashkortostan&quot; &quot;Kypshak&quot; &quot;Nadym&quot; &quot;Argyn&quot; &quot;Kerey&quot; &quot;Pegaya Orda&quot; &quot;Bermuda&quot; &quot;Bahamas&quot; &quot;Turks Islands&quot; &quot;Havana&quot; &quot;Moron&quot; &quot;Guantanamo&quot; &quot;Jamaica&quot; &quot;Les Cayes&quot; &quot;Tortuga&quot; &quot;Barahonas&quot; &quot;Curacao&quot; &quot;Borik&#x00E9;n&quot; &quot;St. Thomas&quot; &quot;St. Kitts&quot; &quot;Antigua&quot; &quot;Guadelupe&quot; &quot;Dominica&quot; &quot;Martinique&quot; &quot;St. Lucia&quot; &quot;St. Vincent&quot; &quot;Barbados&quot; &quot;Trinidad&quot; &quot;Kutch&quot; &quot;Thatta&quot; &quot;Sehwan&quot; &quot;Multan&quot; &quot;Lahore&quot; &quot;Kashmir&quot; &quot;Kangra&quot; &quot;Sirhind&quot; &quot;Garhwal&quot; &quot;Jangladesh&quot; &quot;Jaisalmer&quot; &quot;Marwar&quot; &quot;Girnar&quot; &quot;Baroda&quot; &quot;Surat&quot; &quot;Chittor&quot; &quot;Dhundar&quot; &quot;Mewat&quot; &quot;Kathiawar&quot; &quot;Delhi&quot; &quot;Lucknow&quot; &quot;Central Doab&quot; &quot;Gird&quot; &quot;Mandu&quot; &quot;Khandesh&quot; &quot;Hadoti&quot; &quot;North Konkan&quot; &quot;South Konkan&quot; &quot;North Kanara&quot; &quot;Raichur Doab&quot; &quot;Mysore&quot; &quot;Malabar&quot; &quot;Kochin&quot; &quot;Madurai&quot; &quot;Venad&quot; &quot;Kongu&quot; &quot;Tondainadu&quot; &quot;Coromandel&quot; &quot;Vijayanagar&quot; &quot;Golconda&quot; &quot;Velanadu&quot; &quot;Ahmadnagar&quot; &quot;Marathwada&quot; &quot;East Berar&quot; &quot;Bastar&quot; &quot;West Berar&quot; &quot;Kalingandhra&quot; &quot;Mahakoshal&quot; &quot;Mandla&quot; &quot;Cuttack&quot; &quot;Sambalpur&quot; &quot;Baisi Rajya&quot; &quot;Jaunpur&quot; &quot;Lower Doab&quot; &quot;Katmandu&quot; &quot;Patna&quot; &quot;Bundelkhand&quot; &quot;Jharkhand&quot; &quot;Bengal Delta&quot; &quot;Koch&quot; &quot;Gauda&quot; &quot;Dhaka&quot; &quot;Bhutan&quot; &quot;Assam&quot; &quot;Silhet&quot; &quot;Chittagong&quot; &quot;Bijapur&quot; &quot;Naga&quot; &quot;Darrang&quot; &quot;Kotte&quot; &quot;Cachar&quot; &quot;The Andamans&quot; &quot;Gwadar&quot; &quot;Kalat&quot; &quot;Quetta&quot; &quot;Roh&quot; &quot;Mrauk U&quot; &quot;Kale&quot; &quot;Sagaing&quot; &quot;Mong Yang&quot; &quot;Hsenwi&quot; &quot;Ava&quot; &quot;Taungoo&quot; &quot;Pegu&quot; &quot;Kengtung&quot; &quot;Mong Nai&quot; &quot;Chiang Mai&quot; &quot;Moulmein&quot; &quot;Tavoy&quot; &quot;Ratchaburi&quot; &quot;Nakhon Si Thammarat&quot; &quot;Pattani&quot; &quot;Perak&quot; &quot;Malacca&quot; &quot;Johor&quot; &quot;Pahang&quot; &quot;Kelantan&quot; &quot;Ayutthaya&quot; &quot;Sukhothai&quot; &quot;Chiang Rai&quot; &quot;Nakhon Thung Yai&quot; &quot;Oudong&quot; &quot;Prey Nokor&quot; &quot;Panduranga&quot; &quot;Vijaya&quot; &quot;Champasak&quot; &quot;Angkor&quot; &quot;Thanh Hoa&quot; &quot;Sikhottabong&quot; &quot;Khorat&quot; &quot;Dong Kinh&quot; &quot;Vientiane&quot; &quot;Luang Prabang&quot; &quot;Cao Bang&quot; &quot;Lamuri&quot; &quot;Deli&quot; &quot;Batak&quot; &quot;Siak&quot; &quot;Bengkulu&quot; &quot;Palembang&quot; &quot;Tulangbewang&quot; &quot;Banten&quot; &quot;Kawali&quot; &quot;Karta&quot; &quot;Blambangan&quot; &quot;Surabaya&quot; &quot;Demak&quot; &quot;Kalapa&quot; &quot;Bali&quot; &quot;Sumbawa&quot; &quot;Flores&quot; &quot;Sumba&quot; &quot;West Timor&quot; &quot;Brunei&quot; &quot;Jesselton&quot; &quot;Kutai&quot; &quot;Banjar&quot; &quot;Pontianak&quot; &quot;Makassar&quot; &quot;Kendari&quot; &quot;Poso&quot; &quot;Manado&quot; &quot;Buru&quot; &quot;Ambon&quot; &quot;Ceram&quot; &quot;Halmahera&quot; &quot;Ternate&quot; &quot;Tidore&quot; &quot;Sulu&quot; &quot;Maguindanao&quot; &quot;Lanao&quot; &quot;Samar&quot; &quot;Palawan&quot; &quot;Manila&quot; &quot;Ilocos&quot; &quot;Cagayan&quot; &quot;Lingga&quot; &quot;Sibsongbanna&quot; &quot;Dali&quot; &quot;Yunnan&quot; &quot;Guangnan&quot; &quot;Lingyun&quot; &quot;Shiuhing&quot; &quot;Kingchow&quot; &quot;Canton&quot; &quot;Macau&quot; &quot;Fuzhou&quot; &quot;Ganzhou&quot; &quot;Changsha&quot; &quot;Wuling&quot; &quot;Zhenyuan&quot; &quot;Guiyang&quot; &quot;Umung&quot; &quot;Shigatse&quot; &quot;Lhasa&quot; &quot;Tachienlu&quot; &quot;Chengdu&quot; &quot;Chongqing&quot; &quot;Yichang&quot; &quot;Wuchang&quot; &quot;Nanchang&quot; &quot;Hangzhou&quot; &quot;Yangzhou&quot; &quot;Anqing&quot; &quot;Nanyang&quot; &quot;Kaifeng&quot; &quot;Hanzhong&quot; &quot;Qingzhou&quot; &quot;Jinan&quot; &quot;Huaiqing&quot; &quot;Taiyuan&quot; &quot;Pingyang&quot; &quot;Hejian&quot; &quot;Baoding&quot; &quot;Datong&quot; &quot;Ningxia&quot; &quot;Lanzhou&quot; &quot;Xi\&apos;an&quot; &quot;Ordos&quot; &quot;Hohhot&quot; &quot;Chengde&quot; &quot;Ningyuan&quot; &quot;Gyegu&quot; &quot;Tsaidam&quot; &quot;Yumen&quot; &quot;Zhangye&quot; &quot;Alxa&quot; &quot;Hotan&quot; &quot;Qarqan&quot; &quot;Aksu&quot; &quot;Bechbaliq&quot; &quot;Hoboksar&quot; &quot;Urumqi&quot; &quot;Tannu Uriankhai&quot; &quot;Kherlen&quot; &quot;Kobdo&quot; &quot;Uliastai&quot; &quot;Dornogovi&quot; &quot;Setsen&quot; &quot;Jirem&quot; &quot;Xilin Gol&quot; &quot;Hulunbuir&quot; &quot;Cicigar&quot; &quot;Shenyang&quot; &quot;Aigun&quot; &quot;Tuwan&quot; &quot;Bohori&quot; &quot;Girin&quot; &quot;Ilan Hala&quot; &quot;Hamheung&quot; &quot;Hwangju&quot; &quot;Wonju&quot; &quot;Hanseong&quot; &quot;Sangju&quot; &quot;Jeonju&quot; &quot;Sakam&quot; &quot;Kashgar&quot; &quot;Chanderi&quot; &quot;Cumana&quot; &quot;Angostura&quot; &quot;Essequibo&quot; &quot;Demerara&quot; &quot;Paramaribo&quot; &quot;Cayenne&quot; &quot;Amapa&quot; &quot;Belem&quot; &quot;Maranhao&quot; &quot;Crato&quot; &quot;Ceara&quot; &quot;Oeiras&quot; &quot;Rio Grande&quot; &quot;Paraiba&quot; &quot;Pernambuco&quot; &quot;Bahia&quot; &quot;Ilheus&quot; &quot;Goias&quot; &quot;Diamantina&quot; &quot;Porto Seguro&quot; &quot;Espirito Santo&quot; &quot;Sao Tome&quot; &quot;Rio de Janeiro&quot; &quot;Santo Amaro&quot; &quot;Minas Gerais&quot; &quot;Sao Vicente&quot; &quot;Ortelsburg&quot; &quot;Guayra&quot; &quot;Curitiba&quot; &quot;Braslaw&quot; &quot;Vitebsk&quot; &quot;Uruguay&quot; &quot;Banda Oriental&quot; &quot;Al-Junaynah&quot; &quot;Asuncion&quot; &quot;Concepcion&quot; &quot;Corrientes&quot; &quot;Rio de la Plata&quot; &quot;Tandil&quot; &quot;Candelaria&quot; &quot;Puerto Deseado&quot; &quot;Tierra del Fuego&quot; &quot;Kawesqar&quot; &quot;Huillimapu&quot; &quot;Pehuenmapu&quot; &quot;Carmen&quot; &quot;Picunmapu&quot; &quot;Angoche&quot; &quot;Mtetwa&quot; &quot;Chaco Austral&quot; &quot;Catamarca&quot; &quot;Copiapo&quot; &quot;Iquique&quot; &quot;Jujuy&quot; &quot;Potosi&quot; &quot;Arica&quot; &quot;Oruro&quot; &quot;Mbwila&quot; &quot;Chaco Boreal&quot; &quot;Chiquitos&quot; &quot;Cochabamba&quot; &quot;Chuquiabo&quot; &quot;Moxos&quot; &quot;Puno&quot; &quot;Arequipa&quot; &quot;Nazca&quot; &quot;Abancay&quot; &quot;Cuzco&quot; &quot;Lima&quot; &quot;Huancavelica&quot; &quot;Jauja&quot; &quot;Chanchan&quot; &quot;Cajamarca&quot; &quot;Huanuco&quot; &quot;Iquitos&quot; &quot;Tumbes&quot; &quot;Canari&quot; &quot;Canelos&quot; &quot;Guayaquil&quot; &quot;Quito&quot; &quot;Quijos&quot; &quot;Caqueta&quot; &quot;Cauca&quot; &quot;Mariquita&quot; &quot;Bogota&quot; &quot;Choco&quot; &quot;Antioqu&#x00ED;a&quot; &quot;Cartagena&quot; &quot;Magdalena&quot; &quot;Maracaibo&quot; &quot;Caracas&quot; &quot;Tunja&quot; &quot;Graaff-Reinet&quot; &quot;Barinas&quot; &quot;Panama&quot; &quot;Chorotega&quot; &quot;Nicaragua&quot; &quot;Mosquito&quot; &quot;Pipil&quot; &quot;Honduras&quot; &quot;Guatemala&quot; &quot;Pet&#x00E9;n&quot; &quot;Belize&quot; &quot;Zapotec&quot; &quot;Campeche&quot; &quot;Sotuta&quot; &quot;Mixtec&quot; &quot;Tohancapan&quot; &quot;Tlapanec&quot; &quot;Tlaxcala&quot; &quot;Zacatula&quot; &quot;Mexico&quot; &quot;Huastec&quot; &quot;Sayultecas&quot; &quot;Totorames&quot; &quot;Zacatecas&quot; &quot;Guachichil&quot; &quot;Tamaulipas&quot; &quot;Sinaloa&quot; &quot;Tepehuan&quot; &quot;Coahuila&quot; &quot;Yaqui&quot; &quot;Suma&quot; &quot;Concho&quot; &quot;Cochimi&quot; &quot;Guaycura&quot; &quot;Cahuilla&quot; &quot;Chumash&quot; &quot;Salinan&quot; &quot;Yokuts&quot; &quot;Pomo&quot; &quot;Siuslaw&quot; &quot;Chinook&quot; &quot;Salish&quot; &quot;Paiute&quot; &quot;Yavapai&quot; &quot;Pima&quot; &quot;Navajo&quot; &quot;Apache&quot; &quot;Pueblo&quot; &quot;Piro&quot; &quot;Mescalero&quot; &quot;Lipan&quot; &quot;Karankawa&quot; &quot;Teyas&quot; &quot;Waco&quot; &quot;Tonkawa&quot; &quot;Atakapa&quot; &quot;Arapaho&quot; &quot;Kiowa&quot; &quot;Naisha&quot; &quot;Wichita&quot; &quot;Chitimacha&quot; &quot;Caddo&quot; &quot;Arkansas&quot; &quot;Yscani&quot; &quot;Quapaw&quot; &quot;Kansas&quot; &quot;Pahatsi&quot; &quot;Tamaroa&quot; &quot;Pawnee&quot; &quot;Missouri&quot; &quot;Omaha&quot; &quot;Wahpeton&quot; &quot;Iowa&quot; &quot;Yanktonai&quot; &quot;Yankton&quot; &quot;Sisseton&quot; &quot;Mandan&quot; &quot;Makoua&quot; &quot;Menominee&quot; &quot;Sauk&quot; &quot;Mesquakie&quot; &quot;Winnebago&quot; &quot;Illinois&quot; &quot;Kaskaskia&quot; &quot;Cahokia&quot; &quot;Tennessee&quot; &quot;Chickasaw&quot; &quot;Choctaw&quot; &quot;Bayougoula&quot; &quot;Mobile&quot; &quot;Pensacola&quot; &quot;Alabama&quot; &quot;Tuskegee&quot; &quot;Ais&quot; &quot;Timucua&quot; &quot;Apalachee&quot; &quot;Guale&quot; &quot;Muskogee&quot; &quot;Coosa&quot; &quot;Santee&quot; &quot;Catawba&quot; &quot;Yuchi&quot; &quot;Cherokee&quot; &quot;Cheraw&quot; &quot;Tuscarora&quot; &quot;Pamlico&quot; &quot;Kaskinampo&quot; &quot;Kentucky&quot; &quot;Chisca&quot; &quot;Wea&quot; &quot;Miami&quot; &quot;Potawatomi&quot; &quot;Michigan&quot; &quot;Wyandot&quot; &quot;Erie&quot; &quot;Ohio&quot; &quot;Monacan&quot; &quot;Chesapeake&quot; &quot;Kanawha&quot; &quot;Powhatan&quot; &quot;Conoy&quot; &quot;Allegheny&quot; &quot;Susquehanna&quot; &quot;Lenape&quot; &quot;Delaware&quot; &quot;Seneca&quot; &quot;Cayuga&quot; &quot;Onondaga&quot; &quot;Oneida&quot; &quot;Unami&quot; &quot;Mahican&quot; &quot;Mohawk&quot; &quot;Manhattan&quot; &quot;Nipmuc&quot; &quot;Narraganset&quot; &quot;Massachusetts&quot; &quot;Pocumtuk&quot; &quot;Merrimack&quot; &quot;Penobscott&quot; &quot;Nootka&quot; &quot;Squamish&quot; &quot;Kwakiutl&quot; &quot;Tsimshian&quot; &quot;Tlingit&quot; &quot;Yakutat&quot; &quot;Kenai&quot; &quot;Aleut&quot; &quot;Beothuk&quot; &quot;Taqamkuk&quot; &quot;Unamakik&quot; &quot;Epekwitk&quot; &quot;Sipeknekatik&quot; &quot;Mikmaq&quot; &quot;Kespek&quot; &quot;Niagara&quot; &quot;Huron&quot; &quot;Ontario&quot; &quot;Maisouna&quot; &quot;Nipissing&quot; &quot;Algonquin&quot; &quot;Hochelaga&quot; &quot;Stadacona&quot; &quot;Tadoussac&quot; &quot;Innu&quot; &quot;Chisedec&quot; &quot;Qikirmiut&quot; &quot;Cisasipi&quot; &quot;Cree&quot; &quot;Soto&quot; &quot;Abitibi&quot; &quot;Mosoni&quot; &quot;Attawapiskat&quot; &quot;Muskegon&quot; &quot;Chipewyan&quot; &quot;Ojibwa&quot; &quot;Winnipeg&quot; &quot;Atikaki&quot; &quot;Manitoba&quot; &quot;Kinougeoulini&quot; &quot;Satsuma&quot; &quot;Cheongju&quot; &quot;Bungo&quot; &quot;Okinawa&quot; &quot;Ha Tinh&quot; &quot;Suo&quot; &quot;Izumo&quot; &quot;Harima&quot; &quot;Kyoto&quot; &quot;Settsu&quot; &quot;Indrapura&quot; &quot;Echizen&quot; &quot;Echigo&quot; &quot;Uzen&quot; &quot;Rikuzen&quot; &quot;Hitachi&quot; &quot;Musashi&quot; &quot;Kai&quot; &quot;Owari&quot; &quot;Kamikawa&quot; &quot;The Kurils&quot; &quot;Sakhalin&quot; &quot;Kamchatka&quot; &quot;Penzhina&quot; &quot;Kolyma&quot; &quot;Omolon&quot; &quot;Karalveyem&quot; &quot;Verkhoyansk&quot; &quot;Suntar Khayata&quot; &quot;Gizhiga&quot; &quot;Sakha&quot; &quot;Okhotsk&quot; &quot;Tauisk&quot; &quot;Yakut&quot; &quot;Maya&quot; &quot;Jugjur&quot; &quot;Miyoo Gasan&quot; &quot;Haiilanboo&quot; &quot;Deren&quot; &quot;Aldan&quot; &quot;Stanovoy&quot; &quot;Hinggan&quot; &quot;Mukhtuya&quot; &quot;Kirenga&quot; &quot;Barguzin&quot; &quot;Ude&quot; &quot;Onan Gol&quot; &quot;East Tunguska&quot; &quot;Irkutsk&quot; &quot;West Tunguska&quot; &quot;Angara&quot; &quot;Sayan&quot; &quot;Tomsk&quot; &quot;Kuznetsk&quot; &quot;Altai Uriankhai&quot; &quot;Turukhan&quot; &quot;Ket&quot; &quot;Surgut&quot; &quot;Narim&quot; &quot;Irtesh&quot; &quot;Obdorsk&quot; &quot;Berezov&quot; &quot;Sibir&quot; &quot;Tyumen&quot; &quot;Kurgan&quot; &quot;Solikamsk&quot; &quot;Tura&quot; &quot;Viatka&quot; &quot;Pelym&quot; &quot;Simbirsk&quot; &quot;Kazan&quot; &quot;Vetluga&quot; &quot;Wadjuk&quot; &quot;Paredarerme&quot; &quot;Kaurna&quot; &quot;Wurundjeri&quot; &quot;Wergaia&quot; &quot;Wiradjuri&quot; &quot;Eora&quot; &quot;Kamilaroi&quot; &quot;Bundjalung&quot; &quot;Barunggam&quot; &quot;Turrbal&quot; &quot;Falklands&quot; &quot;Cape Verde&quot; &quot;Fernando Po&quot; &quot;St. Helena&quot; &quot;Socotra&quot; &quot;Mahe&quot; &quot;Hollhavai&quot; &quot;Mauritius&quot; &quot;&#x00CE;le Bourbon&quot; &quot;Eiriksfjord&quot; &quot;Vestbygden&quot; &quot;Whangarei&quot; &quot;Taranaki&quot; &quot;Tauranga&quot; &quot;Timaru&quot; &quot;Agadir&quot; &quot;Arguin&quot; &quot;Trarza&quot; &quot;Cayor&quot; &quot;Gabu&quot; &quot;Brakna&quot; &quot;Wolof&quot; &quot;Futa Jallon&quot; &quot;Sierra Leone&quot; &quot;Grain Coast&quot; &quot;Bambuk&quot; &quot;Bure&quot; &quot;Bagoe&quot; &quot;Segu&quot; &quot;Joma&quot; &quot;Kong&quot; &quot;Ivory Coast&quot; &quot;Tuat&quot; &quot;Taudeni&quot; &quot;Azawad&quot; &quot;Tadmekka&quot; &quot;Massina&quot; &quot;Timbuktu&quot; &quot;Gao&quot; &quot;Jenne&quot; &quot;Yatenga&quot; &quot;Gurma&quot; &quot;Wagadugu&quot; &quot;Kumasi&quot; &quot;Gold Coast&quot; &quot;Abomey&quot; &quot;Whydah&quot; &quot;Dendi&quot; &quot;Borgu&quot; &quot;Oyo&quot; &quot;Nupe&quot; &quot;Ife&quot; &quot;Benin&quot; &quot;Gobir&quot; &quot;Katsina&quot; &quot;Zamfara&quot; &quot;Bonny&quot; &quot;Idah&quot; &quot;Pindinga&quot; &quot;Zazzau&quot; &quot;Kano&quot; &quot;Damagaram&quot; &quot;Borno&quot; &quot;Kanem&quot; &quot;Bagirmi&quot; &quot;Mandara&quot; &quot;Bauchi&quot; &quot;Wukari&quot; &quot;Calabar&quot; &quot;Cameroon&quot; &quot;Gabon&quot; &quot;Loango&quot; &quot;Luanda&quot; &quot;Mbamba&quot; &quot;Anziku&quot; &quot;Mpemba&quot; &quot;Ndongo&quot; &quot;Benguela&quot; &quot;Namibia&quot; &quot;Ezorongondo&quot; &quot;Lesser Namaqualand&quot; &quot;Roggeveld&quot; &quot;Cape&quot; &quot;Great Karoo&quot; &quot;Swellendam&quot; &quot;Xhosa&quot; &quot;Natal&quot; &quot;Matsolo&quot; &quot;Inhambane&quot; &quot;Zimbabwe&quot; &quot;Butua&quot; &quot;Sofala&quot; &quot;Sena&quot; &quot;Massapa&quot; &quot;Shangwe&quot; &quot;Zumbo&quot; &quot;Tete&quot; &quot;Quelimane&quot; &quot;Menabe&quot; &quot;Besalampy&quot; &quot;Mozambique&quot; &quot;Kilwa&quot; &quot;Mzizima&quot; &quot;Lindi&quot; &quot;Bagamoyo&quot; &quot;Tanga&quot; &quot;Zanzibar&quot; &quot;Mombasa&quot; &quot;Malindi&quot; &quot;Lamu&quot; &quot;Mogadishu&quot; &quot;Qardho&quot; &quot;Ogaden&quot; &quot;Degehabur&quot; &quot;Berbera&quot; &quot;Dawaro&quot; &quot;Harer&quot; &quot;Zeila&quot; &quot;Shewa&quot; &quot;Wollo&quot; &quot;Tajura&quot; &quot;Tegali&quot; &quot;Fazughli&quot; &quot;Sidamo&quot; &quot;Darfur&quot; &quot;Bayuda&quot; &quot;El Obeid&quot; &quot;Gezira&quot; &quot;Gojjam&quot; &quot;Gonder&quot; &quot;Butana&quot; &quot;Beja&quot; &quot;Aksum&quot; &quot;Dongola&quot; &quot;Berber&quot; &quot;Massawa&quot; &quot;Aswan&quot; &quot;Suakin&quot; &quot;Kharga&quot; &quot;Qasr Ibrim&quot; &quot;Guam&quot; &quot;Rabaul&quot; &quot;Hanuabada&quot; &quot;Solomon Islands&quot; &quot;Vanuatu&quot; &quot;Hawaii&quot; &quot;Kiribati&quot; &quot;Fiji&quot; &quot;Samoa&quot; &quot;Tuamotu Islands&quot; &quot;Manokwari&quot; &quot;Waihopai&quot; &quot;Corsica&quot; &quot;Maldives&quot; &quot;Yola&quot; &quot;V&#x00E4;nern&quot; &quot;V&#x00E4;ttern&quot; &quot;Gulf of Bothnia&quot; &quot;Eastern Sea of &#x00C5;land&quot; &quot;Gulf of Finland&quot; &quot;Western Baltic Sea&quot; &quot;Gulf of Riga&quot; &quot;Southern Baltic Sea&quot; &quot;&#x00D6;resund&quot; &quot;Kattegat&quot; &quot;Lake Peipus&quot; &quot;Ladoga&quot; &quot;Onega&quot; &quot;Barents Sea&quot; &quot;Lofoten Sea&quot; &quot;Northern Norwegian Sea&quot; &quot;Southern Norwegian Sea&quot; &quot;Skagerrak&quot; &quot;Helgoland Bight&quot; &quot;Coast of Holland&quot; &quot;Dogger Bank&quot; &quot;Straits of Dover&quot; &quot;The Channel&quot; &quot;Taveta&quot; &quot;Coast of Brittany&quot; &quot;Quiberon Bay&quot; &quot;Cote D\&apos;Argent&quot; &quot;Bay of Biscay&quot; &quot;Cantabrian Sea&quot; &quot;Tyne&quot; &quot;Firth of Forth&quot; &quot;Coast of Shetland&quot; &quot;Moray Firth&quot; &quot;North Channel&quot; &quot;Irish Sea&quot; &quot;St. George\&apos;s Channel&quot; &quot;Donegal Bay&quot; &quot;Dingle Bay&quot; &quot;Celtic Sea&quot; &quot;Western Approaches&quot; &quot;Finisterre Bay&quot; &quot;Lusitanian Sea&quot; &quot;Gulf of Cadiz&quot; &quot;Straits of Gibraltar&quot; &quot;Gulf of Almeria&quot; &quot;Gulf of Valencia&quot; &quot;Gulf of Lion&quot; &quot;Cote D\&apos;Azur&quot; &quot;Ligurian Sea&quot; &quot;Coast of the Faeroes&quot; &quot;Western Mediterranean&quot; &quot;Barbary Coast&quot; &quot;Cape Bon&quot; &quot;Tyrrenean Sea&quot; &quot;Bay of Napoli&quot; &quot;Gulf of Gabes&quot; &quot;Sao Tome&quot; &quot;Straits of Messina&quot; &quot;Gulf of Venice&quot; &quot;Adriatic Sea&quot; &quot;Straits of Otranto&quot; &quot;Gulf of Taranto&quot; &quot;Ionian Sea&quot; &quot;Gulf of Sirte&quot; &quot;Gulf of Bomba&quot; &quot;Bay of Alexandria&quot; &quot;Palestinian Coast&quot; &quot;Gulf of Cyprus&quot; &quot;Spi&#x0161;&quot; &quot;Aegean Sea&quot; &quot;Sea of Marmara&quot; &quot;Gulf of Varna&quot; &quot;Gulf of Odessa&quot; &quot;Sea of Azov&quot; &quot;Eastern Black Sea&quot; &quot;Lake Balaton&quot; &quot;Caspian Sea&quot; &quot;Aral Sea&quot; &quot;Gulf of Suez&quot; &quot;Red Sea&quot; &quot;Bab el Mandeb&quot; &quot;Gulf of Aden&quot; &quot;Gulf of Oman&quot; &quot;Gulf of Masirah&quot; &quot;Straits of Hormuz&quot; &quot;Persian Gulf&quot; &quot;Coast of Makran&quot; &quot;Coast of Gujarat&quot; &quot;Konkan Coast&quot; &quot;Malabar Coast&quot; &quot;Comorin Cape&quot; &quot;Coast of Coromandel&quot; &quot;Coast of Orissa&quot; &quot;Ganges Delta&quot; &quot;Arakan Coast&quot; &quot;Irrawady Delta&quot; &quot;Eastern Bay of Bengal&quot; &quot;Andaman Sea&quot; &quot;Straits of Malacca&quot; &quot;Nicobar Islands&quot; &quot;Coast of Aceh&quot; &quot;Coast of Sumatra&quot; &quot;Sunda Strait&quot; &quot;Coast of Java&quot; &quot;Coast of Blambangan&quot; &quot;Straits of Lombok&quot; &quot;Sawu Sea&quot; &quot;Flores Sea&quot; &quot;Java Sea&quot; &quot;Straits of Makassar&quot; &quot;Karimata Strait&quot; &quot;Straits of Johor&quot; &quot;Malayan Sea&quot; &quot;Coast of Sarawak&quot; &quot;Cape C&#x00E0; Mau&quot; &quot;Gulf of Siam&quot; &quot;Cam Ranh Bay&quot; &quot;South China Sea&quot; &quot;Palawan Passage&quot; &quot;Coast of Annam&quot; &quot;Gulf of Tonkin&quot; &quot;Guangzhou Bay&quot; &quot;Taiwan Strait&quot; &quot;Yang Tse Delta&quot; &quot;Eastern Yellow Sea&quot; &quot;Korea Bay&quot; &quot;South Korean Sea&quot; &quot;North Korean Sea&quot; &quot;Olga Bay&quot; &quot;Tatar Straits&quot; &quot;Shantar Islands&quot; &quot;Tauisk Bay&quot; &quot;Bay of Komenskoie&quot; &quot;Coast of Kamchatka&quot; &quot;Okhotsk Sea&quot; &quot;Coast of Sakhalin&quot; &quot;Soya Strait&quot; &quot;Tsugaru Strait&quot; &quot;Yamato Basin&quot; &quot;Amakusa Sea&quot; &quot;Seto Inland Sea&quot; &quot;Kii Channel&quot; &quot;Ryukyu Islands&quot; &quot;Luzon Strait&quot; &quot;Paracel Islands&quot; &quot;Manila Bay&quot; &quot;Coast of Luzon&quot; &quot;Visayan Sea&quot; &quot;Sulu Sea&quot; &quot;Sea of Celebes&quot; &quot;Halmaheran Sea&quot; &quot;Banda Sea&quot; &quot;Mindanao Coast&quot; &quot;Palau Islands&quot; &quot;Cenderawasih Bay&quot; &quot;Vitiaz Strait&quot; &quot;Trobrian Islands&quot; &quot;Torres Strait&quot; &quot;Timor Sea&quot; &quot;Arafura Sea&quot; &quot;Gulf of Carpentaria&quot; &quot;Great Barrier Reef&quot; &quot;Coral Sea&quot; &quot;Flinders Bay&quot; &quot;Bass Strait&quot; &quot;Kangaroo Island&quot; &quot;Great Australian Bight&quot; &quot;Cape Leeuwin&quot; &quot;Houtman Abrolhos&quot; &quot;Northwest Cape&quot; &quot;Roebuck Bay&quot; &quot;Western Tasman Sea&quot; &quot;Macquarie Harbour&quot; &quot;Cook Strait&quot; &quot;Lord Howe Island&quot; &quot;Northern Tasman Sea&quot; &quot;Coast of New Zealand&quot; &quot;Southern Tasman Sea&quot; &quot;Canterbury Bight&quot; &quot;New Caledonian Sea&quot; &quot;Vanuatu Islands&quot; &quot;Fiji Basin&quot; &quot;Solomon Sea&quot; &quot;Tuvalu Islands&quot; &quot;Melanesia Sea&quot; &quot;Mariana Islands&quot; &quot;Philippine Sea&quot; &quot;Northern Philippine Sea&quot; &quot;Volcano Islands&quot; &quot;Izu Islands&quot; &quot;Sanriku Coast&quot; &quot;Kuril Islands&quot; &quot;Kamchatka Trench&quot; &quot;Ulakhan Fault&quot; &quot;Bay of Anadyr&quot; &quot;Bering Sea&quot; &quot;Horn of Africa&quot; &quot;Coast of Pepper&quot; &quot;Zanzibar Strait&quot; &quot;Mozambique Channel&quot; &quot;Diego Suarez Bay&quot; &quot;Southwestern Arabian Sea&quot; &quot;Northern Arabian Sea&quot; &quot;The Seychelles&quot; &quot;Coast of Tamatave&quot; &quot;The Mascareignes&quot; &quot;Coast of Menabe&quot; &quot;Coast of Sofala&quot; &quot;Coast of Natal&quot; &quot;Coast of Ciskei&quot; &quot;Cape of Good Hope&quot; &quot;Coast of Namibia&quot; &quot;Coast of Angola&quot; &quot;Gulf of Kongo&quot; &quot;Coast of Cameroon&quot; &quot;Gulf of Guinea&quot; &quot;Ivory Coast&quot; &quot;Grain Coast&quot; &quot;Coast of Gambia&quot; &quot;Bay of Arguin&quot; &quot;Mauretanian Coast&quot; &quot;Cape Bojador&quot; &quot;Coast of Morocco&quot; &quot;Jan Mayen Sea&quot; &quot;Spitzberg Sea&quot; &quot;Icelandic Sea&quot; &quot;Eastern Coast of Iceland&quot; &quot;Western Coast of Iceland&quot; &quot;Northeastern Atlantic&quot; &quot;Rockall&quot; &quot;Denmark Strait&quot; &quot;Eastern Coast of Greenland&quot; &quot;Western Coast of Greenland&quot; &quot;Labrador Strait&quot; &quot;Baffin Bay&quot; &quot;Hudson Straits&quot; &quot;James Bay&quot; &quot;Western Hudson Bay&quot; &quot;Eastern Hudson Bay&quot; &quot;Foxe Basin&quot; &quot;Gulf of St. Lawrence&quot; &quot;Cabot Strait&quot; &quot;Bay of Fundy&quot; &quot;Strait of Belle Isle&quot; &quot;Fortune Bay&quot; &quot;Notre Dame Bay&quot; &quot;Labrador Sea&quot; &quot;Greenland Sea&quot; &quot;Northern Atlantic&quot; &quot;Massachusetts Bay&quot; &quot;Delaware Bay&quot; &quot;Cape Hatteras&quot; &quot;Sea Islands&quot; &quot;Bahama Banks&quot; &quot;Western Sargasso Sea&quot; &quot;Florida Straits&quot; &quot;Apalachee Bay&quot; &quot;Mobile Bay&quot; &quot;Galveston Bay&quot; &quot;Tampico Bay&quot; &quot;Bay of Campeche&quot; &quot;Gulf of Mexico&quot; &quot;Yucatan Channel&quot; &quot;Gulf of Honduras&quot; &quot;Mosquito Coast&quot; &quot;Gulf of Darien&quot; &quot;Jamaica Channel&quot; &quot;Central Caribbean&quot; &quot;Northwestern Caribbean&quot; &quot;Venezuelan Gulf&quot; &quot;Venezuelan Sea&quot; &quot;Eastern Caribbean&quot; &quot;Windward Islands&quot; &quot;Lesser Antilles&quot; &quot;Turks &amp; Caicos Sea&quot; &quot;Bahama Channel&quot; &quot;Mona Passage&quot; &quot;Guyana Coast&quot; &quot;Cape Orange&quot; &quot;Amazonas Gulf&quot; &quot;Coast of Brazil&quot; &quot;Coast of Pernambuco&quot; &quot;Coast of Porto Seguro&quot; &quot;Costa Verde&quot; &quot;Coast of Santa Catarina&quot; &quot;Patos Lagoon&quot; &quot;La Plata River&quot; &quot;Northern Coast of Patagonia&quot; &quot;Southern Coast of Patagonia&quot; &quot;Magellan Strait&quot; &quot;Gulf of Penas&quot; &quot;Coast of Chile&quot; &quot;Atacama Coast&quot; &quot;Coast of Antofagasta&quot; &quot;Arica Bend&quot; &quot;Coast of Peru&quot; &quot;Gulf of Guayaquil&quot; &quot;Coast of Ecuador&quot; &quot;Gulf of Panama&quot; &quot;Costa Rica&quot; &quot;Gulf of Tehuantepec&quot; &quot;Manzanillo Bay&quot; &quot;Mazatlan Bay&quot; &quot;Gulf of California&quot; &quot;Cape San Lucas&quot; &quot;Gulf of Catalina&quot; &quot;San Francisco Bay&quot; &quot;Cape Blanco&quot; &quot;Salish Sea&quot; &quot;Hecate Strait&quot; &quot;Glacier Bay&quot; &quot;Cook Inlet&quot; &quot;Norton Sound&quot; &quot;Hatton Bank&quot; &quot;Eastern Gibbs Fracture&quot; &quot;Western Gibbs Fracture&quot; &quot;Iberian Shelf&quot; &quot;Sea of Azores&quot; &quot;Corner Seamounts&quot; &quot;Sable Island Bank&quot; &quot;New England Seamounts&quot; &quot;Blake Plateau&quot; &quot;West Bermuda Sea&quot; &quot;East Bermuda Sea&quot; &quot;Antilles Current&quot; &quot;Northern Guiana Basin&quot; &quot;Guiana Basin&quot; &quot;Southern Guiana Basin&quot; &quot;Canary Approach&quot; &quot;Cape Verde Approach&quot; &quot;Central North Atlantic&quot; &quot;North Equatorial Current&quot; &quot;Northeast Sargasso Sea&quot; &quot;Southeast Sargasso Sea&quot; &quot;Romanche Gap&quot; &quot;East Guinea Basin&quot; &quot;West Guinea Basin&quot; &quot;Coast of Falklands&quot; &quot;Scotia Basin&quot; &quot;Brazil-Malvinas Confluence Zone&quot; &quot;South Brazil Current&quot; &quot;Brazil Current&quot; &quot;Rio Grande Rise&quot; &quot;Argentine Basin&quot; &quot;South Orkney Islands&quot; &quot;East of Magellans&quot; &quot;North Brazil Current&quot; &quot;South Equatorial Current&quot; &quot;Central South Atlantic&quot; &quot;Brazil Basin&quot; &quot;Saint Helena Island&quot; &quot;Benguela Current&quot; &quot;Walvis Ridge&quot; &quot;Bouvet Island&quot; &quot;Tristan da Cunha Islands&quot; &quot;Southern Mid-Atlantic Ridget&quot; &quot;South Atlantic Current&quot; &quot;South Sandwich Islands&quot; &quot;South Atlantic&quot; &quot;South Atlantic Roaring Forties&quot; &quot;Denmark Sea&quot; &quot;Northern Bay of Bengal&quot; &quot;Western Bay of Bengal&quot; &quot;Southern Bay of Bengal&quot; &quot;Ceylon Sea&quot; &quot;Southeastern Arabian Sea&quot; &quot;North Indian Ocean&quot; &quot;Mascarene Plateau&quot; &quot;Western Equatorial Counter Current&quot; &quot;Coast of Maldives&quot; &quot;Central Indian Ocean&quot; &quot;Chagos Archipelago&quot; &quot;Eastern Equatorial Counter Current&quot; &quot;Ninetyeast Ridge&quot; &quot;Northeast Indian Ocean&quot; &quot;Marion Island&quot; &quot;Natal Basin&quot; &quot;Taolagnaro Bay&quot; &quot;Crozet Islands&quot; &quot;Crozet Basin&quot; &quot;Madagascar Basin&quot; &quot;Kerguelen Islands&quot; &quot;Heard and McDonald Islands&quot; &quot;South Indian Ocean&quot; &quot;Indian Ocean Raging Fifties&quot; &quot;South Australian Basin&quot; &quot;Southwestern Indian Ridge&quot; &quot;St Paul and Amsterdam Islands&quot; &quot;Southeastern Indian Ridge&quot; &quot;Naturaliste Plateau&quot; &quot;Broken Ridge&quot; &quot;East Indian Ocean&quot; &quot;Zenith Plateau&quot; &quot;Wallaby Plateau&quot; &quot;West Australian Basin&quot; &quot;Eastern Indian Ocean South Equatorial Current&quot; &quot;Indian Ocean South Equatorial Current&quot; &quot;Western Indian Ocean South Equatorial Current&quot; &quot;Lake Tchad&quot; &quot;Lake Victoria&quot; &quot;Lake Tanganyika&quot; &quot;Lake Malawi&quot; &quot;White Sea&quot; &quot;Lake Balchasj&quot; &quot;Lake Bajkal&quot; &quot;Poyang Lake&quot; &quot;Lake Titicaca&quot; &quot;Lake Nicaragua&quot; &quot;Lake Okeechobee&quot; &quot;Lake Ontario&quot; &quot;Lake Erie&quot; &quot;Lake Huron&quot; &quot;Lake Michigan&quot; &quot;Lake Superior&quot; &quot;Lake Nipigon&quot; &quot;Lake Winnipeg&quot; &quot;Commander Basin&quot; &quot;Emperor Ridge&quot; &quot;Northwestern Pacific&quot; &quot;Oyashio Current&quot; &quot;Northern Kuroshio Current&quot; &quot;Kuroshio Current&quot; &quot;Western Pacific&quot; &quot;Micronesia Sea&quot; &quot;Mariana Trench&quot; &quot;North Pacific Equatorial Current&quot; &quot;Melanesian Basin&quot; &quot;Kuskokwim Bay&quot; &quot;Bering Strait&quot; &quot;Shirshov Ridge&quot; &quot;Aleutian Islands&quot; &quot;Shumagin Islands&quot; &quot;Gulf of Alaska&quot; &quot;Western Aleutian Trench&quot; &quot;Northern California Current&quot; &quot;Eastern Aleutian Trench&quot; &quot;Eastern North Pacific Drift&quot; &quot;California Current&quot; &quot;Murray Fracture Zone&quot; &quot;North Pacific Drift&quot; &quot;Western North Pacific Drift&quot; &quot;Wake Island&quot; &quot;Midway Island&quot; &quot;Molokai Fracture Zone&quot; &quot;Southern California Current&quot; &quot;Revilla Gigedo Islands&quot; &quot;Clarion Fracture Zone&quot; &quot;Coast of Hawaii&quot; &quot;Marshall Islands&quot; &quot;Central Pacific Basin&quot; &quot;Cocos Ridge&quot; &quot;Guatemala Basin&quot; &quot;Galapagos Islands&quot; &quot;Nazca Ridge&quot; &quot;Juan Fernandez Islands&quot; &quot;Chile Rise&quot; &quot;West of Magellans&quot; &quot;Clipperton Island&quot; &quot;Galapagos Rise&quot; &quot;Peru Current&quot; &quot;Humboldt Current&quot; &quot;East Pacific Rise&quot; &quot;South Equatorial Pacific Current&quot; &quot;Easter Island&quot; &quot;North Pacific Converge Zone&quot; &quot;Eastern Equatorial Pacific Current&quot; &quot;Clipperton Fracture Zone&quot; &quot;Southern Humboldt Current&quot; &quot;Mornington Abyssal Plain&quot; &quot;South Pacific Raging Fifties&quot; &quot;Tharp Fault&quot; &quot;South Pacific Roaring Forties&quot; &quot;Louisville Seamount Chain&quot; &quot;Chatham Islands&quot; &quot;Southeast Pacific&quot; &quot;Tuamotu Islands&quot; &quot;Samoa Islands&quot; &quot;Bass Islands&quot; &quot;Society Islands&quot; &quot;South Pacific&quot; &quot;East Pacific Ridge&quot; &quot;Eltanin Fracture Zone&quot; &quot;Kiribati Islands&quot; &quot;Phoenix Islands&quot; &quot;Gilbert Islands&quot; &quot;Line Islands&quot; &quot;Western Equatorial Pacific Counter Current&quot; &quot;Marquesas Islands&quot; &quot;Flint Island&quot; &quot;Pitcairn Islands&quot; &quot;Equatorial Pacific Counter Current&quot; &quot;Tiki Basin&quot; &quot;Upper Guelders&quot; &quot;Cambray&quot; &quot;Antwerpen&quot; &quot;Cantabria&quot; &quot;Burgos&quot; &quot;Extremadura&quot; &quot;Ja&#x00E9;n&quot; &quot;Cadiz&quot; &quot;Alicante&quot; &quot;Ceuta&quot; &quot;Rzhev&quot; &quot;Kostroma&quot; &quot;Murom&quot; &quot;Ustyug&quot; &quot;Bessarabia&quot; &quot;Oberpfalz&quot; &quot;Hanover&quot; &quot;Potsdam&quot; &quot;Koblenz&quot; &quot;Pfalz&quot; &quot;Kassel&quot; &quot;Niederlausitz&quot; &quot;Burgas&quot; &quot;Sofia&quot; &quot;Kosovo&quot; &quot;Slavonia&quot; &quot;Lienz&quot; &quot;G&#x00F6;rz&quot; &quot;Ostmarch&quot; &quot;Erz&quot; &quot;Pozsony&quot; &quot;Achaea&quot; &quot;Treviso&quot; &quot;Holstein&quot; &quot;White Karelia&quot; &quot;Kola&quot; &quot;Kasimov&quot; &quot;Rub\&apos; al Khali&quot; &quot;Komi&quot; &quot;Western Siberia&quot; &quot;Central Siberia&quot; &quot;Eastern Siberia&quot; &quot;Tian Shan&quot; &quot;Pamir&quot; &quot;Takla Makan&quot; &quot;Himalaya&quot; &quot;Arunachal&quot; &quot;Papua&quot; &quot;Western Australia&quot; &quot;Central Australia&quot; &quot;Merina&quot; &quot;El Djouf&quot; &quot;Central Sahara&quot; &quot;East Sahara&quot; &quot;Central Africa&quot; &quot;Northern Congo Basin&quot; &quot;Imatong&quot; &quot;Urgoma&quot; &quot;Limpopo&quot; &quot;Kalahari&quot; &quot;Western Amazonas&quot; &quot;Eastern Amazonas&quot; &quot;Greenland&quot; &quot;Ungava&quot; &quot;Weagamow&quot; &quot;Baffin&quot; &quot;Great Basin&quot; &quot;S&#x00F3;\&apos;taeo\&apos;o&quot; &quot;Alaska&quot; &quot;Nunavut&quot; &quot;Northwest Territories&quot; &quot;Saskatchewan&quot; &quot;Columbia&quot; &quot;Pathein&quot; &quot;Beijing&quot; &quot;Nan&quot; &quot;Chikuzen&quot; &quot;Tosa&quot; &quot;Awa&quot; &quot;Nanjing&quot; &quot;Suzhou&quot; &quot;Stung Treng&quot; &quot;Wenzhou&quot; &quot;Aki&quot; &quot;Lika&quot; &quot;Raska&quot; &quot;Donji Kraji&quot; &quot;Quanzhou&quot; &quot;Tajima&quot; &quot;Travunia&quot; &quot;Ji\&apos;an&quot; &quot;Yamato&quot; &quot;Dorpat&quot; &quot;Mino&quot; &quot;Luoyang&quot; &quot;Etchu&quot; &quot;Hefei&quot; &quot;Suruga&quot; &quot;Guilin&quot; &quot;Marienburg&quot; &quot;Narva&quot; &quot;Kozuke&quot; &quot;Xiankhouang&quot; &quot;Pyeongyang&quot; &quot;Amasya&quot; &quot;Shiribeshi&quot; &quot;Hamid&quot; &quot;Hama&quot; &quot;Yaran&quot; &quot;Coimbra&quot; &quot;Tokachi&quot; &quot;Kastoria&quot; &quot;Jaffa&quot; &quot;Sidon&quot; &quot;Abkhazia&quot; &quot;Lauenburg&quot; &quot;Stettin&quot; &quot;Chelmno&quot; &quot;Norfolk&quot; &quot;Derby&quot; &quot;Cremona&quot; &quot;Graz&quot; &quot;Somogy&quot; &quot;Ghent&quot; &quot;Namur&quot; &quot;Vaud&quot; &quot;Augsburg&quot; &quot;Z&#x00FC;rich&quot; &quot;St Gallen&quot; &quot;Wallis&quot; &quot;Ulm&quot; &quot;Graub&#x00FC;nden&quot; &quot;Bremen&quot; &quot;Cuneo&quot; &quot;Frankfurt&quot; &quot;Charolais&quot; &quot;Aachen&quot; &quot;Alen&#x00E7;on&quot; &quot;Sundgau&quot; &quot;St. Martin&quot; &quot;Annaba&quot; &quot;Western Finnish Lakes&quot; &quot;East Finnish Lakes&quot; &quot;Central Finnish Lakes&quot; &quot;Storavan&quot; &quot;Storsj&#x00F6;n&quot; &quot;Kara Sea&quot; &quot;Lake Geneva&quot; &quot;Lake Constance&quot; &quot;Lake Tuz&quot; &quot;Lake Van&quot; &quot;Lake Urmia&quot; &quot;Sevan Lake&quot; &quot;Lake Taihu&quot; &quot;Lake Hongze&quot; &quot;Dongting&quot; &quot;Tonl&#x00E9; Sap Lake&quot; &quot;Tana Lake&quot; &quot;Lake Turkana&quot; &quot;Mpangu&quot; &quot;Lake Poopo&quot; &quot;Lake Champlain&quot; &quot;Lake Saint-Jean&quot; &quot;Lake Manicouagan&quot; &quot;Lake Michikamau&quot; &quot;Lake Bienville&quot; &quot;Clearwater Lakes&quot; &quot;Lake Minto&quot; &quot;La Grande River&quot; &quot;Lake Island&quot; &quot;Lake Reindeer&quot; &quot;Wollaston Lake&quot; &quot;Great Slave Lake&quot; &quot;Lake Athabasca&quot; &quot;Dubawni Lake&quot; &quot;Yathkyed Lake&quot; &quot;Kasba Lake&quot; &quot;Nueltin Lake&quot; &quot;Wholdaia Lake&quot; &quot;Peter Pond Lake&quot; &quot;Great Salt Lake&quot; &quot;Williston Lake&quot; &quot;Greenland Tip&quot; &quot;Tana&quot; &quot;Northern Baltic Sea&quot; &quot;Eastern Baltic Sea&quot; &quot;Western Sea of &#x00C5;land&quot; &quot;Western Norwegian Sea&quot; &quot;&#x00C5;land&quot; &quot;East Frisia&quot; &quot;Gulf of Satalia&quot; &quot;Bari&quot; &quot;Lucania&quot; &quot;Mitau&quot; &quot;Kovno&quot; &quot;Grodno&quot; &quot;Wizna&quot; &quot;Leczyca&quot; &quot;Belz&quot; &quot;Turov&quot; &quot;Zhytomyr&quot; &quot;Bratslav&quot; &quot;Cherkasy&quot; &quot;Severia&quot; &quot;Desh&quot; &quot;Gingee&quot; &quot;Bidar&quot; &quot;Rayalaseema&quot; &quot;Meghalaya&quot; &quot;Hunyad&quot; &quot;Maramaros&quot; &quot;Szabolcs&quot; &quot;Toront&#x00E1;l&quot; &quot;Kholmogory&quot; &quot;Suzdal&quot; &quot;Galich&quot; &quot;Kargopol&quot; &quot;Torzhok&quot; &quot;Ostrov&quot; &quot;Ladoga&quot; &quot;Kudymkar&quot; &quot;Cherdyn&quot; &quot;Ust-Sysolsk&quot; &quot;Buzuluk&quot; &quot;Chelyaba&quot; &quot;Khujand&quot; &quot;Kulob&quot; &quot;Sozak&quot; &quot;Syghnak&quot; &quot;Beljamen&quot; &quot;Udmurtia&quot; &quot;Urgench&quot; &quot;Yedishkul&quot; &quot;North Sea&quot; &quot;Dead Sea&quot; &quot;M&#x00E4;laren&quot; &quot;Shetland&quot; &quot;F&#x00E4;r&#x00F6;arna&quot; &quot;Hokuriku Coast&quot; &quot;Bornholm&quot; &quot;Blekinge&quot; &quot;Lolland&quot; &quot;Nordjylland&quot; &quot;N&#x00E4;rke&quot; &quot;New Caledonia&quot; &quot;Society Islands&quot; &quot;Rapanui&quot; &quot;Tonga&quot; &quot;Tuvalu&quot; &quot;Gilbert Islands&quot; &quot;Nauru&quot; &quot;Marshall Islands&quot; &quot;Wake&quot; &quot;Micronesia&quot; &quot;Palau&quot; &quot;Midway&quot; &quot;Christmas Island&quot; &quot;Cocos Island&quot; &quot;Qinghai Lake&quot; &quot;Siling Lake&quot; &quot;Gal&#x00E1;pagos Islands&quot; &quot;Ktunaxa&quot; &quot;Niitsitapi&quot; &quot;Asinaan&quot; &quot;Aps&#x00E1;alooke&quot; &quot;Arikara&quot; &quot;Lakota&quot; &quot;Oglala&quot; &quot;Connecticut&quot; &quot;Shenandoah&quot; &quot;Arsigantegok&quot; &quot;Androscoggin&quot; &quot;Natchitoches&quot; &quot;Nipigon&quot; &quot;Bungi&quot; &quot;Nehiyawewin&quot; &quot;Tsuu Tina&quot; &quot;Nimiipu&quot; &quot;Bannock&quot; &quot;Miwok&quot; &quot;Haida&quot; &quot;Munsee&quot; &quot;Garoowe&quot; &quot;Tanjore&quot; &quot;Arcot&quot; &quot;Mahur&quot; &quot;South Kanara&quot; &quot;Goa&quot; &quot;Morasanadu&quot; &quot;Malenadu&quot; &quot;Savanur&quot; &quot;Pune&quot; &quot;Gulbarga&quot; &quot;Baglana&quot; &quot;Warangal&quot; &quot;Midnapore&quot; &quot;Sunderbans&quot; &quot;Sadiya&quot; &quot;Manipur&quot; &quot;Koch Hajo&quot; &quot;Balasore&quot; &quot;Bhagalpur&quot; &quot;Barind&quot; &quot;Nasirabad&quot; &quot;Tirhut&quot; &quot;Garjat&quot; &quot;Khurda&quot; &quot;Chanda&quot; &quot;Bhavnagar&quot; &quot;Navanagar&quot; &quot;Patan&quot; &quot;Ahmadabad&quot; &quot;Gorakhpur&quot; &quot;Rewakantha&quot; &quot;Bhilsa&quot; &quot;Mewar&quot; &quot;Kalpi&quot; &quot;Upper Doab&quot; &quot;Katehar&quot; &quot;Panipat&quot; &quot;Etawah&quot; &quot;Shekhawati&quot; &quot;Bhattiana&quot; &quot;Nagaur&quot; &quot;Gorwar&quot; &quot;Siwi&quot; &quot;Kumaon&quot; &quot;Chaubisi Rajya&quot; &quot;Limbuwan&quot; &quot;Bhakkar&quot; &quot;Baltistan&quot; &quot;Ladakh&quot; &quot;Doaba&quot; &quot;Sialkot&quot; &quot;Margalla&quot; &quot;Sind Sagar&quot; &quot;Derajat&quot; &quot;Srikakulam&quot; &quot;Lakhnor&quot; &quot;Raipur&quot; &quot;Kosta&quot; &quot;Konaseema&quot; &quot;Tiruchirappalli&quot; &quot;Cholistan&quot; &quot;Ajmer&quot; &quot;Umarkot&quot; &quot;Chaul&quot; &quot;Kurnool&quot; &quot;Tripura&quot; &quot;Mahadeo&quot; &quot;Mandsaur&quot; &quot;Bahreich&quot; &quot;Varanasi&quot; &quot;Damin&quot; &quot;Baghelkhand&quot; &quot;Surguja&quot; &quot;Kandy&quot; &quot;Vanni&quot; &quot;Tirunelveli&quot; &quot;Urkan&quot; &quot;Udi&quot; &quot;Birija&quot; &quot;Kuru&quot; &quot;Furdan&quot; &quot;Ningguta&quot; &quot;Huncun&quot; &quot;Boduna&quot; &quot;Yehe&quot; &quot;Hetu Ala&quot; &quot;Andong&quot; &quot;Gaizhou&quot; &quot;Ereen&quot; &quot;Chahar&quot; &quot;Ih Huree&quot; &quot;Zasagt&quot; &quot;Urzhar&quot; &quot;Chuguchak&quot; &quot;Ili&quot; &quot;Kuqa&quot; &quot;Hami&quot; &quot;Qakilik&quot; &quot;Yarkand&quot; &quot;Kochkor&quot; &quot;Chuy&quot; &quot;Yashilkul&quot; &quot;Ngari&quot; &quot;Changtang&quot; &quot;Nyingchi&quot; &quot;Qamdo&quot; &quot;Markam&quot; &quot;Dege&quot; &quot;Rebgong&quot; &quot;Garze&quot; &quot;Xuanhua&quot; &quot;Daming&quot; &quot;Wuding&quot; &quot;Laizhou&quot; &quot;Yanzhou&quot; &quot;Xuzhou&quot; &quot;Huai\&apos;an&quot; &quot;Fengyang&quot; &quot;Fuyang&quot; &quot;Zhenjiang&quot; &quot;Ningguo&quot; &quot;Huizhou&quot; &quot;Shaoxin&quot; &quot;Ningbo&quot; &quot;Jinhua&quot; &quot;Poyang&quot; &quot;Jianning&quot; &quot;Tingzhou&quot; &quot;Kelang&quot; &quot;Middag&quot; &quot;Chaochow&quot; &quot;Waichow&quot; &quot;Shiukwan&quot; &quot;Leichow&quot; &quot;Ngaichow&quot; &quot;Limchow&quot; &quot;Ngchow&quot; &quot;Liuzhou&quot; &quot;Namning&quot; &quot;Pu\&apos;er&quot; &quot;Dehong&quot; &quot;Lijiang&quot; &quot;Bozhou&quot; &quot;Langzhong&quot; &quot;Songqu&quot; &quot;Xiangyang&quot; &quot;Jingzhou&quot; &quot;Yuanling&quot; &quot;Hengyang&quot; &quot;Runing&quot; &quot;Shangqiu&quot; &quot;Ningwu&quot; &quot;Lu\&apos;an&quot; &quot;Yan\&apos;an&quot; &quot;Tianshui&quot; &quot;Pingliang&quot; &quot;Liangzhou&quot; &quot;Taozhou&quot; &quot;Xining&quot; &quot;Mergen&quot; &quot;Iman&quot; &quot;Sartu&quot; &quot;Alchuka&quot; &quot;Tsetserleg&quot; &quot;Qaraqorum&quot; &quot;Ejin&quot; &quot;Korla&quot; &quot;Govi&quot; &quot;Kunlun&quot; &quot;Adyghe&quot; &quot;Guria&quot; &quot;Kabardia&quot; &quot;Khundzia&quot; &quot;Tarki&quot; &quot;Suleiman Range&quot; &quot;Alania&quot; &quot;Melikates&quot; &quot;Kakheti&quot; &quot;Kars&quot; &quot;Nakhchivan&quot; &quot;Urmia&quot; &quot;Maragheh&quot; &quot;Terek&quot; &quot;Ilam&quot; &quot;Kirmanshah&quot; &quot;Ardalan&quot; &quot;Zanjan&quot; &quot;Qom&quot; &quot;Golestan&quot; &quot;Qazvin&quot; &quot;Semnan&quot; &quot;Yasuj&quot; &quot;Shiraz&quot; &quot;Bandar Langeh&quot; &quot;Bam&quot; &quot;Mashhad&quot; &quot;Ardakan&quot; &quot;Larestan&quot; &quot;Ferah&quot; &quot;Bamyan&quot; &quot;Jalalabad&quot; &quot;Kunduz&quot; &quot;Maymana&quot; &quot;Bust&quot; &quot;Chakhansur&quot; &quot;Bela&quot; &quot;Kharan&quot; &quot;Chabahar&quot; &quot;Rafsanjan&quot; &quot;Sabzevar&quot; &quot;Bojnord&quot; &quot;Tekrur&quot; &quot;Kantor&quot; &quot;Siine&quot; &quot;Galam&quot; &quot;Beafada&quot; &quot;Karou&quot; &quot;Termes&quot; &quot;Tagant&quot; &quot;Wagadu&quot; &quot;Baghena&quot; &quot;Hodh&quot; &quot;Do&quot; &quot;Sibiridugu&quot; &quot;Bendugu&quot; &quot;Guinea&quot; &quot;Lobi&quot; &quot;Gwiriko&quot; &quot;Bonoman&quot; &quot;Gyaaman&quot; &quot;Dagbon&quot; &quot;Denkyira&quot; &quot;Cape Coast&quot; &quot;Sah&quot; &quot;Mema&quot; &quot;Kala&quot; &quot;Karabara&quot; &quot;Haayre&quot; &quot;Hombori&quot; &quot;Liptako&quot; &quot;Bilanga&quot; &quot;Tenkodogo&quot; &quot;Aribanda&quot; &quot;Zarmaganda&quot; &quot;Dallol&quot; &quot;Azawagh&quot; &quot;Azbin&quot; &quot;Ader&quot; &quot;Air&quot; &quot;Tenere&quot; &quot;Itesan&quot; &quot;Kawar&quot; &quot;Kebbi&quot; &quot;Daura&quot; &quot;Biram&quot; &quot;Rano&quot; &quot;Muniyo&quot; &quot;Bedde&quot; &quot;Manga&quot; &quot;Marghi&quot; &quot;Logone&quot; &quot;Kotoko&quot; &quot;Yao&quot; &quot;Ondo&quot; &quot;Ijebu&quot; &quot;Ketu&quot; &quot;Moshi&quot; &quot;Yawuri&quot; &quot;Warri&quot; &quot;Atakora&quot; &quot;Karasi&quot; &quot;Saruhan&quot; &quot;Tekke&quot; &quot;Bolu&quot; &quot;Bozok&quot; &quot;Kayseri&quot; &quot;I&#x00E7;el&quot; &quot;Malatya&quot; &quot;Canik&quot; &quot;Erzincan&quot; &quot;Mush&quot; &quot;Van&quot; &quot;Urfa&quot; &quot;Sinjar&quot; &quot;Tikrit&quot; &quot;Samawat&quot; &quot;Wasit&quot; &quot;Antioch&quot; &quot;Rahba&quot; &quot;Suez&quot; &quot;Al Gharbia&quot; &quot;Minya&quot; &quot;Bahiriya&quot; &quot;Manfalut&quot; &quot;Ras Gharib&quot; &quot;Queseer&quot; &quot;Wadi Halfa&quot; &quot;Sahra an N&#x00FC;byah&quot; &quot;Halaib&quot; &quot;Tarrana&quot; &quot;Bardiyah&quot; &quot;Maan&quot; &quot;Al Ula&quot; &quot;Yanbu&quot; &quot;Ma\&apos;din Sulaym&quot; &quot;Jeddah&quot; &quot;Turubah&quot; &quot;Zufra&quot; &quot;Badiyat ash Sham&quot; &quot;Dawasir&quot; &quot;Aflaj&quot; &quot;Buraydah&quot; &quot;Hafar&quot; &quot;Yabrin&quot; &quot;Grane&quot; &quot;Masirah&quot; &quot;Wusta&quot; &quot;Kathiri&quot; &quot;Marib&quot; &quot;Beihan&quot; &quot;Jazan&quot; &quot;Hofuf&quot; &quot;Chios&quot; &quot;Kizil-Su&quot; &quot;Konjikala&quot; &quot;Shekty&quot; &quot;Alty-Kuduk&quot; &quot;Tortkara&quot; &quot;Shegendyk&quot; &quot;Narym&quot; &quot;Shymkent&quot; &quot;Aksary&quot; &quot;Altyn&quot; &quot;Baganaly&quot; &quot;Tobykty&quot; &quot;Dzhaman-Kuduk&quot; &quot;Gurganj&quot; &quot;Atakent&quot; &quot;Talas&quot; &quot;Orda&quot; &quot;Utva&quot; &quot;Lower Yik&quot; &quot;Karamegdan&quot; &quot;Lower Ishim&quot; &quot;Kungirot&quot; &quot;Song La&quot; &quot;Hai Phong&quot; &quot;Hue&quot; &quot;Kauthara&quot; &quot;Tay Nguyen&quot; &quot;Prek Russey&quot; &quot;Teuk Khmao&quot; &quot;Kratie&quot; &quot;Battambang&quot; &quot;Phnom Penh&quot; &quot;Luang Namtha&quot; &quot;Savanh Nakhone&quot; &quot;Khukhanor Surin&quot; &quot;Nong Khai&quot; &quot;Nongbua Lamphu&quot; &quot;Chaiyaphum&quot; &quot;Phetchaburi&quot; &quot;Phitsanulok&quot; &quot;Phra Bang&quot; &quot;Chaiya&quot; &quot;Thalang&quot; &quot;Selangor&quot; &quot;Terengganu&quot; &quot;Kedah&quot; &quot;Hkamti Long&quot; &quot;Mong Kawng&quot; &quot;Tamanthi&quot; &quot;Thaungdut&quot; &quot;Pagan&quot; &quot;Hsipaw&quot; &quot;Mong Pai&quot; &quot;Sandoway&quot; &quot;Martaban&quot; &quot;Mergui&quot; &quot;Bender&quot; &quot;Ingil&quot; &quot;Pereyaslav&quot; &quot;Yelets&quot; &quot;Bahmut&quot; &quot;Theodoro&quot; &quot;Mansur&quot; &quot;Kyzyl-Yar&quot; &quot;Tyn&quot; &quot;Azaraba&quot; &quot;Etkara&quot; &quot;Majar&quot; &quot;Kuma&quot; &quot;Ukek&quot; &quot;Kanadey&quot; &quot;Agyidel&quot; &quot;Juketau&quot; &quot;Veda-Suvar&quot; &quot;Alatyr&quot; &quot;Peremyshl&quot; &quot;Nenets&quot; &quot;Yamal&quot; &quot;Ostyaki&quot; &quot;Yugan&quot; &quot;Agan&quot; &quot;Baykha&quot; &quot;Uchamin&quot; &quot;Chulym&quot; &quot;Vah&quot; &quot;Barnaul&quot; &quot;Nukhtui&quot; &quot;Chuna&quot; &quot;Seganka&quot; &quot;Kharya&quot; &quot;Yarmanka&quot; &quot;Kagyrgyn&quot; &quot;Iglino&quot; &quot;Ust-Kut&quot; &quot;Kan&quot; &quot;Bashgird&quot; &quot;Mangazea&quot; &quot;Chara&quot; &quot;Matrega&quot; &quot;Fezzan&quot; &quot;Jufra&quot; &quot;Ghadames&quot; &quot;Thubaqt&quot; &quot;Zuwarah&quot; &quot;Sfax&quot; &quot;Kef&quot; &quot;Bizerte&quot; &quot;Touggourt&quot; &quot;Mzab&quot; &quot;Hodna&quot; &quot;Titteri&quot; &quot;Saoura&quot; &quot;Dahra&quot; &quot;Ouarsenis&quot; &quot;Kasdir&quot; &quot;Ouarzazate&quot; &quot;Oujda&quot; &quot;Draa&quot; &quot;Meknes&quot; &quot;Tadla&quot; &quot;Dukkala&quot; &quot;Haha&quot; &quot;Chott el-Jerid&quot; &quot;Ouargla&quot; &quot;Sousse&quot; &quot;Tajhari&quot; &quot;Djado&quot; &quot;Kumeyaay&quot; &quot;Yuki&quot; &quot;Tachi&quot; &quot;Maidu&quot; &quot;Shasta&quot; &quot;Klamath&quot; &quot;Kalapuya&quot; &quot;Umatilla&quot; &quot;Quileute&quot; &quot;Chehalis&quot; &quot;Yakima&quot; &quot;Spokane&quot; &quot;Palus&quot; &quot;Bohogue&quot; &quot;Goshute&quot; &quot;Hualapai&quot; &quot;Chiricahua&quot; &quot;Hopi&quot; &quot;Zuni&quot; &quot;Acoma&quot; &quot;Jicarilla&quot; &quot;Lipiyanes&quot; &quot;Jumano&quot; &quot;Coahuilteco&quot; &quot;Querecho&quot; &quot;Piegan&quot; &quot;Haaninin&quot; &quot;Ashshipite&quot; &quot;Eeelalapito&quot; &quot;Tsisistas&quot; &quot;Kuccuntikka&quot; &quot;Baachinena&quot; &quot;Skiri&quot; &quot;Utsetha&quot; &quot;Hidatsa&quot; &quot;Itscheabine&quot; &quot;Wahpekute&quot; &quot;Moingwena&quot; &quot;Michigamea&quot; &quot;Satuskhdin&quot; &quot;Adai&quot; &quot;Mdewakanton&quot; &quot;Noquet&quot; &quot;Kilatika&quot; &quot;Mengkonkia&quot; &quot;Okouara&quot; &quot;Mascouten&quot; &quot;Piankeshaw&quot; &quot;Wabash&quot; &quot;Chillicothe&quot; &quot;Shatteras&quot; &quot;Chickamauga&quot; &quot;Yazoo&quot; &quot;Natchez&quot; &quot;Biloxi&quot; &quot;Napochi&quot; &quot;Tohome&quot; &quot;Chatot&quot; &quot;Yustaga&quot; &quot;Calusa&quot; &quot;Mayaimi&quot; &quot;Hitchiti&quot; &quot;Yamasee&quot; &quot;Mocama&quot; &quot;Coweta&quot; &quot;Saluda&quot; &quot;Cusabo&quot; &quot;Waccamaw&quot; &quot;Yadkin&quot; &quot;Waxhaw&quot; &quot;Chicora&quot; &quot;Roanoke&quot; &quot;Tutelo&quot; &quot;Moratok&quot; &quot;Doeg&quot; &quot;Monongahela&quot; &quot;Manahoac&quot; &quot;Potomac&quot; &quot;Nanticoke&quot; &quot;Honniasont&quot; &quot;Juniata&quot; &quot;Atrakwaye&quot; &quot;Espachomy&quot; &quot;Adirondack&quot; &quot;Quinnipiac&quot; &quot;Wampanoag&quot; &quot;Pennacook&quot; &quot;Missisquoi&quot; &quot;Sokoki&quot; &quot;Kennebec&quot; &quot;Passamaquoddy&quot; &quot;Aroostook&quot; &quot;Kespukwitk&quot; &quot;Eskikewakik&quot; &quot;Wolystoq&quot; &quot;Madawaska&quot; &quot;Siknikt&quot; &quot;Placentia&quot; &quot;Sikumiut&quot; &quot;Naskapi&quot; &quot;Mingan&quot; &quot;Manicouagan&quot; &quot;Anticosti&quot;</Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Keywords6">&quot;Piekouagami&quot; &quot;Atikamekw&quot; &quot;Timiskaming&quot; &quot;Maliseet&quot; &quot;Etchemins&quot; &quot;Loup&quot; &quot;Kichesipi&quot; &quot;Tionontate&quot; &quot;Odawa&quot; &quot;Piscatang&quot; &quot;Kesagami&quot; &quot;Shaggami&quot; &quot;Outoulibi&quot; &quot;Omushkego&quot; &quot;Wappus&quot; &quot;Quennebigon&quot; &quot;Kesyehotinne&quot; &quot;Mahmikiwiniyak&quot; &quot;Sipiwininiwak&quot; &quot;Hebina&quot; &quot;Athabasca&quot; &quot;Nihithawak&quot; &quot;Danezaa&quot; &quot;Siksikawa&quot; &quot;Sekani&quot; &quot;Dakelh&quot; &quot;Secwepemc&quot; &quot;Tsilhoqotin&quot; &quot;Okanagan&quot; &quot;Rocky Mountains&quot; &quot;Nisga\&apos;a&quot; &quot;Heiltsuk&quot; &quot;Kodiak&quot; &quot;Eyak&quot; &quot;Sitka&quot; &quot;Cotoname&quot; &quot;Guamares&quot; &quot;Seri&quot; &quot;Huichol&quot; &quot;Toboso&quot; &quot;Laguneros&quot; &quot;Nakipa&quot; &quot;Tizapan&quot; &quot;Cuitzeo&quot; &quot;Cutzamala&quot; &quot;Patzcuaro&quot; &quot;Hinonoeino&quot; &quot;Tullucan&quot; &quot;Cihuatlan&quot; &quot;Tepeacac&quot; &quot;Coyolapan&quot; &quot;Tochtepec&quot; &quot;Mixe&quot; &quot;Xicallanco&quot; &quot;Mani&quot; &quot;Uaymil&quot; &quot;Chiapas&quot; &quot;Chacujal&quot; &quot;Chortli&quot; &quot;Xocnochco&quot; &quot;Raritan&quot; &quot;Lenca&quot; &quot;Tziccoac&quot; &quot;Metztitlan&quot; &quot;Apatzingan&quot; &quot;Cholula&quot; &quot;Teloloapan&quot; &quot;Coixtlahuacan&quot; &quot;Cuetlaxtlan&quot; &quot;Yopitzinco&quot; &quot;Tehuantepec&quot; &quot;Champutun&quot; &quot;Ah Canul&quot; &quot;Ecab&quot; &quot;Iximch&#x00E9;&quot; &quot;Baracoa&quot; &quot;Bayamo&quot; &quot;Camaguey&quot; &quot;Colima&quot; &quot;Maguana&quot; &quot;Magua&quot; &quot;Managua&quot; &quot;Uluas&quot; &quot;Olancho&quot; &quot;Nicoya&quot; &quot;Veraguas&quot; &quot;Eyeish&quot; &quot;Tuintsund&#x00E9;&quot; &quot;Cacaxtes&quot; &quot;Borrado&quot; &quot;Hasinai&quot; &quot;Tkaronto&quot; &quot;Missisage&quot; &quot;Kitkehaki&quot; &quot;Pasai&quot; &quot;Peureulak&quot; &quot;Rokan&quot; &quot;Indragiri&quot; &quot;Jambi&quot; &quot;Bangka&quot; &quot;Belitung&quot; &quot;Muko-Muko&quot; &quot;Pagarruyung&quot; &quot;Pariaman&quot; &quot;Mentawai&quot; &quot;Nias&quot; &quot;Gayo&quot; &quot;Bintan&quot; &quot;Pakuan&quot; &quot;Cirebon&quot; &quot;Kendal&quot; &quot;Pajang&quot; &quot;Kediri&quot; &quot;Madura&quot; &quot;Lombok&quot; &quot;Gangneung&quot; &quot;East Timor&quot; &quot;Yamdena&quot; &quot;Tondo&quot; &quot;Pangasinan&quot; &quot;Bikol&quot; &quot;Panay&quot; &quot;Tagloc&quot; &quot;Butuan&quot; &quot;Lehad Datu&quot; &quot;Sibu&quot; &quot;Kuching&quot; &quot;Katapang&quot; &quot;Barito&quot; &quot;Sampit&quot; &quot;Tarakan&quot; &quot;Berau&quot; &quot;Bulungan&quot; &quot;Samarinda&quot; &quot;Gorontalo&quot; &quot;Palu&quot; &quot;Palopo&quot; &quot;Buton&quot; &quot;Sula&quot; &quot;Fak-Fak&quot; &quot;Madang&quot; &quot;Lae&quot; &quot;Kerema&quot; &quot;Daru&quot; &quot;Yos Sudarso&quot; &quot;Asmat&quot; &quot;Aru&quot; &quot;Malgana&quot; &quot;Minang&quot; &quot;Tiwi&quot; &quot;Yolngu&quot; &quot;Awngthim&quot; &quot;Guugu Yimithirr&quot; &quot;Wulgurukaba&quot; &quot;Baiali&quot; &quot;Yuin&quot; &quot;Gunditjmara&quot; &quot;Nukunu&quot; &quot;Ahuriri&quot; &quot;Waitaha&quot; &quot;Kirikiriroa&quot; &quot;Borneo&quot; &quot;Jeju&quot; &quot;Yukjin&quot; &quot;Gyeongseong&quot; &quot;Nyeongbyeon&quot; &quot;Gyeongju&quot; &quot;Vidin&quot; &quot;Khara Narin Ula&quot; &quot;Jianchang&quot; &quot;Tikhvin&quot; &quot;Plovdiv&quot; &quot;Cuenca&quot; &quot;Romsdal&quot; &quot;Narbonne&quot; &quot;La Mancha&quot; &quot;Soria&quot; &quot;Welayta&quot; &quot;Kaffa&quot; &quot;Illubabor&quot; &quot;Gambela&quot; &quot;Hadiya&quot; &quot;Arsi&quot; &quot;Damot&quot; &quot;Asosa&quot; &quot;Ausa&quot; &quot;Assab&quot; &quot;Mendefera&quot; &quot;Enderta&quot; &quot;Angot&quot; &quot;Lasta&quot; &quot;Agew&quot; &quot;Semien&quot; &quot;Dembiya&quot; &quot;Mora&quot; &quot;Kismayo&quot; &quot;Merca&quot; &quot;Afgooye&quot; &quot;Bardera&quot; &quot;Werder&quot; &quot;Afder&quot; &quot;Beledweyne&quot; &quot;Gedo&quot; &quot;Warsheikh&quot; &quot;Hobyo&quot; &quot;Galkayo&quot; &quot;El Buur&quot; &quot;Bosaso&quot; &quot;Hamasien&quot; &quot;Hafun&quot; &quot;Las Khorey&quot; &quot;Sanaag&quot; &quot;Ankober&quot; &quot;Togdheer&quot; &quot;Hargeisa&quot; &quot;Barawa&quot; &quot;Meregh&quot; &quot;Pate&quot; &quot;Shendy&quot; &quot;Soba&quot; &quot;Sennar&quot; &quot;Kosti&quot; &quot;Medwa&quot; &quot;Kobbe&quot; &quot;Orinoco Delta&quot; &quot;Guasipati&quot; &quot;Uyapari&quot; &quot;Guajira&quot; &quot;Altagracia&quot; &quot;Coro&quot; &quot;Llanos&quot; &quot;Apure&quot; &quot;Atabapo&quot; &quot;Pore&quot; &quot;Merida&quot; &quot;Meta&quot; &quot;Puerto Carreno&quot; &quot;Guaviare&quot; &quot;Neiva&quot; &quot;Popayan&quot; &quot;Darien&quot; &quot;Esmeraldas&quot; &quot;Piwra&quot; &quot;Tucume&quot; &quot;Moyobamba&quot; &quot;Wankapampa&quot; &quot;Pisqupampa&quot; &quot;Chimbote&quot; &quot;Huaraz&quot; &quot;Camana&quot; &quot;Ayaviri&quot; &quot;Quero&quot; &quot;Tiahuanaco&quot; &quot;San Joaquin&quot; &quot;Madre de Dios&quot; &quot;Santa Cruz de la Sierra&quot; &quot;Sucre&quot; &quot;Tucuman&quot; &quot;Santa Catalina&quot; &quot;Tarija&quot; &quot;Puna de Atacama&quot; &quot;Calama&quot; &quot;Antofagasta&quot; &quot;Santiago del Estero&quot; &quot;La Rioja&quot; &quot;Chepes&quot; &quot;San Juan&quot; &quot;Quisquisacate&quot; &quot;San Luis&quot; &quot;Santa Fe&quot; &quot;Rosario&quot; &quot;Montevideo&quot; &quot;Colonia&quot; &quot;Salto&quot; &quot;Yareyu&quot; &quot;Chaco Central&quot; &quot;Misiones&quot; &quot;Highveld&quot; &quot;Rio Grande do Sul&quot; &quot;Santiago&quot; &quot;Itap&#x00FA;a&quot; &quot;Querandi&quot; &quot;Sauce&quot; &quot;Coquimbo&quot; &quot;Rio Negro&quot; &quot;Senqu&quot; &quot;Puelches&quot; &quot;Olavarria&quot; &quot;Chanar&quot; &quot;San Antonio&quot; &quot;Florida Blanca&quot; &quot;Tehuelmapu&quot; &quot;Poya&quot; &quot;Chiquiyami&quot; &quot;Chiloe&quot; &quot;Aysen&quot; &quot;Chubut&quot; &quot;Teush&quot; &quot;Mendoza&quot; &quot;Matara&quot; &quot;Santa Tecla&quot; &quot;Griqualand&quot; &quot;Corumba&quot; &quot;Fuerte Borbon&quot; &quot;Melodia&quot; &quot;Povos das Missoes&quot; &quot;Barra&quot; &quot;Parnaiba&quot; &quot;Santa Catarina&quot; &quot;Cuiaba&quot; &quot;Rio Branco&quot; &quot;Maraj&#x00F3;&quot; &quot;Santo Antonio da Manga&quot; &quot;Araxas&quot; &quot;Ofaie&quot; &quot;Sao Joao del Rei&quot; &quot;Castro&quot; &quot;Campinas&quot; &quot;Araraquara&quot; &quot;Serro&quot; &quot;Vila Rica&quot; &quot;Guapore&quot; &quot;Cerejeiras&quot; &quot;Vila Bela&quot; &quot;Caceres&quot; &quot;Diamantino&quot; &quot;Rio Das Mortes&quot; &quot;Ipora&quot; &quot;Vila Boa&quot; &quot;Arrial dos Couros&quot; &quot;Conceicao&quot; &quot;Pontal&quot; &quot;Natividad&quot; &quot;Sergipe&quot; &quot;Jeremoabo&quot; &quot;Inhambupe&quot; &quot;Pambu&quot; &quot;Rio Contas&quot; &quot;Paratinga&quot; &quot;Campo Largo&quot; &quot;Luziana&quot; &quot;Coxim&quot; &quot;Alagoas&quot; &quot;Borborema&quot; &quot;Pastos Bons&quot; &quot;Timon&quot; &quot;Parnagua&quot; &quot;Grajau&quot; &quot;Alcantara&quot; &quot;Tucurui&quot; &quot;Para&quot; &quot;Santarem&quot; &quot;Pirara&quot; &quot;Waddai&quot; &quot;Barcelos&quot; &quot;Manaus&quot; &quot;Muturu&quot; &quot;Guyana&quot; &quot;Suriname&quot; &quot;Oiapoque&quot; &quot;Zaraza&quot; &quot;Chichas&quot; &quot;Choquechaca&quot; &quot;Charcas&quot; &quot;Chachapoyas&quot; &quot;Ucayali&quot; &quot;Yurimaguas&quot; &quot;Quillacas&quot; &quot;Macaya&quot; &quot;Matamba&quot; &quot;Mbata&quot; &quot;Buhera&quot; &quot;Manikya&quot; &quot;Madanda&quot; &quot;Hj&#x00E4;lmaren&quot; &quot;Djerba&quot; &quot;Ingolstadt&quot; &quot;Straubing&quot; &quot;Regensburg&quot; &quot;Osterode&quot; &quot;Tarnow&quot; &quot;Nowy Sacz&quot; &quot;Lwow&quot; &quot;Rowne&quot; &quot;Notec&quot; &quot;Altmark&quot; &quot;Vogtland&quot; &quot;Glogau&quot; &quot;Eger&quot; &quot;Budejovice&quot; &quot;Sternberg&quot; &quot;Hradecko&quot; &quot;Hoya&quot; &quot;Paderborn&quot; &quot;Meppen&quot; &quot;Loon&quot; &quot;Kleves&quot; &quot;Umbria&quot; &quot;Urbino&quot; &quot;Arezzo&quot; &quot;Novara&quot; &quot;Lucca&quot; &quot;Montferrat&quot; &quot;Syracuse&quot; &quot;Salerno&quot; &quot;Cosenza&quot; &quot;Capitanata&quot; &quot;Cagliari&quot; &quot;Urgell&quot; &quot;Tarragona&quot; &quot;Rioja&quot; &quot;Teruel&quot; &quot;Forcalquier&quot; &quot;Albenga&quot; &quot;Uckermark&quot; &quot;Greifswald&quot; &quot;Stolp&quot; &quot;Wismar&quot; &quot;Tuchola&quot; &quot;Buzau&quot; &quot;Hormuz&quot; &quot;Nis&quot; &quot;Skopje&quot; &quot;Visoki&quot; &quot;Euboea&quot; &quot;Comoros&quot; &quot;Antankara&quot; &quot;Iboina&quot; &quot;Tsimihety&quot; &quot;Maroantsetra&quot; &quot;Vatomandry&quot; &quot;Antemoro&quot; &quot;Betsileo&quot; &quot;Mahafaly&quot; &quot;Antanosy&quot; &quot;Bara&quot; &quot;Antsalova&quot; &quot;Fiherana&quot; &quot;Al Qadarif&quot; &quot;Makua&quot; &quot;Ngindo&quot; &quot;Wayao&quot; &quot;Katsekera&quot; &quot;Lolo&quot; &quot;Lundu&quot; &quot;Kalonga&quot; &quot;Kinga&quot; &quot;Makonde&quot; &quot;Phangwa&quot; &quot;Ngonde&quot; &quot;Tumbuka&quot; &quot;Lala&quot; &quot;Nsenga&quot; &quot;Lomwe&quot; &quot;Ibo&quot; &quot;Luangwa&quot; &quot;Ewaso Ngiro&quot; &quot;Dawa&quot; &quot;Turkana&quot; &quot;Kuria&quot; &quot;Shamba&quot; &quot;Gogo&quot; &quot;Nyatura&quot; &quot;Zigua&quot; &quot;Shaga&quot; &quot;Kikuyu&quot; &quot;Buzinza&quot; &quot;Busoga&quot; &quot;Karagwe&quot; &quot;Buganda&quot; &quot;Bunyoro&quot; &quot;Nkore&quot; &quot;Nduga&quot; &quot;Bafuriru&quot; &quot;Bushubi&quot; &quot;Nkoma&quot; &quot;Buyogoma&quot; &quot;Ruguru&quot; &quot;Hehe&quot; &quot;Pubungo&quot; &quot;Lango&quot; &quot;Muhambwe&quot; &quot;Rukwa&quot; &quot;Mayumba&quot; &quot;Ngoyo&quot; &quot;Soyo&quot; &quot;Songo&quot; &quot;Kasanje&quot; &quot;Shinje&quot; &quot;Malem&quot; &quot;Yaka&quot; &quot;Nunu&quot; &quot;Kumbana&quot; &quot;Munene&quot; &quot;Kuba&quot; &quot;Songye&quot; &quot;Mpasu&quot; &quot;Rund&quot; &quot;Lwena&quot; &quot;Chokwe&quot; &quot;Ishindi&quot; &quot;Kalundwe&quot; &quot;Luba&quot; &quot;Upemba&quot; &quot;Hemba&quot; &quot;Luapula&quot; &quot;Lualaba&quot; &quot;Bemba&quot; &quot;Tabwa&quot; &quot;Lamba&quot; &quot;Kusu&quot; &quot;Lenje&quot; &quot;Kanongesha&quot; &quot;Kaonde&quot; &quot;Lega&quot; &quot;Sutherland&quot; &quot;Saintonge&quot; &quot;Quercy&quot; &quot;Rovaniemi&quot; &quot;Jokkmokk&quot; &quot;Mazyr&quot; &quot;Oka&quot; &quot;Bezhetsk&quot; &quot;Cork&quot; &quot;Sligo&quot; &quot;Kildare&quot; &quot;Ulster&quot; &quot;Shenkursk&quot; &quot;Pirkanmaa&quot; &quot;Karelia&quot; &quot;Szolnok&quot; &quot;Bacs&quot; &quot;Turda&quot; &quot;Kir&#x00E1;lyf&#x00F6;ld&quot; &quot;Ust-Vym&quot; &quot;Somerset&quot; &quot;Mutsu&quot; &quot;Mweru&quot; &quot;Kivu&quot; &quot;Rutanzige&quot; &quot;Lake Albert&quot; &quot;Zaysan&quot; &quot;Alakol&quot; &quot;Issyk-Kul&quot; &quot;Ouluj&#x00E4;rvi&quot; &quot;Saimaa&quot; &quot;Dithmarschen&quot; &quot;&#x00D8;stjylland&quot; &quot;Sm&#x00E5;lenene&quot; &quot;Bratsberg&quot; &quot;Agdesiden&quot; &quot;Langfjella&quot; &quot;Rostov&quot; &quot;Luki&quot; &quot;Kolding&quot; &quot;&#x00C9;vora&quot; &quot;Enare&quot; &quot;Kainuu&quot; &quot;The Scandes&quot; &quot;The Pyrenees&quot; &quot;The Carpathians&quot; &quot;The Caucasus&quot; &quot;The Alps&quot; &quot;Janjiro&quot; &quot;The Alps&quot; &quot;The Alps&quot; &quot;The Alps&quot; &quot;The Alps&quot; &quot;Elfsborg&quot; &quot;Dal&quot; &quot;G&#x00F6;inge&quot; &quot;Tioh&#x00E4;rad&quot; &quot;High Atlas&quot; &quot;High Atlas&quot; &quot;Aures&quot; &quot;Zagros&quot; &quot;Abarquh&quot; &quot;Zagros&quot; &quot;Syrmia&quot; &quot;Durr&#x00EB;s&quot; &quot;Lezh&#x00EB;&quot; &quot;Branicevo&quot; &quot;Alborz&quot; &quot;Pontic Mountains&quot; &quot;Hakkari Mountains&quot; &quot;Hyuga&quot; &quot;Higo&quot; &quot;Hizen&quot; &quot;Iwami&quot; &quot;Bizen&quot; &quot;Tango&quot; &quot;Iyo&quot; &quot;Kii&quot; &quot;Shinano&quot; &quot;Sagami&quot; &quot;Shimousa&quot; &quot;Shimotsuke&quot; &quot;Ugo&quot; &quot;Oshima&quot; &quot;Yongping&quot; &quot;Zhending&quot; &quot;Haizhou&quot; &quot;Huangzhou&quot; &quot;Fengxiang&quot; &quot;Tongren&quot; &quot;Hulan&quot; &quot;Jianzhou&quot; &quot;Taining&quot; &quot;Ju Ud&quot; &quot;Anding&quot; &quot;Nagchu&quot; &quot;Balikul&quot; &quot;Turpan&quot; &quot;Qurqara-usu&quot; &quot;Maralbexi&quot; &quot;Yangi Hissar&quot; &quot;Dazhou&quot; &quot;Jiazhou&quot; &quot;Luzhou&quot; &quot;Kalar&quot; &quot;Fudali&quot; &quot;Ulch&quot; &quot;Pijin&quot; &quot;Buteha&quot; &quot;Bayan Tumen&quot; &quot;Khiagt&quot; &quot;Dundgovi&quot; &quot;Ulaangom&quot; &quot;Hetao&quot; &quot;Tokai Sea&quot; &quot;Hokkaido Coast&quot; &quot;Japan Basin&quot; &quot;Jinju&quot; &quot;Naju&quot; &quot;Chungju&quot; &quot;Suwon&quot; &quot;Haeju&quot; &quot;Ganggye&quot; &quot;Bohai Sea&quot; &quot;Western Yellow Sea&quot; &quot;Vistula Lagoon&quot; &quot;Trencin&quot; &quot;Olomouc&quot; &quot;Liegnitz&quot; &quot;Belgrade&quot; &quot;Fej&#x00E9;r&quot; &quot;Wenden&quot; &quot;Ula&quot; &quot;Toropets&quot; &quot;Trubchevsk&quot; &quot;Vyazma&quot; &quot;Mstislav&quot; &quot;Owrucz&quot; &quot;Kashin&quot; &quot;Zubtsov&quot; &quot;Mologa&quot; &quot;Mozhaisk&quot; &quot;Kolomna&quot; &quot;Yuriev&quot; &quot;Starodub&quot; &quot;Pronsk&quot; &quot;Solvychegodsk&quot; &quot;Mezen&quot; &quot;Onega&quot; &quot;Velsk&quot; &quot;Vyshny Volochyok&quot; &quot;Ustyuzhna&quot; &quot;Totma&quot; &quot;Sol Galitskaya&quot; &quot;Tetyushi&quot; &quot;Ar-Chally&quot; &quot;Izhkar&quot; &quot;Bolgar&quot; &quot;Aqabah&quot; &quot;Al Wajh&quot; &quot;Azraq&quot; &quot;Suwayda&quot; &quot;Al Jawf&quot; &quot;Al-Kariatan&quot; &quot;Sudayr&quot; &quot;Al-Yamamah&quot; &quot;Jabal Tubaiq&quot; &quot;Taif&quot; &quot;Qunfudhah&quot; &quot;Zabid&quot; &quot;Taiz&quot; &quot;Dhamar&quot; &quot;Sahda&quot; &quot;Shihr&quot; &quot;Al Ghaydah&quot; &quot;Baraimi&quot; &quot;Ash Sharqiyah&quot; &quot;Ibra&quot; &quot;Shatt&quot; &quot;Shushtar&quot; &quot;Hoveyzeh&quot; &quot;Qazaniya&quot; &quot;Mardin&quot; &quot;Arbil&quot; &quot;Sulimaniyeh&quot; &quot;Hisn Kayfa&quot; &quot;Bitlis&quot; &quot;Homs&quot; &quot;Ayntab&quot; &quot;Shamakhi&quot; &quot;Mianeh&quot; &quot;Kartli&quot; &quot;Bayazid&quot; &quot;Oltu&quot; &quot;Khoy&quot; &quot;Shaki&quot; &quot;Lakia&quot; &quot;Aksaray&quot; &quot;Denizli&quot; &quot;Aydin&quot; &quot;Divrigi&quot; &quot;Karahisar&quot; &quot;Sultan&#x00F6;n&#x00FC;&quot; &quot;Kangiri&quot; &quot;Kirshehir&quot; &quot;Tokat&quot; &quot;Sharqiya&quot; &quot;Buhaira&quot; &quot;Atfih&quot; &quot;Isna&quot; &quot;Girga&quot; &quot;Egyptian Desert&quot; &quot;Egyptian Desert&quot; &quot;Farafreh&quot; &quot;Ghuriyan&quot; &quot;Sarakhs&quot; &quot;Nishapur&quot; &quot;Jask&quot; &quot;Chagai&quot; &quot;Fasa&quot; &quot;Darab&quot; &quot;Kazerun&quot; &quot;Siraf&quot; &quot;Dahlak Archipelago&quot; &quot;Tabas&quot; &quot;Kashan&quot; &quot;Tun&quot; &quot;Savah&quot; &quot;Soltanieh&quot; &quot;Rasht&quot; &quot;Astara&quot; &quot;Sari&quot; &quot;Malamir&quot; &quot;Termez&quot; &quot;Kish&quot; &quot;Saidabad&quot; &quot;Qamr Bay&quot; &quot;Pirate Coast&quot; &quot;Ifugao&quot; &quot;Laguna&quot; &quot;Mindoro&quot; &quot;Buglas&quot; &quot;Cebu&quot; &quot;Leyte&quot; &quot;Zamboanga&quot; &quot;Caraga&quot; &quot;Taytay&quot; &quot;Cuyo Archipelago&quot; &quot;Philippine Trench&quot; &quot;Ise&quot; &quot;Mikawa&quot; &quot;East March&quot; &quot;West March&quot; &quot;Argyll&quot; &quot;Inner Hebrides&quot; &quot;Mann&quot; &quot;Montgomery&quot; &quot;Hull&quot; &quot;Scarborough&quot; &quot;Carmarthen&quot; &quot;Cambridge&quot; &quot;Sussex&quot; &quot;Coventry&quot; &quot;Devon&quot; &quot;Dorset&quot; &quot;Chester&quot; &quot;Leicester&quot; &quot;Ormond&quot; &quot;Desmond&quot; &quot;Midlands&quot; &quot;Donegal&quot; &quot;Oversticht&quot; &quot;Groningen&quot; &quot;Den Haag&quot; &quot;Rennais&quot; &quot;Cotentin&quot; &quot;Bas-Poitou&quot; &quot;Angoumois&quot; &quot;Chartres&quot; &quot;Touraine&quot; &quot;Troyes&quot; &quot;Vivarais&quot; &quot;Auxerrois&quot; &#x000D;&#x000A;&#x000D;&#x000A;&quot;Stockholm.&quot; &quot;&#x00D6;sterg&#x00F6;tland.&quot; &quot;Kalmar.&quot; &quot;Bergslagen.&quot; &quot;V&#x00E4;rmland.&quot; &quot;Lund.&quot; &quot;Skaraborg.&quot; &quot;Dalaskogen.&quot; &quot;H&#x00E4;lsingland.&quot; &quot;J&#x00E4;mtland.&quot; &quot;V&#x00E4;sterbotten.&quot; &quot;Sj&#x00E6;lland.&quot; &quot;Slesvig.&quot; &quot;Fyn.&quot; &quot;Vestjylland.&quot; &quot;Bohusl&#x00E4;n.&quot; &quot;Akershus.&quot; &quot;Lappland.&quot; &quot;&#x00D6;sterbotten.&quot; &quot;Tr&#x00F8;ndelag.&quot; &quot;H&#x00E5;logaland.&quot; &quot;Opplanda.&quot; &quot;Bergenhus.&quot; &quot;Stavanger.&quot; &quot;Gotland.&quot; &quot;Halland.&quot; &quot;&#x00C5;bo.&quot; &quot;Nyland.&quot; &quot;Tavastland.&quot; &quot;Viborg.&quot; &quot;Savolax.&quot; &quot;Kexholm.&quot; &quot;Neva.&quot; &quot;Ingermanland.&quot; &quot;&#x00D6;sel.&quot; &quot;Reval.&quot; &quot;Livland.&quot; &quot;Riga.&quot; &quot;Goldingen.&quot; &quot;Memel.&quot; &quot;K&#x00F6;nigsberg.&quot; &quot;Warmia.&quot; &quot;Danzig.&quot; &quot;Hamburg.&quot; &quot;L&#x00FC;beck.&quot; &quot;Rostock.&quot; &quot;Stralsund.&quot; &quot;Kolberg.&quot; &quot;Neumark.&quot; &quot;Berlin.&quot; &quot;Ruppin.&quot; &quot;Magdeburg.&quot; &quot;L&#x00FC;neburg.&quot; &quot;Stade.&quot; &quot;Oldenburg.&quot; &quot;Osnabr&#x00FC;ck.&quot; &quot;Brunswick.&quot; &quot;Anhalt.&quot; &quot;Wittenberg.&quot; &quot;Oberlausitz.&quot; &quot;Dresden.&quot; &quot;Leipzig.&quot; &quot;Th&#x00FC;ringen.&quot; &quot;Landshut.&quot; &quot;M&#x00FC;nchen.&quot; &quot;Bamberg.&quot; &quot;N&#x00FC;rnberg.&quot; &quot;Memmingen.&quot; &quot;Oberschwaben.&quot; &quot;W&#x00FC;rttemberg.&quot; &quot;Ansbach.&quot; &quot;Breisgau.&quot; &quot;Tirol.&quot; &quot;Baden.&quot; &quot;Elsass.&quot; &quot;Salzburg.&quot; &quot;Heidelberg.&quot; &quot;Mainz.&quot; &quot;W&#x00FC;rzburg.&quot; &quot;Trier.&quot; &quot;Hessen.&quot; &quot;Westfalen.&quot; &quot;Nassau.&quot; &quot;Berg.&quot; &quot;K&#x00F6;ln.&quot; &quot;M&#x00FC;nster.&quot; &quot;Calais.&quot; &quot;Artois.&quot; &quot;Picardie.&quot; &quot;Vlaanderen.&quot; &quot;Hainaut.&quot; &quot;Brussels.&quot; &quot;Li&#x00E8;ge.&quot; &quot;Luxemburg.&quot; &quot;Breda.&quot; &quot;Zeeland.&quot; &quot;Amsterdam.&quot; &quot;Utrecht.&quot; &quot;Gelre.&quot; &quot;Friesland.&quot; &quot;Genoa.&quot; &quot;Nice.&quot; &quot;Piedmont.&quot; &quot;Milan.&quot; &quot;Parma.&quot; &quot;Modena.&quot; &quot;Brescia.&quot; &quot;Verona.&quot; &quot;Mantua.&quot; &quot;Trent.&quot; &quot;Friuli.&quot; &quot;Venezia.&quot; &quot;Ferrara.&quot; &quot;Romagna.&quot; &quot;Pisa.&quot; &quot;Firenze.&quot; &quot;Siena.&quot; &quot;Roma.&quot; &quot;Ancona.&quot; &quot;Abruzzi.&quot; &quot;Napoli.&quot; &quot;Salento.&quot; &quot;Calabria.&quot; &quot;Messina.&quot; &quot;Palermo.&quot; &quot;Malta.&quot; &quot;Sassari.&quot; &quot;K&#x00E4;rnten.&quot; &quot;Krain.&quot; &quot;Istria.&quot; &quot;Zagreb.&quot; &quot;Steiermark.&quot; &quot;Linz.&quot; &quot;Wien.&quot; &quot;Sopron.&quot; &quot;Dalmatia.&quot; &quot;Ragusa.&quot; &quot;Zeta.&quot; &quot;Hum.&quot; &quot;Bosnia.&quot; &quot;Smederevo.&quot; &quot;Corfu.&quot; &quot;Vlor&#x00EB;.&quot; &quot;Epirus.&quot; &quot;Morea.&quot; &quot;Athens.&quot; &quot;Thessaly.&quot; &quot;Macedonia.&quot; &quot;Edirne.&quot; &quot;Tarnovo.&quot; &quot;Constantinople.&quot; &quot;Varasd.&quot; &quot;Pest.&quot; &quot;Hont.&quot; &quot;B&#x00E9;k&#x00E9;s.&quot; &quot;Temes.&quot; &quot;Bihar.&quot; &quot;Maros.&quot; &quot;Silistria.&quot; &quot;Oltenia.&quot; &quot;T&#x00EE;rgoviste.&quot; &quot;Zempl&#x00E9;n.&quot; &quot;Crete.&quot; &quot;Naxos.&quot; &quot;Bern.&quot; &quot;Waldst&#x00E4;tte.&quot; &quot;Caux.&quot; &quot;Caen.&quot; &quot;Armor.&quot; &quot;Finist&#x00E8;re.&quot; &quot;Vannetais.&quot; &quot;Nantais.&quot; &quot;Labourd.&quot; &quot;Aquitaine.&quot; &quot;Armagnac.&quot; &quot;B&#x00E9;arn.&quot; &quot;Maine.&quot; &quot;Anjou.&quot; &quot;Berry.&quot; &quot;Haut-Poitou.&quot; &quot;Rethel.&quot; &quot;Valois.&quot; &quot;Paris.&quot; &quot;Orleanais.&quot; &quot;Nemours.&quot; &quot;Reims.&quot; &quot;Barrois.&quot; &quot;Metz.&quot; &quot;Lothringen.&quot; &quot;Bourbonnais.&quot; &quot;Nivernais.&quot; &quot;Dijonnais.&quot; &quot;Franche-Comt&#x00E9;.&quot; &quot;P&#x00E9;rigord.&quot; &quot;Limousin.&quot; &quot;Toulouse.&quot; &quot;Roussillon.&quot; &quot;Rouergue.&quot; &quot;Auvergne.&quot; &quot;Montpellier.&quot; &quot;Provence.&quot; &quot;Avignon.&quot; &quot;Lyonnais.&quot; &quot;Dauphin&#x00E9;.&quot; &quot;Savoie.&quot; &quot;Galicia.&quot; &quot;Asturias.&quot; &quot;Le&#x00F3;n.&quot; &quot;Vizcaya.&quot; &quot;Navarra.&quot; &quot;Pirineo.&quot; &quot;Girona.&quot; &quot;Barcelona.&quot; &quot;Zaragoza.&quot; &quot;Castilla La Vieja.&quot; &quot;Salamanca.&quot; &quot;Madrid.&quot; &quot;Badajoz.&quot; &quot;Toledo.&quot; &quot;Val&#x00E8;ncia.&quot; &quot;Murcia.&quot; &quot;Almer&#x00ED;a.&quot; &quot;Granada.&quot; &quot;Sevilla.&quot; &quot;C&#x00F3;rdoba.&quot; &quot;Gibraltar.&quot; &quot;Lisboa.&quot; &quot;Beira.&quot; &quot;Beja.&quot; &quot;Algarve.&quot; &quot;Porto.&quot; &quot;Bragan&#x00E7;a.&quot; &quot;Cornwall.&quot; &quot;Hampshire.&quot; &quot;Kent.&quot; &quot;London.&quot; &quot;Oxford.&quot; &quot;Essex.&quot; &quot;Gloucester.&quot; &quot;Shrewsbury.&quot; &quot;Glamorgan.&quot; &quot;Gwynedd.&quot; &quot;Lincolnshire.&quot; &quot;Lancashire.&quot; &quot;York.&quot; &quot;Northumberland.&quot; &quot;Cumbria.&quot; &quot;Lothian.&quot; &quot;Ayrshire.&quot; &quot;Perth.&quot; &quot;Aberdeen.&quot; &quot;Inverness.&quot; &quot;Outer Hebrides.&quot; &quot;Poznan.&quot; &quot;Kalisz.&quot; &quot;Plock.&quot; &quot;Warszawa.&quot; &quot;Sieradz.&quot; &quot;Sandomierz.&quot; &quot;Lublin.&quot; &quot;Halicz.&quot; &quot;Krakow.&quot; &quot;Ratibor.&quot; &quot;Breslau.&quot; &quot;Brno.&quot; &quot;Prague.&quot; &quot;Plzen.&quot; &quot;Moldavia.&quot; &quot;Podlasie.&quot; &quot;Trakai.&quot; &quot;Samogitia.&quot; &quot;Vilna.&quot; &quot;Latgalia.&quot; &quot;Pskov.&quot; &quot;Polotsk.&quot; &quot;Minsk.&quot; &quot;Brest.&quot; &quot;Pinsk.&quot; &quot;Volhynia.&quot; &quot;Kiev.&quot; &quot;Podolia.&quot; &quot;Yedisan.&quot; &quot;Zaporozhia.&quot; &quot;Crimea.&quot; &quot;Caffa.&quot; &quot;Azov.&quot; &quot;Kuban.&quot; &quot;Lower Don.&quot; &quot;Chernigov.&quot; &quot;Poltava.&quot; &quot;Kharkov.&quot; &quot;Mogilev.&quot; &quot;Smolensk.&quot; &quot;Tver.&quot; &quot;Moskva.&quot; &quot;Kaluga.&quot; &quot;Bryansk.&quot; &quot;Kursk.&quot; &quot;Voronezh.&quot; &quot;Tula.&quot; &quot;Ryazan.&quot; &quot;Tambov.&quot; &quot;Saratov.&quot; &quot;Penza.&quot; &quot;Perm.&quot; &quot;Nizhny Novgorod.&quot; &quot;Vladimir.&quot; &quot;Yaroslavl.&quot; &quot;Olonets.&quot; &quot;Novgorod.&quot; &quot;Kholm.&quot; &quot;Beloozero.&quot; &quot;Soroka.&quot; &quot;Vologda.&quot; &quot;Finnmark.&quot; &quot;Kocaeli.&quot; &quot;H&#x00FC;davendigar.&quot; &quot;Sugla.&quot; &quot;Mentese.&quot; &quot;Rhodes.&quot; &quot;Cyprus.&quot; &quot;K&#x00FC;tahya.&quot; &quot;Konya.&quot; &quot;Karaman.&quot; &quot;Kastamonu.&quot; &quot;Ankara.&quot; &quot;Adana.&quot; &quot;Sinop.&quot; &quot;Sivas.&quot; &quot;Trebizond.&quot; &quot;Erzurum.&quot; &quot;Marash.&quot; &quot;The Baleares.&quot; &quot;Tangiers.&quot; &quot;Melilla.&quot; &quot;Tlemcen.&quot; &quot;Oran.&quot; &quot;Mitidja.&quot; &quot;Kabylia.&quot; &quot;Constantine.&quot; &quot;Tunis.&quot; &quot;Gharb.&quot; &quot;Fez.&quot; &quot;Marrakech.&quot; &quot;Abda.&quot; &quot;Tafilalt.&quot; &quot;Ifni.&quot; &quot;Sus.&quot; &quot;Figuig.&quot; &quot;Laghouat.&quot; &quot;Biskra.&quot; &quot;Gafsa.&quot; &quot;Tataouine.&quot; &quot;Tripoli.&quot; &quot;Sirt.&quot; &quot;Benghazi.&quot; &quot;Darnah.&quot; &quot;Alexandria.&quot; &quot;Fayyum.&quot; &quot;Qus.&quot; &quot;Cairo.&quot; &quot;Rosetta.&quot; &quot;Damietta.&quot; &quot;Gaza.&quot; &quot;Sinai.&quot; &quot;The Canarias.&quot; &quot;The Azores.&quot; &quot;Madeira.&quot; &quot;Orkney.&quot; &quot;Reykjavik.&quot; &quot;Akureyri.&quot; &quot;Tyrone.&quot; &quot;Pale.&quot; &quot;Leinster.&quot; &quot;Limerick.&quot; &quot;Connaught.&quot; &quot;Aleppo.&quot; &quot;Tarabulus.&quot; &quot;Jerusalem.&quot; &quot;Al Karak.&quot; &quot;Ajlun.&quot; &quot;Damascus.&quot; &quot;Tabuk.&quot; &quot;Medina.&quot; &quot;Mecca.&quot; &quot;Bishah.&quot; &quot;Mokha.&quot; &quot;Aden.&quot; &quot;Mukalla.&quot; &quot;Sana\&apos;a.&quot; &quot;Najran.&quot; &quot;Al-Arid.&quot; &quot;Jabal Shammar.&quot; &quot;Al-Qatif.&quot; &quot;Qatar.&quot; &quot;Bahrain.&quot; &quot;Bani Yas.&quot; &quot;Qawasim.&quot; &quot;Batinah.&quot; &quot;Muscat.&quot; &quot;Dhofar.&quot; &quot;Qishn.&quot; &quot;Nizwa.&quot; &quot;Liwa.&quot; &quot;Tadmor.&quot; &quot;Haditha.&quot; &quot;Ar Raqqa.&quot; &quot;Basra.&quot; &quot;Karbala.&quot; &quot;Baghdad.&quot; &quot;Mosul.&quot; &quot;Ahvaz.&quot; &quot;Khorramabad.&quot; &quot;Hamadan.&quot; &quot;Kirkuk.&quot; &quot;Tabriz.&quot; &quot;Lahijan.&quot; &quot;Diyarbakir.&quot; &quot;Yerevan.&quot; &quot;Ganja.&quot; &quot;Shirvan.&quot; &quot;Imereti.&quot; &quot;Tbilisi.&quot; &quot;Ardabil.&quot; &quot;Dagestan.&quot; &quot;Amol.&quot; &quot;Qumis.&quot; &quot;Teheran.&quot; &quot;Isfahan.&quot; &quot;Dashtistan.&quot; &quot;Mogostan.&quot; &quot;Kerman.&quot; &quot;Yazd.&quot; &quot;Quhistan.&quot; &quot;Zaranj.&quot; &quot;Birjand.&quot; &quot;Kopet Dag.&quot; &quot;Karakum.&quot; &quot;Mangyshlak.&quot; &quot;Qaraqalpak.&quot; &quot;Khiva.&quot; &quot;Bukhara.&quot; &quot;Ustyurt.&quot; &quot;Charjuy.&quot; &quot;Merv.&quot; &quot;Herat.&quot; &quot;Kandahar.&quot; &quot;Gazni.&quot; &quot;Ghor.&quot; &quot;Balkh.&quot; &quot;Kabul.&quot; &quot;Badakhshan.&quot; &quot;Qarshi.&quot; &quot;Samarkand.&quot; &quot;Kyzylkum.&quot; &quot;Turkestan.&quot; &quot;Tashkent.&quot; &quot;Kokand.&quot; &quot;Taraz.&quot; &quot;Uzkend.&quot; &quot;Almaty.&quot; &quot;Odishi.&quot; &quot;Circassia.&quot; &quot;Astrakhan.&quot; &quot;Nogay.&quot; &quot;Sarai.&quot; &quot;Borisoglebsk.&quot; &quot;Manych.&quot; &quot;Ryn.&quot; &quot;Bayuly.&quot; &quot;Alimuly.&quot; &quot;Zhetyru.&quot; &quot;Samara.&quot; &quot;Yaik.&quot; &quot;Bashkortostan.&quot; &quot;Kypshak.&quot; &quot;Nadym.&quot; &quot;Argyn.&quot; &quot;Kerey.&quot; &quot;Pegaya Orda.&quot; &quot;Bermuda.&quot; &quot;Bahamas.&quot; &quot;Turks Islands.&quot; &quot;Havana.&quot; &quot;Moron.&quot; &quot;Guantanamo.&quot; &quot;Jamaica.&quot; &quot;Les Cayes.&quot; &quot;Tortuga.&quot; &quot;Barahonas.&quot; &quot;Curacao.&quot; &quot;Borik&#x00E9;n.&quot; &quot;St. Thomas.&quot; &quot;St. Kitts.&quot; &quot;Antigua.&quot; &quot;Guadelupe.&quot; &quot;Dominica.&quot; &quot;Martinique.&quot; &quot;St. Lucia.&quot; &quot;St. Vincent.&quot; &quot;Barbados.&quot; &quot;Trinidad.&quot; &quot;Kutch.&quot; &quot;Thatta.&quot; &quot;Sehwan.&quot; &quot;Multan.&quot; &quot;Lahore.&quot; &quot;Kashmir.&quot; &quot;Kangra.&quot; &quot;Sirhind.&quot; &quot;Garhwal.&quot; &quot;Jangladesh.&quot; &quot;Jaisalmer.&quot; &quot;Marwar.&quot; &quot;Girnar.&quot; &quot;Baroda.&quot; &quot;Surat.&quot; &quot;Chittor.&quot; &quot;Dhundar.&quot; &quot;Mewat.&quot; &quot;Kathiawar.&quot; &quot;Delhi.&quot; &quot;Lucknow.&quot; &quot;Central Doab.&quot; &quot;Gird.&quot; &quot;Mandu.&quot; &quot;Khandesh.&quot; &quot;Hadoti.&quot; &quot;North Konkan.&quot; &quot;South Konkan.&quot; &quot;North Kanara.&quot; &quot;Raichur Doab.&quot; &quot;Mysore.&quot; &quot;Malabar.&quot; &quot;Kochin.&quot; &quot;Madurai.&quot; &quot;Venad.&quot; &quot;Kongu.&quot; &quot;Tondainadu.&quot; &quot;Coromandel.&quot; &quot;Vijayanagar.&quot; &quot;Golconda.&quot; &quot;Velanadu.&quot; &quot;Ahmadnagar.&quot; &quot;Marathwada.&quot; &quot;East Berar.&quot; &quot;Bastar.&quot; &quot;West Berar.&quot; &quot;Kalingandhra.&quot; &quot;Mahakoshal.&quot; &quot;Mandla.&quot; &quot;Cuttack.&quot; &quot;Sambalpur.&quot; &quot;Baisi Rajya.&quot; &quot;Jaunpur.&quot; &quot;Lower Doab.&quot; &quot;Katmandu.&quot; &quot;Patna.&quot; &quot;Bundelkhand.&quot; &quot;Jharkhand.&quot; &quot;Bengal Delta.&quot; &quot;Koch.&quot; &quot;Gauda.&quot; &quot;Dhaka.&quot; &quot;Bhutan.&quot; &quot;Assam.&quot; &quot;Silhet.&quot; &quot;Chittagong.&quot; &quot;Bijapur.&quot; &quot;Naga.&quot; &quot;Darrang.&quot; &quot;Kotte.&quot; &quot;Cachar.&quot; &quot;The Andamans.&quot; &quot;Gwadar.&quot; &quot;Kalat.&quot; &quot;Quetta.&quot; &quot;Roh.&quot; &quot;Mrauk U.&quot; &quot;Kale.&quot; &quot;Sagaing.&quot; &quot;Mong Yang.&quot; &quot;Hsenwi.&quot; &quot;Ava.&quot; &quot;Taungoo.&quot; &quot;Pegu.&quot; &quot;Kengtung.&quot; &quot;Mong Nai.&quot; &quot;Chiang Mai.&quot; &quot;Moulmein.&quot; &quot;Tavoy.&quot; &quot;Ratchaburi.&quot; &quot;Nakhon Si Thammarat.&quot; &quot;Pattani.&quot; &quot;Perak.&quot; &quot;Malacca.&quot; &quot;Johor.&quot; &quot;Pahang.&quot; &quot;Kelantan.&quot; &quot;Ayutthaya.&quot; &quot;Sukhothai.&quot; &quot;Chiang Rai.&quot; &quot;Nakhon Thung Yai.&quot; &quot;Oudong.&quot; &quot;Prey Nokor.&quot; &quot;Panduranga.&quot; &quot;Vijaya.&quot; &quot;Champasak.&quot; &quot;Angkor.&quot; &quot;Thanh Hoa.&quot; &quot;Sikhottabong.&quot; &quot;Khorat.&quot; &quot;Dong Kinh.&quot; &quot;Vientiane.&quot; &quot;Luang Prabang.&quot; &quot;Cao Bang.&quot; &quot;Lamuri.&quot; &quot;Deli.&quot; &quot;Batak.&quot; &quot;Siak.&quot; &quot;Bengkulu.&quot; &quot;Palembang.&quot; &quot;Tulangbewang.&quot; &quot;Banten.&quot; &quot;Kawali.&quot; &quot;Karta.&quot; &quot;Blambangan.&quot; &quot;Surabaya.&quot; &quot;Demak.&quot; &quot;Kalapa.&quot; &quot;Bali.&quot; &quot;Sumbawa.&quot; &quot;Flores.&quot; &quot;Sumba.&quot; &quot;West Timor.&quot; &quot;Brunei.&quot; &quot;Jesselton.&quot; &quot;Kutai.&quot; &quot;Banjar.&quot; &quot;Pontianak.&quot; &quot;Makassar.&quot; &quot;Kendari.&quot; &quot;Poso.&quot; &quot;Manado.&quot; &quot;Buru.&quot; &quot;Ambon.&quot; &quot;Ceram.&quot; &quot;Halmahera.&quot; &quot;Ternate.&quot; &quot;Tidore.&quot; &quot;Sulu.&quot; &quot;Maguindanao.&quot; &quot;Lanao.&quot; &quot;Samar.&quot; &quot;Palawan.&quot; &quot;Manila.&quot; &quot;Ilocos.&quot; &quot;Cagayan.&quot; &quot;Lingga.&quot; &quot;Sibsongbanna.&quot; &quot;Dali.&quot; &quot;Yunnan.&quot; &quot;Guangnan.&quot; &quot;Lingyun.&quot; &quot;Shiuhing.&quot; &quot;Kingchow.&quot; &quot;Canton.&quot; &quot;Macau.&quot; &quot;Fuzhou.&quot; &quot;Ganzhou.&quot; &quot;Changsha.&quot; &quot;Wuling.&quot; &quot;Zhenyuan.&quot; &quot;Guiyang.&quot; &quot;Umung.&quot; &quot;Shigatse.&quot; &quot;Lhasa.&quot; &quot;Tachienlu.&quot; &quot;Chengdu.&quot; &quot;Chongqing.&quot; &quot;Yichang.&quot; &quot;Wuchang.&quot; &quot;Nanchang.&quot; &quot;Hangzhou.&quot; &quot;Yangzhou.&quot; &quot;Anqing.&quot; &quot;Nanyang.&quot; &quot;Kaifeng.&quot; &quot;Hanzhong.&quot; &quot;Qingzhou.&quot; &quot;Jinan.&quot; &quot;Huaiqing.&quot; &quot;Taiyuan.&quot; &quot;Pingyang.&quot; &quot;Hejian.&quot; &quot;Baoding.&quot; &quot;Datong.&quot; &quot;Ningxia.&quot; &quot;Lanzhou.&quot; &quot;Xi\&apos;an.&quot; &quot;Ordos.&quot; &quot;Hohhot.&quot; &quot;Chengde.&quot; &quot;Ningyuan.&quot; &quot;Gyegu.&quot; &quot;Tsaidam.&quot; &quot;Yumen.&quot; &quot;Zhangye.&quot; &quot;Alxa.&quot; &quot;Hotan.&quot; &quot;Qarqan.&quot; &quot;Aksu.&quot; &quot;Bechbaliq.&quot; &quot;Hoboksar.&quot; &quot;Urumqi.&quot; &quot;Tannu Uriankhai.&quot; &quot;Kherlen.&quot; &quot;Kobdo.&quot; &quot;Uliastai.&quot; &quot;Dornogovi.&quot; &quot;Setsen.&quot; &quot;Jirem.&quot; &quot;Xilin Gol.&quot; &quot;Hulunbuir.&quot; &quot;Cicigar.&quot; &quot;Shenyang.&quot; &quot;Aigun.&quot; &quot;Tuwan.&quot; &quot;Bohori.&quot; &quot;Girin.&quot; &quot;Ilan Hala.&quot; &quot;Hamheung.&quot; &quot;Hwangju.&quot; &quot;Wonju.&quot; &quot;Hanseong.&quot; &quot;Sangju.&quot; &quot;Jeonju.&quot; &quot;Sakam.&quot; &quot;Kashgar.&quot; &quot;Chanderi.&quot; &quot;Cumana.&quot; &quot;Angostura.&quot; &quot;Essequibo.&quot; &quot;Demerara.&quot; &quot;Paramaribo.&quot; &quot;Cayenne.&quot; &quot;Amapa.&quot; &quot;Belem.&quot; &quot;Maranhao.&quot; &quot;Crato.&quot; &quot;Ceara.&quot; &quot;Oeiras.&quot; &quot;Rio Grande.&quot; &quot;Paraiba.&quot; &quot;Pernambuco.&quot; &quot;Bahia.&quot; &quot;Ilheus.&quot; &quot;Goias.&quot; &quot;Diamantina.&quot; &quot;Porto Seguro.&quot; &quot;Espirito Santo.&quot; &quot;Sao Tome.&quot; &quot;Rio de Janeiro.&quot; &quot;Santo Amaro.&quot; &quot;Minas Gerais.&quot; &quot;Sao Vicente.&quot; &quot;Ortelsburg.&quot; &quot;Guayra.&quot; &quot;Curitiba.&quot; &quot;Braslaw.&quot; &quot;Vitebsk.&quot; &quot;Uruguay.&quot; &quot;Banda Oriental.&quot; &quot;Al-Junaynah.&quot; &quot;Asuncion.&quot; &quot;Concepcion.&quot; &quot;Corrientes.&quot; &quot;Rio de la Plata.&quot; &quot;Tandil.&quot; &quot;Candelaria.&quot; &quot;Puerto Deseado.&quot; &quot;Tierra del Fuego.&quot; &quot;Kawesqar.&quot; &quot;Huillimapu.&quot; &quot;Pehuenmapu.&quot; &quot;Carmen.&quot; &quot;Picunmapu.&quot; &quot;Angoche.&quot; &quot;Mtetwa.&quot; &quot;Chaco Austral.&quot; &quot;Catamarca.&quot; &quot;Copiapo.&quot; &quot;Iquique.&quot; &quot;Jujuy.&quot; &quot;Potosi.&quot; &quot;Arica.&quot; &quot;Oruro.&quot; &quot;Mbwila.&quot; &quot;Chaco Boreal.&quot; &quot;Chiquitos.&quot; &quot;Cochabamba.&quot; &quot;Chuquiabo.&quot; &quot;Moxos.&quot; &quot;Puno.&quot; &quot;Arequipa.&quot; &quot;Nazca.&quot; &quot;Abancay.&quot; &quot;Cuzco.&quot; &quot;Lima.&quot; &quot;Huancavelica.&quot; &quot;Jauja.&quot; &quot;Chanchan.&quot; &quot;Cajamarca.&quot; &quot;Huanuco.&quot; &quot;Iquitos.&quot; &quot;Tumbes.&quot; &quot;Canari.&quot; &quot;Canelos.&quot; &quot;Guayaquil.&quot; &quot;Quito.&quot; &quot;Quijos.&quot; &quot;Caqueta.&quot; &quot;Cauca.&quot; &quot;Mariquita.&quot; &quot;Bogota.&quot; &quot;Choco.&quot; &quot;Antioqu&#x00ED;a.&quot; &quot;Cartagena.&quot; &quot;Magdalena.&quot; &quot;Maracaibo.&quot; &quot;Caracas.&quot; &quot;Tunja.&quot; &quot;Graaff-Reinet.&quot; &quot;Barinas.&quot; &quot;Panama.&quot; &quot;Chorotega.&quot; &quot;Nicaragua.&quot; &quot;Mosquito.&quot; &quot;Pipil.&quot; &quot;Honduras.&quot; &quot;Guatemala.&quot; &quot;Pet&#x00E9;n.&quot; &quot;Belize.&quot; &quot;Zapotec.&quot; &quot;Campeche.&quot; &quot;Sotuta.&quot; &quot;Mixtec.&quot; &quot;Tohancapan.&quot; &quot;Tlapanec.&quot; &quot;Tlaxcala.&quot; &quot;Zacatula.&quot; &quot;Mexico.&quot; &quot;Huastec.&quot; &quot;Sayultecas.&quot; &quot;Totorames.&quot; &quot;Zacatecas.&quot; &quot;Guachichil.&quot; &quot;Tamaulipas.&quot; &quot;Sinaloa.&quot; &quot;Tepehuan.&quot; &quot;Coahuila.&quot; &quot;Yaqui.&quot; &quot;Suma.&quot; &quot;Concho.&quot; &quot;Cochimi.&quot; &quot;Guaycura.&quot; &quot;Cahuilla.&quot; &quot;Chumash.&quot; &quot;Salinan.&quot; &quot;Yokuts.&quot; &quot;Pomo.&quot; &quot;Siuslaw.&quot; &quot;Chinook.&quot; &quot;Salish.&quot; &quot;Paiute.&quot; &quot;Yavapai.&quot; &quot;Pima.&quot; &quot;Navajo.&quot; &quot;Apache.&quot; &quot;Pueblo.&quot; &quot;Piro.&quot; &quot;Mescalero.&quot; &quot;Lipan.&quot; &quot;Karankawa.&quot; &quot;Teyas.&quot; &quot;Waco.&quot; &quot;Tonkawa.&quot; &quot;Atakapa.&quot; &quot;Arapaho.&quot; &quot;Kiowa.&quot; &quot;Naisha.&quot; &quot;Wichita.&quot; &quot;Chitimacha.&quot; &quot;Caddo.&quot; &quot;Arkansas.&quot; &quot;Yscani.&quot; &quot;Quapaw.&quot; &quot;Kansas.&quot; &quot;Pahatsi.&quot; &quot;Tamaroa.&quot; &quot;Pawnee.&quot; &quot;Missouri.&quot; &quot;Omaha.&quot; &quot;Wahpeton.&quot; &quot;Iowa.&quot; &quot;Yanktonai.&quot; &quot;Yankton.&quot; &quot;Sisseton.&quot; &quot;Mandan.&quot; &quot;Makoua.&quot; &quot;Menominee.&quot; &quot;Sauk.&quot; &quot;Mesquakie.&quot; &quot;Winnebago.&quot; &quot;Illinois.&quot; &quot;Kaskaskia.&quot; &quot;Cahokia.&quot; &quot;Tennessee.&quot; &quot;Chickasaw.&quot; &quot;Choctaw.&quot; &quot;Bayougoula.&quot; &quot;Mobile.&quot; &quot;Pensacola.&quot; &quot;Alabama.&quot; &quot;Tuskegee.&quot; &quot;Ais.&quot; &quot;Timucua.&quot; &quot;Apalachee.&quot; &quot;Guale.&quot; &quot;Muskogee.&quot; &quot;Coosa.&quot; &quot;Santee.&quot; &quot;Catawba.&quot; &quot;Yuchi.&quot; &quot;Cherokee.&quot; &quot;Cheraw.&quot; &quot;Tuscarora.&quot; &quot;Pamlico.&quot; &quot;Kaskinampo.&quot; &quot;Kentucky.&quot; &quot;Chisca.&quot; &quot;Wea.&quot; &quot;Miami.&quot; &quot;Potawatomi.&quot; &quot;Michigan.&quot; &quot;Wyandot.&quot; &quot;Erie.&quot; &quot;Ohio.&quot; &quot;Monacan.&quot; &quot;Chesapeake.&quot; &quot;Kanawha.&quot; &quot;Powhatan.&quot; &quot;Conoy.&quot; &quot;Allegheny.&quot; &quot;Susquehanna.&quot; &quot;Lenape.&quot; &quot;Delaware.&quot; &quot;Seneca.&quot; &quot;Cayuga.&quot; &quot;Onondaga.&quot; &quot;Oneida.&quot; &quot;Unami.&quot; &quot;Mahican.&quot; &quot;Mohawk.&quot; &quot;Manhattan.&quot; &quot;Nipmuc.&quot; &quot;Narraganset.&quot; &quot;Massachusetts.&quot; &quot;Pocumtuk.&quot; &quot;Merrimack.&quot; &quot;Penobscott.&quot; &quot;Nootka.&quot; &quot;Squamish.&quot; &quot;Kwakiutl.&quot; &quot;Tsimshian.&quot; &quot;Tlingit.&quot; &quot;Yakutat.&quot; &quot;Kenai.&quot; &quot;Aleut.&quot; &quot;Beothuk.&quot; &quot;Taqamkuk.&quot; &quot;Unamakik.&quot; &quot;Epekwitk.&quot; &quot;Sipeknekatik.&quot; &quot;Mikmaq.&quot; &quot;Kespek.&quot; &quot;Niagara.&quot; &quot;Huron.&quot; &quot;Ontario.&quot; &quot;Maisouna.&quot; &quot;Nipissing.&quot; &quot;Algonquin.&quot; &quot;Hochelaga.&quot; &quot;Stadacona.&quot; &quot;Tadoussac.&quot; &quot;Innu.&quot; &quot;Chisedec.&quot; &quot;Qikirmiut.&quot; &quot;Cisasipi.&quot; &quot;Cree.&quot; &quot;Soto.&quot; &quot;Abitibi.&quot; &quot;Mosoni.&quot; &quot;Attawapiskat.&quot; &quot;Muskegon.&quot; &quot;Chipewyan.&quot; &quot;Ojibwa.&quot; &quot;Winnipeg.&quot; &quot;Atikaki.&quot; &quot;Manitoba.&quot; &quot;Kinougeoulini.&quot; &quot;Satsuma.&quot; &quot;Cheongju.&quot; &quot;Bungo.&quot; &quot;Okinawa.&quot; &quot;Ha Tinh.&quot; &quot;Suo.&quot; &quot;Izumo.&quot; &quot;Harima.&quot; &quot;Kyoto.&quot; &quot;Settsu.&quot; &quot;Indrapura.&quot; &quot;Echizen.&quot; &quot;Echigo.&quot; &quot;Uzen.&quot; &quot;Rikuzen.&quot; &quot;Hitachi.&quot; &quot;Musashi.&quot; &quot;Kai.&quot; &quot;Owari.&quot; &quot;Kamikawa.&quot; &quot;The Kurils.&quot; &quot;Sakhalin.&quot; &quot;Kamchatka.&quot; &quot;Penzhina.&quot; &quot;Kolyma.&quot; &quot;Omolon.&quot; &quot;Karalveyem.&quot; &quot;Verkhoyansk.&quot; &quot;Suntar Khayata.&quot; &quot;Gizhiga.&quot; &quot;Sakha.&quot; &quot;Okhotsk.&quot; &quot;Tauisk.&quot; &quot;Yakut.&quot; &quot;Maya.&quot; &quot;Jugjur.&quot; &quot;Miyoo Gasan.&quot; &quot;Haiilanboo.&quot; &quot;Deren.&quot; &quot;Aldan.&quot; &quot;Stanovoy.&quot; &quot;Hinggan.&quot; &quot;Mukhtuya.&quot; &quot;Kirenga.&quot; &quot;Barguzin.&quot; &quot;Ude.&quot; &quot;Onan Gol.&quot; &quot;East Tunguska.&quot; &quot;Irkutsk.&quot; &quot;West Tunguska.&quot; &quot;Angara.&quot; &quot;Sayan.&quot; &quot;Tomsk.&quot; &quot;Kuznetsk.&quot; &quot;Altai Uriankhai.&quot; &quot;Turukhan.&quot; &quot;Ket.&quot; &quot;Surgut.&quot; &quot;Narim.&quot; &quot;Irtesh.&quot; &quot;Obdorsk.&quot; &quot;Berezov.&quot; &quot;Sibir.&quot; &quot;Tyumen.&quot; &quot;Kurgan.&quot; &quot;Solikamsk.&quot; &quot;Tura.&quot; &quot;Viatka.&quot; &quot;Pelym.&quot; &quot;Simbirsk.&quot; &quot;Kazan.&quot; &quot;Vetluga.&quot; &quot;Wadjuk.&quot; &quot;Paredarerme.&quot; &quot;Kaurna.&quot; &quot;Wurundjeri.&quot; &quot;Wergaia.&quot; &quot;Wiradjuri.&quot; &quot;Eora.&quot; &quot;Kamilaroi.&quot; &quot;Bundjalung.&quot; &quot;Barunggam.&quot; &quot;Turrbal.&quot; &quot;Falklands.&quot; &quot;Cape Verde.&quot; &quot;Fernando Po.&quot; &quot;St. Helena.&quot; &quot;Socotra.&quot; &quot;Mahe.&quot; &quot;Hollhavai.&quot; &quot;Mauritius.&quot; &quot;&#x00CE;le Bourbon.&quot; &quot;Eiriksfjord.&quot; &quot;Vestbygden.&quot; &quot;Whangarei.&quot; &quot;Taranaki.&quot; &quot;Tauranga.&quot; &quot;Timaru.&quot; &quot;Agadir.&quot; &quot;Arguin.&quot; &quot;Trarza.&quot; &quot;Cayor.&quot; &quot;Gabu.&quot; &quot;Brakna.&quot; &quot;Wolof.&quot; &quot;Futa Jallon.&quot; &quot;Sierra Leone.&quot; &quot;Grain Coast.&quot; &quot;Bambuk.&quot; &quot;Bure.&quot; &quot;Bagoe.&quot; &quot;Segu.&quot; &quot;Joma.&quot; &quot;Kong.&quot; &quot;Ivory Coast.&quot; &quot;Tuat.&quot; &quot;Taudeni.&quot; &quot;Azawad.&quot; &quot;Tadmekka.&quot; &quot;Massina.&quot; &quot;Timbuktu.&quot; &quot;Gao.&quot; &quot;Jenne.&quot; &quot;Yatenga.&quot; &quot;Gurma.&quot; &quot;Wagadugu.&quot; &quot;Kumasi.&quot; &quot;Gold Coast.&quot; &quot;Abomey.&quot; &quot;Whydah.&quot; &quot;Dendi.&quot; &quot;Borgu.&quot; &quot;Oyo.&quot; &quot;Nupe.&quot; &quot;Ife.&quot; &quot;Benin.&quot; &quot;Gobir.&quot; &quot;Katsina.&quot; &quot;Zamfara.&quot; &quot;Bonny.&quot; &quot;Idah.&quot; &quot;Pindinga.&quot; &quot;Zazzau.&quot; &quot;Kano.&quot; &quot;Damagaram.&quot; &quot;Borno.&quot; &quot;Kanem.&quot; &quot;Bagirmi.&quot; &quot;Mandara.&quot; &quot;Bauchi.&quot; &quot;Wukari.&quot; &quot;Calabar.&quot; &quot;Cameroon.&quot; &quot;Gabon.&quot; &quot;Loango.&quot; &quot;Luanda.&quot; &quot;Mbamba.&quot; &quot;Anziku.&quot; &quot;Mpemba.&quot; &quot;Ndongo.&quot; &quot;Benguela.&quot; &quot;Namibia.&quot; &quot;Ezorongondo.&quot; &quot;Lesser Namaqualand.&quot; &quot;Roggeveld.&quot; &quot;Cape.&quot; &quot;Great Karoo.&quot; &quot;Swellendam.&quot; &quot;Xhosa.&quot; &quot;Natal.&quot; &quot;Matsolo.&quot; &quot;Inhambane.&quot; &quot;Zimbabwe.&quot; &quot;Butua.&quot; &quot;Sofala.&quot; &quot;Sena.&quot; &quot;Massapa.&quot; &quot;Shangwe.&quot; &quot;Zumbo.&quot; &quot;Tete.&quot; &quot;Quelimane.&quot; &quot;Menabe.&quot; &quot;Besalampy.&quot; &quot;Mozambique.&quot; &quot;Kilwa.&quot; &quot;Mzizima.&quot; &quot;Lindi.&quot; &quot;Bagamoyo.&quot; &quot;Tanga.&quot; &quot;Zanzibar.&quot; &quot;Mombasa.&quot; &quot;Malindi.&quot; &quot;Lamu.&quot; &quot;Mogadishu.&quot; &quot;Qardho.&quot; &quot;Ogaden.&quot; &quot;Degehabur.&quot; &quot;Berbera.&quot; &quot;Dawaro.&quot; &quot;Harer.&quot; &quot;Zeila.&quot; &quot;Shewa.&quot; &quot;Wollo.&quot; &quot;Tajura.&quot; &quot;Tegali.&quot; &quot;Fazughli.&quot; &quot;Sidamo.&quot; &quot;Darfur.&quot; &quot;Bayuda.&quot; &quot;El Obeid.&quot; &quot;Gezira.&quot; &quot;Gojjam.&quot; &quot;Gonder.&quot; &quot;Butana.&quot; &quot;Beja.&quot; &quot;Aksum.&quot; &quot;Dongola.&quot; &quot;Berber.&quot; &quot;Massawa.&quot; &quot;Aswan.&quot; &quot;Suakin.&quot; &quot;Kharga.&quot; &quot;Qasr Ibrim.&quot; &quot;Guam.&quot; &quot;Rabaul.&quot; &quot;Hanuabada.&quot; &quot;Solomon Islands.&quot; &quot;Vanuatu.&quot; &quot;Hawaii.&quot; &quot;Kiribati.&quot; &quot;Fiji.&quot; &quot;Samoa.&quot; &quot;Tuamotu Islands.&quot; &quot;Manokwari.&quot; &quot;Waihopai.&quot; &quot;Corsica.&quot; &quot;Maldives.&quot; &quot;Yola.&quot; &quot;V&#x00E4;nern.&quot; &quot;V&#x00E4;ttern.&quot; &quot;Gulf of Bothnia.&quot; &quot;Eastern Sea of &#x00C5;land.&quot; &quot;Gulf of Finland.&quot; &quot;Western Baltic Sea.&quot; &quot;Gulf of Riga.&quot; &quot;Southern Baltic Sea.&quot; &quot;&#x00D6;resund.&quot; &quot;Kattegat.&quot; &quot;Lake Peipus.&quot; &quot;Ladoga.&quot; &quot;Onega.&quot; &quot;Barents Sea.&quot; &quot;Lofoten Sea.&quot; &quot;Northern Norwegian Sea.&quot; &quot;Southern Norwegian Sea.&quot; &quot;Skagerrak.&quot; &quot;Helgoland Bight.&quot; &quot;Coast of Holland.&quot; &quot;Dogger Bank.&quot; &quot;Straits of Dover.&quot; &quot;The Channel.&quot; &quot;Taveta.&quot; &quot;Coast of Brittany.&quot; &quot;Quiberon Bay.&quot; &quot;Cote D\&apos;Argent.&quot; &quot;Bay of Biscay.&quot; &quot;Cantabrian Sea.&quot; &quot;Tyne.&quot; &quot;Firth of Forth.&quot; &quot;Coast of Shetland.&quot; &quot;Moray Firth.&quot; &quot;North Channel.&quot; &quot;Irish Sea.&quot; &quot;St. George\&apos;s Channel.&quot; &quot;Donegal Bay.&quot; &quot;Dingle Bay.&quot; &quot;Celtic Sea.&quot; &quot;Western Approaches.&quot; &quot;Finisterre Bay.&quot; &quot;Lusitanian Sea.&quot; &quot;Gulf of Cadiz.&quot; &quot;Straits of Gibraltar.&quot; &quot;Gulf of Almeria.&quot; &quot;Gulf of Valencia.&quot; &quot;Gulf of Lion.&quot; &quot;Cote D\&apos;Azur.&quot; &quot;Ligurian Sea.&quot; &quot;Coast of the Faeroes.&quot; &quot;Western Mediterranean.&quot; &quot;Barbary Coast.&quot; &quot;Cape Bon.&quot; &quot;Tyrrenean Sea.&quot; &quot;Bay of Napoli.&quot; &quot;Gulf of Gabes.&quot; &quot;Sao Tome.&quot; &quot;Straits of Messina.&quot; &quot;Gulf of Venice.&quot; &quot;Adriatic Sea.&quot; &quot;Straits of Otranto.&quot; &quot;Gulf of Taranto.&quot; &quot;Ionian Sea.&quot; &quot;Gulf of Sirte.&quot; &quot;Gulf of Bomba.&quot; &quot;Bay of Alexandria.&quot; &quot;Palestinian Coast.&quot; &quot;Gulf of Cyprus.&quot; &quot;Spi&#x0161;.&quot; &quot;Aegean Sea.&quot; &quot;Sea of Marmara.&quot; &quot;Gulf of Varna.&quot; &quot;Gulf of Odessa.&quot; &quot;Sea of Azov.&quot; &quot;Eastern Black Sea.&quot; &quot;Lake Balaton.&quot; &quot;Caspian Sea.&quot; &quot;Aral Sea.&quot; &quot;Gulf of Suez.&quot; &quot;Red Sea.&quot; &quot;Bab el Mandeb.&quot; &quot;Gulf of Aden.&quot; &quot;Gulf of Oman.&quot; &quot;Gulf of Masirah.&quot; &quot;Straits of Hormuz.&quot; &quot;Persian Gulf.&quot; &quot;Coast of Makran.&quot; &quot;Coast of Gujarat.&quot; &quot;Konkan Coast.&quot; &quot;Malabar Coast.&quot; &quot;Comorin Cape.&quot; &quot;Coast of Coromandel.&quot; &quot;Coast of Orissa.&quot; &quot;Ganges Delta.&quot; &quot;Arakan Coast.&quot; &quot;Irrawady Delta.&quot; &quot;Eastern Bay of Bengal.&quot; &quot;Andaman Sea.&quot; &quot;Straits of Malacca.&quot; &quot;Nicobar Islands.&quot; &quot;Coast of Aceh.&quot; &quot;Coast of Sumatra.&quot; &quot;Sunda Strait.&quot; &quot;Coast of Java.&quot; &quot;Coast of Blambangan.&quot; &quot;Straits of Lombok.&quot; &quot;Sawu Sea.&quot; &quot;Flores Sea.&quot; &quot;Java Sea.&quot; &quot;Straits of Makassar.&quot; &quot;Karimata Strait.&quot; &quot;Straits of Johor.&quot; &quot;Malayan Sea.&quot; &quot;Coast of Sarawak.&quot; &quot;Cape C&#x00E0; Mau.&quot; &quot;Gulf of Siam.&quot; &quot;Cam Ranh Bay.&quot; &quot;South China Sea.&quot; &quot;Palawan Passage.&quot; &quot;Coast of Annam.&quot; &quot;Gulf of Tonkin.&quot; &quot;Guangzhou Bay.&quot; &quot;Taiwan Strait.&quot; &quot;Yang Tse Delta.&quot; &quot;Eastern Yellow Sea.&quot; &quot;Korea Bay.&quot; &quot;South Korean Sea.&quot; &quot;North Korean Sea.&quot; &quot;Olga Bay.&quot; &quot;Tatar Straits.&quot; &quot;Shantar Islands.&quot; &quot;Tauisk Bay.&quot; &quot;Bay of Komenskoie.&quot; &quot;Coast of Kamchatka.&quot; &quot;Okhotsk Sea.&quot; &quot;Coast of Sakhalin.&quot; &quot;Soya Strait.&quot; &quot;Tsugaru Strait.&quot; &quot;Yamato Basin.&quot; &quot;Amakusa Sea.&quot; &quot;Seto Inland Sea.&quot; &quot;Kii Channel.&quot; &quot;Ryukyu Islands.&quot; &quot;Luzon Strait.&quot; &quot;Paracel Islands.&quot; &quot;Manila Bay.&quot; &quot;Coast of Luzon.&quot; &quot;Visayan Sea.&quot; &quot;Sulu Sea.&quot; &quot;Sea of Celebes.&quot; &quot;Halmaheran Sea.&quot; &quot;Banda Sea.&quot; &quot;Mindanao Coast.&quot; &quot;Palau Islands.&quot; &quot;Cenderawasih Bay.&quot; &quot;Vitiaz Strait.&quot; &quot;Trobrian Islands.&quot; &quot;Torres Strait.&quot; &quot;Timor Sea.&quot; &quot;Arafura Sea.&quot; &quot;Gulf of Carpentaria.&quot; &quot;Great Barrier Reef.&quot; &quot;Coral Sea.&quot; &quot;Flinders Bay.&quot; &quot;Bass Strait.&quot; &quot;Kangaroo Island.&quot; &quot;Great Australian Bight.&quot; &quot;Cape Leeuwin.&quot; &quot;Houtman Abrolhos.&quot; &quot;Northwest Cape.&quot; &quot;Roebuck Bay.&quot; &quot;Western Tasman Sea.&quot; &quot;Macquarie Harbour.&quot; &quot;Cook Strait.&quot; &quot;Lord Howe Island.&quot; &quot;Northern Tasman Sea.&quot; &quot;Coast of New Zealand.&quot; &quot;Southern Tasman Sea.&quot; &quot;Canterbury Bight.&quot; &quot;New Caledonian Sea.&quot; &quot;Vanuatu Islands.&quot; &quot;Fiji Basin.&quot; &quot;Solomon Sea.&quot; &quot;Tuvalu Islands.&quot; &quot;Melanesia Sea.&quot; &quot;Mariana Islands.&quot; &quot;Philippine Sea.&quot; &quot;Northern Philippine Sea.&quot; &quot;Volcano Islands.&quot; &quot;Izu Islands.&quot; &quot;Sanriku Coast.&quot; &quot;Kuril Islands.&quot; &quot;Kamchatka Trench.&quot; &quot;Ulakhan Fault.&quot; &quot;Bay of Anadyr.&quot; &quot;Bering Sea.&quot; &quot;Horn of Africa.&quot; &quot;Coast of Pepper.&quot; &quot;Zanzibar Strait.&quot; &quot;Mozambique Channel.&quot; &quot;Diego Suarez Bay.&quot; &quot;Southwestern Arabian Sea.&quot; &quot;Northern Arabian Sea.&quot; &quot;The Seychelles.&quot; &quot;Coast of Tamatave.&quot; &quot;The Mascareignes.&quot; &quot;Coast of Menabe.&quot; &quot;Coast of Sofala.&quot; &quot;Coast of Natal.&quot; &quot;Coast of Ciskei.&quot; &quot;Cape of Good Hope.&quot; &quot;Coast of Namibia.&quot; &quot;Coast of Angola.&quot; &quot;Gulf of Kongo.&quot; &quot;Coast of Cameroon.&quot; &quot;Gulf of Guinea.&quot; &quot;Ivory Coast.&quot; &quot;Grain Coast.&quot; &quot;Coast of Gambia.&quot; &quot;Bay of Arguin.&quot; &quot;Mauretanian Coast.&quot; &quot;Cape Bojador.&quot; &quot;Coast of Morocco.&quot; &quot;Jan Mayen Sea.&quot; &quot;Spitzberg Sea.&quot; &quot;Icelandic Sea.&quot; &quot;Eastern Coast of Iceland.&quot; &quot;Western Coast of Iceland.&quot; &quot;Northeastern Atlantic.&quot; &quot;Rockall.&quot; &quot;Denmark Strait.&quot; &quot;Eastern Coast of Greenland.&quot; &quot;Western Coast of Greenland.&quot; &quot;Labrador Strait.&quot; &quot;Baffin Bay.&quot; &quot;Hudson Straits.&quot; &quot;James Bay.&quot; &quot;Western Hudson Bay.&quot; &quot;Eastern Hudson Bay.&quot; &quot;Foxe Basin.&quot; &quot;Gulf of St. Lawrence.&quot; &quot;Cabot Strait.&quot; &quot;Bay of Fundy.&quot; &quot;Strait of Belle Isle.&quot; &quot;Fortune Bay.&quot; &quot;Notre Dame Bay.&quot; &quot;Labrador Sea.&quot; &quot;Greenland Sea.&quot; &quot;Northern Atlantic.&quot; &quot;Massachusetts Bay.&quot; &quot;Delaware Bay.&quot; &quot;Cape Hatteras.&quot; &quot;Sea Islands.&quot; &quot;Bahama Banks.&quot; &quot;Western Sargasso Sea.&quot; &quot;Florida Straits.&quot; &quot;Apalachee Bay.&quot; &quot;Mobile Bay.&quot; &quot;Galveston Bay.&quot; &quot;Tampico Bay.&quot; &quot;Bay of Campeche.&quot; &quot;Gulf of Mexico.&quot; &quot;Yucatan Channel.&quot; &quot;Gulf of Honduras.&quot; &quot;Mosquito Coast.&quot; &quot;Gulf of Darien.&quot; &quot;Jamaica Channel.&quot; &quot;Central Caribbean.&quot; &quot;Northwestern Caribbean.&quot; &quot;Venezuelan Gulf.&quot; &quot;Venezuelan Sea.&quot; &quot;Eastern Caribbean.&quot; &quot;Windward Islands.&quot; &quot;Lesser Antilles.&quot; &quot;Turks &amp; Caicos Sea.&quot; &quot;Bahama Channel.&quot; &quot;Mona Passage.&quot; &quot;Guyana Coast.&quot; &quot;Cape Orange.&quot; &quot;Amazonas Gulf.&quot; &quot;Coast of Brazil.&quot; &quot;Coast of Pernambuco.&quot; &quot;Coast of Porto Seguro.&quot; &quot;Costa Verde.&quot; &quot;Coast of Santa Catarina.&quot; &quot;Patos Lagoon.&quot; &quot;La Plata River.&quot; &quot;Northern Coast of Patagonia.&quot; &quot;Southern Coast of Patagonia.&quot; &quot;Magellan Strait.&quot; &quot;Gulf of Penas.&quot; &quot;Coast of Chile.&quot; &quot;Atacama Coast.&quot; &quot;Coast of Antofagasta.&quot; &quot;Arica Bend.&quot; &quot;Coast of Peru.&quot; &quot;Gulf of Guayaquil.&quot; &quot;Coast of Ecuador.&quot; &quot;Gulf of Panama.&quot; &quot;Costa Rica.&quot; &quot;Gulf of Tehuantepec.&quot; &quot;Manzanillo Bay.&quot; &quot;Mazatlan Bay.&quot; &quot;Gulf of California.&quot; &quot;Cape San Lucas.&quot; &quot;Gulf of Catalina.&quot; &quot;San Francisco Bay.&quot; &quot;Cape Blanco.&quot; &quot;Salish Sea.&quot; &quot;Hecate Strait.&quot; &quot;Glacier Bay.&quot; &quot;Cook Inlet.&quot; &quot;Norton Sound.&quot; &quot;Hatton Bank.&quot; &quot;Eastern Gibbs Fracture.&quot; &quot;Western Gibbs Fracture.&quot; &quot;Iberian Shelf.&quot; &quot;Sea of Azores.&quot; &quot;Corner Seamounts.&quot; &quot;Sable Island Bank.&quot; &quot;New England Seamounts.&quot; &quot;Blake Plateau.&quot; &quot;West Bermuda Sea.&quot; &quot;East Bermuda Sea.&quot; &quot;Antilles Current.&quot; &quot;Northern Guiana Basin.&quot; &quot;Guiana Basin.&quot; &quot;Southern Guiana Basin.&quot; &quot;Canary Approach.&quot; &quot;Cape Verde Approach.&quot; &quot;Central North Atlantic.&quot; &quot;North Equatorial Current.&quot; &quot;Northeast Sargasso Sea.&quot; &quot;Southeast Sargasso Sea.&quot; &quot;Romanche Gap.&quot; &quot;East Guinea Basin.&quot; &quot;West Guinea Basin.&quot; &quot;Coast of Falklands.&quot; &quot;Scotia Basin.&quot; &quot;Brazil-Malvinas Confluence Zone.&quot; &quot;South Brazil Current.&quot; &quot;Brazil Current.&quot; &quot;Rio Grande Rise.&quot; &quot;Argentine Basin.&quot; &quot;South Orkney Islands.&quot; &quot;East of Magellans.&quot; &quot;North Brazil Current.&quot; &quot;South Equatorial Current.&quot; &quot;Central South Atlantic.&quot; &quot;Brazil Basin.&quot; &quot;Saint Helena Island.&quot; &quot;Benguela Current.&quot; &quot;Walvis Ridge.&quot; &quot;Bouvet Island.&quot; &quot;Tristan da Cunha Islands.&quot; &quot;Southern Mid-Atlantic Ridget.&quot; &quot;South Atlantic Current.&quot; &quot;South Sandwich Islands.&quot; &quot;South Atlantic.&quot; &quot;South Atlantic Roaring Forties.&quot; &quot;Denmark Sea.&quot; &quot;Northern Bay of Bengal.&quot; &quot;Western Bay of Bengal.&quot; &quot;Southern Bay of Bengal.&quot; &quot;Ceylon Sea.&quot; &quot;Southeastern Arabian Sea.&quot; &quot;North Indian Ocean.&quot; &quot;Mascarene Plateau.&quot; &quot;Western Equatorial Counter Current.&quot; &quot;Coast of Maldives.&quot; &quot;Central Indian Ocean.&quot; &quot;Chagos Archipelago.&quot; &quot;Eastern Equatorial Counter Current.&quot; &quot;Ninetyeast Ridge.&quot; &quot;Northeast Indian Ocean.&quot; &quot;Marion Island.&quot; &quot;Natal Basin.&quot; &quot;Taolagnaro Bay.&quot; &quot;Crozet Islands.&quot; &quot;Crozet Basin.&quot; &quot;Madagascar Basin.&quot; &quot;Kerguelen Islands.&quot; &quot;Heard and McDonald Islands.&quot; &quot;South Indian Ocean.&quot; &quot;Indian Ocean Raging Fifties.&quot; &quot;South Australian Basin.&quot; &quot;Southwestern Indian Ridge.&quot; &quot;St Paul and Amsterdam Islands.&quot; &quot;Southeastern Indian Ridge.&quot; &quot;Naturaliste Plateau.&quot; &quot;Broken Ridge.&quot; &quot;East Indian Ocean.&quot; &quot;Zenith Plateau.&quot; &quot;Wallaby Plateau.&quot; &quot;West Australian Basin.&quot; &quot;Eastern Indian Ocean South Equatorial Current.&quot; &quot;Indian Ocean South Equatorial Current.&quot; &quot;Western Indian Ocean South Equatorial Current.&quot; &quot;Lake Tchad.&quot; &quot;Lake Victoria.&quot; &quot;Lake Tanganyika.&quot; &quot;Lake Malawi.&quot; &quot;White Sea.&quot; &quot;Lake Balchasj.&quot; &quot;Lake Bajkal.&quot; &quot;Poyang Lake.&quot; &quot;Lake Titicaca.&quot; &quot;Lake Nicaragua.&quot; &quot;Lake Okeechobee.&quot; &quot;Lake Ontario.&quot; &quot;Lake Erie.&quot; &quot;Lake Huron.&quot; &quot;Lake Michigan.&quot; &quot;Lake Superior.&quot; &quot;Lake Nipigon.&quot; &quot;Lake Winnipeg.&quot; &quot;Commander Basin.&quot; &quot;Emperor Ridge.&quot; &quot;Northwestern Pacific.&quot; &quot;Oyashio Current.&quot; &quot;Northern Kuroshio Current.&quot; &quot;Kuroshio Current.&quot; &quot;Western Pacific.&quot; &quot;Micronesia Sea.&quot; &quot;Mariana Trench.&quot; &quot;North Pacific Equatorial Current.&quot; &quot;Melanesian Basin.&quot; &quot;Kuskokwim Bay.&quot; &quot;Bering Strait.&quot; &quot;Shirshov Ridge.&quot; &quot;Aleutian Islands.&quot; &quot;Shumagin Islands.&quot; &quot;Gulf of Alaska.&quot; &quot;Western Aleutian Trench.&quot; &quot;Northern California Current.&quot; &quot;Eastern Aleutian Trench.&quot; &quot;Eastern North Pacific Drift.&quot; &quot;California Current.&quot; &quot;Murray Fracture Zone.&quot; &quot;North Pacific Drift.&quot; &quot;Western North Pacific Drift.&quot;</Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Keywords7">&quot;Western North Pacific Drift.&quot; &quot;Wake Island.&quot; &quot;Midway Island.&quot; &quot;Molokai Fracture Zone.&quot; &quot;Southern California Current.&quot; &quot;Revilla Gigedo Islands.&quot; &quot;Clarion Fracture Zone.&quot; &quot;Coast of Hawaii.&quot; &quot;Marshall Islands.&quot; &quot;Central Pacific Basin.&quot; &quot;Cocos Ridge.&quot; &quot;Guatemala Basin.&quot; &quot;Galapagos Islands.&quot; &quot;Nazca Ridge.&quot; &quot;Juan Fernandez Islands.&quot; &quot;Chile Rise.&quot; &quot;West of Magellans.&quot; &quot;Clipperton Island.&quot; &quot;Galapagos Rise.&quot; &quot;Peru Current.&quot; &quot;Humboldt Current.&quot; &quot;East Pacific Rise.&quot; &quot;South Equatorial Pacific Current.&quot; &quot;Easter Island.&quot; &quot;North Pacific Converge Zone.&quot; &quot;Eastern Equatorial Pacific Current.&quot; &quot;Clipperton Fracture Zone.&quot; &quot;Southern Humboldt Current.&quot; &quot;Mornington Abyssal Plain.&quot; &quot;South Pacific Raging Fifties.&quot; &quot;Tharp Fault.&quot; &quot;South Pacific Roaring Forties.&quot; &quot;Louisville Seamount Chain.&quot; &quot;Chatham Islands.&quot; &quot;Southeast Pacific.&quot; &quot;Tuamotu Islands.&quot; &quot;Samoa Islands.&quot; &quot;Bass Islands.&quot; &quot;Society Islands.&quot; &quot;South Pacific.&quot; &quot;East Pacific Ridge.&quot; &quot;Eltanin Fracture Zone.&quot; &quot;Kiribati Islands.&quot; &quot;Phoenix Islands.&quot; &quot;Gilbert Islands.&quot; &quot;Line Islands.&quot; &quot;Western Equatorial Pacific Counter Current.&quot; &quot;Marquesas Islands.&quot; &quot;Flint Island.&quot; &quot;Pitcairn Islands.&quot; &quot;Equatorial Pacific Counter Current.&quot; &quot;Tiki Basin.&quot; &quot;Upper Guelders.&quot; &quot;Cambray.&quot; &quot;Antwerpen.&quot; &quot;Cantabria.&quot; &quot;Burgos.&quot; &quot;Extremadura.&quot; &quot;Ja&#x00E9;n.&quot; &quot;Cadiz.&quot; &quot;Alicante.&quot; &quot;Ceuta.&quot; &quot;Rzhev.&quot; &quot;Kostroma.&quot; &quot;Murom.&quot; &quot;Ustyug.&quot; &quot;Bessarabia.&quot; &quot;Oberpfalz.&quot; &quot;Hanover.&quot; &quot;Potsdam.&quot; &quot;Koblenz.&quot; &quot;Pfalz.&quot; &quot;Kassel.&quot; &quot;Niederlausitz.&quot; &quot;Burgas.&quot; &quot;Sofia.&quot; &quot;Kosovo.&quot; &quot;Slavonia.&quot; &quot;Lienz.&quot; &quot;G&#x00F6;rz.&quot; &quot;Ostmarch.&quot; &quot;Erz.&quot; &quot;Pozsony.&quot; &quot;Achaea.&quot; &quot;Treviso.&quot; &quot;Holstein.&quot; &quot;White Karelia.&quot; &quot;Kola.&quot; &quot;Kasimov.&quot; &quot;Rub\&apos; al Khali.&quot; &quot;Komi.&quot; &quot;Western Siberia.&quot; &quot;Central Siberia.&quot; &quot;Eastern Siberia.&quot; &quot;Tian Shan.&quot; &quot;Pamir.&quot; &quot;Takla Makan.&quot; &quot;Himalaya.&quot; &quot;Arunachal.&quot; &quot;Papua.&quot; &quot;Western Australia.&quot; &quot;Central Australia.&quot; &quot;Merina.&quot; &quot;El Djouf.&quot; &quot;Central Sahara.&quot; &quot;East Sahara.&quot; &quot;Central Africa.&quot; &quot;Northern Congo Basin.&quot; &quot;Imatong.&quot; &quot;Urgoma.&quot; &quot;Limpopo.&quot; &quot;Kalahari.&quot; &quot;Western Amazonas.&quot; &quot;Eastern Amazonas.&quot; &quot;Greenland.&quot; &quot;Ungava.&quot; &quot;Weagamow.&quot; &quot;Baffin.&quot; &quot;Great Basin.&quot; &quot;S&#x00F3;\&apos;taeo\&apos;o.&quot; &quot;Alaska.&quot; &quot;Nunavut.&quot; &quot;Northwest Territories.&quot; &quot;Saskatchewan.&quot; &quot;Columbia.&quot; &quot;Pathein.&quot; &quot;Beijing.&quot; &quot;Nan.&quot; &quot;Chikuzen.&quot; &quot;Tosa.&quot; &quot;Awa.&quot; &quot;Nanjing.&quot; &quot;Suzhou.&quot; &quot;Stung Treng.&quot; &quot;Wenzhou.&quot; &quot;Aki.&quot; &quot;Lika.&quot; &quot;Raska.&quot; &quot;Donji Kraji.&quot; &quot;Quanzhou.&quot; &quot;Tajima.&quot; &quot;Travunia.&quot; &quot;Ji\&apos;an.&quot; &quot;Yamato.&quot; &quot;Dorpat.&quot; &quot;Mino.&quot; &quot;Luoyang.&quot; &quot;Etchu.&quot; &quot;Hefei.&quot; &quot;Suruga.&quot; &quot;Guilin.&quot; &quot;Marienburg.&quot; &quot;Narva.&quot; &quot;Kozuke.&quot; &quot;Xiankhouang.&quot; &quot;Pyeongyang.&quot; &quot;Amasya.&quot; &quot;Shiribeshi.&quot; &quot;Hamid.&quot; &quot;Hama.&quot; &quot;Yaran.&quot; &quot;Coimbra.&quot; &quot;Tokachi.&quot; &quot;Kastoria.&quot; &quot;Jaffa.&quot; &quot;Sidon.&quot; &quot;Abkhazia.&quot; &quot;Lauenburg.&quot; &quot;Stettin.&quot; &quot;Chelmno.&quot; &quot;Norfolk.&quot; &quot;Derby.&quot; &quot;Cremona.&quot; &quot;Graz.&quot; &quot;Somogy.&quot; &quot;Ghent.&quot; &quot;Namur.&quot; &quot;Vaud.&quot; &quot;Augsburg.&quot; &quot;Z&#x00FC;rich.&quot; &quot;St Gallen.&quot; &quot;Wallis.&quot; &quot;Ulm.&quot; &quot;Graub&#x00FC;nden.&quot; &quot;Bremen.&quot; &quot;Cuneo.&quot; &quot;Frankfurt.&quot; &quot;Charolais.&quot; &quot;Aachen.&quot; &quot;Alen&#x00E7;on.&quot; &quot;Sundgau.&quot; &quot;St. Martin.&quot; &quot;Annaba.&quot; &quot;Western Finnish Lakes.&quot; &quot;East Finnish Lakes.&quot; &quot;Central Finnish Lakes.&quot; &quot;Storavan.&quot; &quot;Storsj&#x00F6;n.&quot; &quot;Kara Sea.&quot; &quot;Lake Geneva.&quot; &quot;Lake Constance.&quot; &quot;Lake Tuz.&quot; &quot;Lake Van.&quot; &quot;Lake Urmia.&quot; &quot;Sevan Lake.&quot; &quot;Lake Taihu.&quot; &quot;Lake Hongze.&quot; &quot;Dongting.&quot; &quot;Tonl&#x00E9; Sap Lake.&quot; &quot;Tana Lake.&quot; &quot;Lake Turkana.&quot; &quot;Mpangu.&quot; &quot;Lake Poopo.&quot; &quot;Lake Champlain.&quot; &quot;Lake Saint-Jean.&quot; &quot;Lake Manicouagan.&quot; &quot;Lake Michikamau.&quot; &quot;Lake Bienville.&quot; &quot;Clearwater Lakes.&quot; &quot;Lake Minto.&quot; &quot;La Grande River.&quot; &quot;Lake Island.&quot; &quot;Lake Reindeer.&quot; &quot;Wollaston Lake.&quot; &quot;Great Slave Lake.&quot; &quot;Lake Athabasca.&quot; &quot;Dubawni Lake.&quot; &quot;Yathkyed Lake.&quot; &quot;Kasba Lake.&quot; &quot;Nueltin Lake.&quot; &quot;Wholdaia Lake.&quot; &quot;Peter Pond Lake.&quot; &quot;Great Salt Lake.&quot; &quot;Williston Lake.&quot; &quot;Greenland Tip.&quot; &quot;Tana.&quot; &quot;Northern Baltic Sea.&quot; &quot;Eastern Baltic Sea.&quot; &quot;Western Sea of &#x00C5;land.&quot; &quot;Western Norwegian Sea.&quot; &quot;&#x00C5;land.&quot; &quot;East Frisia.&quot; &quot;Gulf of Satalia.&quot; &quot;Bari.&quot; &quot;Lucania.&quot; &quot;Mitau.&quot; &quot;Kovno.&quot; &quot;Grodno.&quot; &quot;Wizna.&quot; &quot;Leczyca.&quot; &quot;Belz.&quot; &quot;Turov.&quot; &quot;Zhytomyr.&quot; &quot;Bratslav.&quot; &quot;Cherkasy.&quot; &quot;Severia.&quot; &quot;Desh.&quot; &quot;Gingee.&quot; &quot;Bidar.&quot; &quot;Rayalaseema.&quot; &quot;Meghalaya.&quot; &quot;Hunyad.&quot; &quot;Maramaros.&quot; &quot;Szabolcs.&quot; &quot;Toront&#x00E1;l.&quot; &quot;Kholmogory.&quot; &quot;Suzdal.&quot; &quot;Galich.&quot; &quot;Kargopol.&quot; &quot;Torzhok.&quot; &quot;Ostrov.&quot; &quot;Ladoga.&quot; &quot;Kudymkar.&quot; &quot;Cherdyn.&quot; &quot;Ust-Sysolsk.&quot; &quot;Buzuluk.&quot; &quot;Chelyaba.&quot; &quot;Khujand.&quot; &quot;Kulob.&quot; &quot;Sozak.&quot; &quot;Syghnak.&quot; &quot;Beljamen.&quot; &quot;Udmurtia.&quot; &quot;Urgench.&quot; &quot;Yedishkul.&quot; &quot;North Sea.&quot; &quot;Dead Sea.&quot; &quot;M&#x00E4;laren.&quot; &quot;Shetland.&quot; &quot;F&#x00E4;r&#x00F6;arna.&quot; &quot;Hokuriku Coast.&quot; &quot;Bornholm.&quot; &quot;Blekinge.&quot; &quot;Lolland.&quot; &quot;Nordjylland.&quot; &quot;N&#x00E4;rke.&quot; &quot;New Caledonia.&quot; &quot;Society Islands.&quot; &quot;Rapanui.&quot; &quot;Tonga.&quot; &quot;Tuvalu.&quot; &quot;Gilbert Islands.&quot; &quot;Nauru.&quot; &quot;Marshall Islands.&quot; &quot;Wake.&quot; &quot;Micronesia.&quot; &quot;Palau.&quot; &quot;Midway.&quot; &quot;Christmas Island.&quot; &quot;Cocos Island.&quot; &quot;Qinghai Lake.&quot; &quot;Siling Lake.&quot; &quot;Gal&#x00E1;pagos Islands.&quot; &quot;Ktunaxa.&quot; &quot;Niitsitapi.&quot; &quot;Asinaan.&quot; &quot;Aps&#x00E1;alooke.&quot; &quot;Arikara.&quot; &quot;Lakota.&quot; &quot;Oglala.&quot; &quot;Connecticut.&quot; &quot;Shenandoah.&quot; &quot;Arsigantegok.&quot; &quot;Androscoggin.&quot; &quot;Natchitoches.&quot; &quot;Nipigon.&quot; &quot;Bungi.&quot; &quot;Nehiyawewin.&quot; &quot;Tsuu Tina.&quot; &quot;Nimiipu.&quot; &quot;Bannock.&quot; &quot;Miwok.&quot; &quot;Haida.&quot; &quot;Munsee.&quot; &quot;Garoowe.&quot; &quot;Tanjore.&quot; &quot;Arcot.&quot; &quot;Mahur.&quot; &quot;South Kanara.&quot; &quot;Goa.&quot; &quot;Morasanadu.&quot; &quot;Malenadu.&quot; &quot;Savanur.&quot; &quot;Pune.&quot; &quot;Gulbarga.&quot; &quot;Baglana.&quot; &quot;Warangal.&quot; &quot;Midnapore.&quot; &quot;Sunderbans.&quot; &quot;Sadiya.&quot; &quot;Manipur.&quot; &quot;Koch Hajo.&quot; &quot;Balasore.&quot; &quot;Bhagalpur.&quot; &quot;Barind.&quot; &quot;Nasirabad.&quot; &quot;Tirhut.&quot; &quot;Garjat.&quot; &quot;Khurda.&quot; &quot;Chanda.&quot; &quot;Bhavnagar.&quot; &quot;Navanagar.&quot; &quot;Patan.&quot; &quot;Ahmadabad.&quot; &quot;Gorakhpur.&quot; &quot;Rewakantha.&quot; &quot;Bhilsa.&quot; &quot;Mewar.&quot; &quot;Kalpi.&quot; &quot;Upper Doab.&quot; &quot;Katehar.&quot; &quot;Panipat.&quot; &quot;Etawah.&quot; &quot;Shekhawati.&quot; &quot;Bhattiana.&quot; &quot;Nagaur.&quot; &quot;Gorwar.&quot; &quot;Siwi.&quot; &quot;Kumaon.&quot; &quot;Chaubisi Rajya.&quot; &quot;Limbuwan.&quot; &quot;Bhakkar.&quot; &quot;Baltistan.&quot; &quot;Ladakh.&quot; &quot;Doaba.&quot; &quot;Sialkot.&quot; &quot;Margalla.&quot; &quot;Sind Sagar.&quot; &quot;Derajat.&quot; &quot;Srikakulam.&quot; &quot;Lakhnor.&quot; &quot;Raipur.&quot; &quot;Kosta.&quot; &quot;Konaseema.&quot; &quot;Tiruchirappalli.&quot; &quot;Cholistan.&quot; &quot;Ajmer.&quot; &quot;Umarkot.&quot; &quot;Chaul.&quot; &quot;Kurnool.&quot; &quot;Tripura.&quot; &quot;Mahadeo.&quot; &quot;Mandsaur.&quot; &quot;Bahreich.&quot; &quot;Varanasi.&quot; &quot;Damin.&quot; &quot;Baghelkhand.&quot; &quot;Surguja.&quot; &quot;Kandy.&quot; &quot;Vanni.&quot; &quot;Tirunelveli.&quot; &quot;Urkan.&quot; &quot;Udi.&quot; &quot;Birija.&quot; &quot;Kuru.&quot; &quot;Furdan.&quot; &quot;Ningguta.&quot; &quot;Huncun.&quot; &quot;Boduna.&quot; &quot;Yehe.&quot; &quot;Hetu Ala.&quot; &quot;Andong.&quot; &quot;Gaizhou.&quot; &quot;Ereen.&quot; &quot;Chahar.&quot; &quot;Ih Huree.&quot; &quot;Zasagt.&quot; &quot;Urzhar.&quot; &quot;Chuguchak.&quot; &quot;Ili.&quot; &quot;Kuqa.&quot; &quot;Hami.&quot; &quot;Qakilik.&quot; &quot;Yarkand.&quot; &quot;Kochkor.&quot; &quot;Chuy.&quot; &quot;Yashilkul.&quot; &quot;Ngari.&quot; &quot;Changtang.&quot; &quot;Nyingchi.&quot; &quot;Qamdo.&quot; &quot;Markam.&quot; &quot;Dege.&quot; &quot;Rebgong.&quot; &quot;Garze.&quot; &quot;Xuanhua.&quot; &quot;Daming.&quot; &quot;Wuding.&quot; &quot;Laizhou.&quot; &quot;Yanzhou.&quot; &quot;Xuzhou.&quot; &quot;Huai\&apos;an.&quot; &quot;Fengyang.&quot; &quot;Fuyang.&quot; &quot;Zhenjiang.&quot; &quot;Ningguo.&quot; &quot;Huizhou.&quot; &quot;Shaoxin.&quot; &quot;Ningbo.&quot; &quot;Jinhua.&quot; &quot;Poyang.&quot; &quot;Jianning.&quot; &quot;Tingzhou.&quot; &quot;Kelang.&quot; &quot;Middag.&quot; &quot;Chaochow.&quot; &quot;Waichow.&quot; &quot;Shiukwan.&quot; &quot;Leichow.&quot; &quot;Ngaichow.&quot; &quot;Limchow.&quot; &quot;Ngchow.&quot; &quot;Liuzhou.&quot; &quot;Namning.&quot; &quot;Pu\&apos;er.&quot; &quot;Dehong.&quot; &quot;Lijiang.&quot; &quot;Bozhou.&quot; &quot;Langzhong.&quot; &quot;Songqu.&quot; &quot;Xiangyang.&quot; &quot;Jingzhou.&quot; &quot;Yuanling.&quot; &quot;Hengyang.&quot; &quot;Runing.&quot; &quot;Shangqiu.&quot; &quot;Ningwu.&quot; &quot;Lu\&apos;an.&quot; &quot;Yan\&apos;an.&quot; &quot;Tianshui.&quot; &quot;Pingliang.&quot; &quot;Liangzhou.&quot; &quot;Taozhou.&quot; &quot;Xining.&quot; &quot;Mergen.&quot; &quot;Iman.&quot; &quot;Sartu.&quot; &quot;Alchuka.&quot; &quot;Tsetserleg.&quot; &quot;Qaraqorum.&quot; &quot;Ejin.&quot; &quot;Korla.&quot; &quot;Govi.&quot; &quot;Kunlun.&quot; &quot;Adyghe.&quot; &quot;Guria.&quot; &quot;Kabardia.&quot; &quot;Khundzia.&quot; &quot;Tarki.&quot; &quot;Suleiman Range.&quot; &quot;Alania.&quot; &quot;Melikates.&quot; &quot;Kakheti.&quot; &quot;Kars.&quot; &quot;Nakhchivan.&quot; &quot;Urmia.&quot; &quot;Maragheh.&quot; &quot;Terek.&quot; &quot;Ilam.&quot; &quot;Kirmanshah.&quot; &quot;Ardalan.&quot; &quot;Zanjan.&quot; &quot;Qom.&quot; &quot;Golestan.&quot; &quot;Qazvin.&quot; &quot;Semnan.&quot; &quot;Yasuj.&quot; &quot;Shiraz.&quot; &quot;Bandar Langeh.&quot; &quot;Bam.&quot; &quot;Mashhad.&quot; &quot;Ardakan.&quot; &quot;Larestan.&quot; &quot;Ferah.&quot; &quot;Bamyan.&quot; &quot;Jalalabad.&quot; &quot;Kunduz.&quot; &quot;Maymana.&quot; &quot;Bust.&quot; &quot;Chakhansur.&quot; &quot;Bela.&quot; &quot;Kharan.&quot; &quot;Chabahar.&quot; &quot;Rafsanjan.&quot; &quot;Sabzevar.&quot; &quot;Bojnord.&quot; &quot;Tekrur.&quot; &quot;Kantor.&quot; &quot;Siine.&quot; &quot;Galam.&quot; &quot;Beafada.&quot; &quot;Karou.&quot; &quot;Termes.&quot; &quot;Tagant.&quot; &quot;Wagadu.&quot; &quot;Baghena.&quot; &quot;Hodh.&quot; &quot;Do.&quot; &quot;Sibiridugu.&quot; &quot;Bendugu.&quot; &quot;Guinea.&quot; &quot;Lobi.&quot; &quot;Gwiriko.&quot; &quot;Bonoman.&quot; &quot;Gyaaman.&quot; &quot;Dagbon.&quot; &quot;Denkyira.&quot; &quot;Cape Coast.&quot; &quot;Sah.&quot; &quot;Mema.&quot; &quot;Kala.&quot; &quot;Karabara.&quot; &quot;Haayre.&quot; &quot;Hombori.&quot; &quot;Liptako.&quot; &quot;Bilanga.&quot; &quot;Tenkodogo.&quot; &quot;Aribanda.&quot; &quot;Zarmaganda.&quot; &quot;Dallol.&quot; &quot;Azawagh.&quot; &quot;Azbin.&quot; &quot;Ader.&quot; &quot;Air.&quot; &quot;Tenere.&quot; &quot;Itesan.&quot; &quot;Kawar.&quot; &quot;Kebbi.&quot; &quot;Daura.&quot; &quot;Biram.&quot; &quot;Rano.&quot; &quot;Muniyo.&quot; &quot;Bedde.&quot; &quot;Manga.&quot; &quot;Marghi.&quot; &quot;Logone.&quot; &quot;Kotoko.&quot; &quot;Yao.&quot; &quot;Ondo.&quot; &quot;Ijebu.&quot; &quot;Ketu.&quot; &quot;Moshi.&quot; &quot;Yawuri.&quot; &quot;Warri.&quot; &quot;Atakora.&quot; &quot;Karasi.&quot; &quot;Saruhan.&quot; &quot;Tekke.&quot; &quot;Bolu.&quot; &quot;Bozok.&quot; &quot;Kayseri.&quot; &quot;I&#x00E7;el.&quot; &quot;Malatya.&quot; &quot;Canik.&quot; &quot;Erzincan.&quot; &quot;Mush.&quot; &quot;Van.&quot; &quot;Urfa.&quot; &quot;Sinjar.&quot; &quot;Tikrit.&quot; &quot;Samawat.&quot; &quot;Wasit.&quot; &quot;Antioch.&quot; &quot;Rahba.&quot; &quot;Suez.&quot; &quot;Al Gharbia.&quot; &quot;Minya.&quot; &quot;Bahiriya.&quot; &quot;Manfalut.&quot; &quot;Ras Gharib.&quot; &quot;Queseer.&quot; &quot;Wadi Halfa.&quot; &quot;Sahra an N&#x00FC;byah.&quot; &quot;Halaib.&quot; &quot;Tarrana.&quot; &quot;Bardiyah.&quot; &quot;Maan.&quot; &quot;Al Ula.&quot; &quot;Yanbu.&quot; &quot;Ma\&apos;din Sulaym.&quot; &quot;Jeddah.&quot; &quot;Turubah.&quot; &quot;Zufra.&quot; &quot;Badiyat ash Sham.&quot; &quot;Dawasir.&quot; &quot;Aflaj.&quot; &quot;Buraydah.&quot; &quot;Hafar.&quot; &quot;Yabrin.&quot; &quot;Grane.&quot; &quot;Masirah.&quot; &quot;Wusta.&quot; &quot;Kathiri.&quot; &quot;Marib.&quot; &quot;Beihan.&quot; &quot;Jazan.&quot; &quot;Hofuf.&quot; &quot;Chios.&quot; &quot;Kizil-Su.&quot; &quot;Konjikala.&quot; &quot;Shekty.&quot; &quot;Alty-Kuduk.&quot; &quot;Tortkara.&quot; &quot;Shegendyk.&quot; &quot;Narym.&quot; &quot;Shymkent.&quot; &quot;Aksary.&quot; &quot;Altyn.&quot; &quot;Baganaly.&quot; &quot;Tobykty.&quot; &quot;Dzhaman-Kuduk.&quot; &quot;Gurganj.&quot; &quot;Atakent.&quot; &quot;Talas.&quot; &quot;Orda.&quot; &quot;Utva.&quot; &quot;Lower Yik.&quot; &quot;Karamegdan.&quot; &quot;Lower Ishim.&quot; &quot;Kungirot.&quot; &quot;Song La.&quot; &quot;Hai Phong.&quot; &quot;Hue.&quot; &quot;Kauthara.&quot; &quot;Tay Nguyen.&quot; &quot;Prek Russey.&quot; &quot;Teuk Khmao.&quot; &quot;Kratie.&quot; &quot;Battambang.&quot; &quot;Phnom Penh.&quot; &quot;Luang Namtha.&quot; &quot;Savanh Nakhone.&quot; &quot;Khukhanor Surin.&quot; &quot;Nong Khai.&quot; &quot;Nongbua Lamphu.&quot; &quot;Chaiyaphum.&quot; &quot;Phetchaburi.&quot; &quot;Phitsanulok.&quot; &quot;Phra Bang.&quot; &quot;Chaiya.&quot; &quot;Thalang.&quot; &quot;Selangor.&quot; &quot;Terengganu.&quot; &quot;Kedah.&quot; &quot;Hkamti Long.&quot; &quot;Mong Kawng.&quot; &quot;Tamanthi.&quot; &quot;Thaungdut.&quot; &quot;Pagan.&quot; &quot;Hsipaw.&quot; &quot;Mong Pai.&quot; &quot;Sandoway.&quot; &quot;Martaban.&quot; &quot;Mergui.&quot; &quot;Bender.&quot; &quot;Ingil.&quot; &quot;Pereyaslav.&quot; &quot;Yelets.&quot; &quot;Bahmut.&quot; &quot;Theodoro.&quot; &quot;Mansur.&quot; &quot;Kyzyl-Yar.&quot; &quot;Tyn.&quot; &quot;Azaraba.&quot; &quot;Etkara.&quot; &quot;Majar.&quot; &quot;Kuma.&quot; &quot;Ukek.&quot; &quot;Kanadey.&quot; &quot;Agyidel.&quot; &quot;Juketau.&quot; &quot;Veda-Suvar.&quot; &quot;Alatyr.&quot; &quot;Peremyshl.&quot; &quot;Nenets.&quot; &quot;Yamal.&quot; &quot;Ostyaki.&quot; &quot;Yugan.&quot; &quot;Agan.&quot; &quot;Baykha.&quot; &quot;Uchamin.&quot; &quot;Chulym.&quot; &quot;Vah.&quot; &quot;Barnaul.&quot; &quot;Nukhtui.&quot; &quot;Chuna.&quot; &quot;Seganka.&quot; &quot;Kharya.&quot; &quot;Yarmanka.&quot; &quot;Kagyrgyn.&quot; &quot;Iglino.&quot; &quot;Ust-Kut.&quot; &quot;Kan.&quot; &quot;Bashgird.&quot; &quot;Mangazea.&quot; &quot;Chara.&quot; &quot;Matrega.&quot; &quot;Fezzan.&quot; &quot;Jufra.&quot; &quot;Ghadames.&quot; &quot;Thubaqt.&quot; &quot;Zuwarah.&quot; &quot;Sfax.&quot; &quot;Kef.&quot; &quot;Bizerte.&quot; &quot;Touggourt.&quot; &quot;Mzab.&quot; &quot;Hodna.&quot; &quot;Titteri.&quot; &quot;Saoura.&quot; &quot;Dahra.&quot; &quot;Ouarsenis.&quot; &quot;Kasdir.&quot; &quot;Ouarzazate.&quot; &quot;Oujda.&quot; &quot;Draa.&quot; &quot;Meknes.&quot; &quot;Tadla.&quot; &quot;Dukkala.&quot; &quot;Haha.&quot; &quot;Chott el-Jerid.&quot; &quot;Ouargla.&quot; &quot;Sousse.&quot; &quot;Tajhari.&quot; &quot;Djado.&quot; &quot;Kumeyaay.&quot; &quot;Yuki.&quot; &quot;Tachi.&quot; &quot;Maidu.&quot; &quot;Shasta.&quot; &quot;Klamath.&quot; &quot;Kalapuya.&quot; &quot;Umatilla.&quot; &quot;Quileute.&quot; &quot;Chehalis.&quot; &quot;Yakima.&quot; &quot;Spokane.&quot; &quot;Palus.&quot; &quot;Bohogue.&quot; &quot;Goshute.&quot; &quot;Hualapai.&quot; &quot;Chiricahua.&quot; &quot;Hopi.&quot; &quot;Zuni.&quot; &quot;Acoma.&quot; &quot;Jicarilla.&quot; &quot;Lipiyanes.&quot; &quot;Jumano.&quot; &quot;Coahuilteco.&quot; &quot;Querecho.&quot; &quot;Piegan.&quot; &quot;Haaninin.&quot; &quot;Ashshipite.&quot; &quot;Eeelalapito.&quot; &quot;Tsisistas.&quot; &quot;Kuccuntikka.&quot; &quot;Baachinena.&quot; &quot;Skiri.&quot; &quot;Utsetha.&quot; &quot;Hidatsa.&quot; &quot;Itscheabine.&quot; &quot;Wahpekute.&quot; &quot;Moingwena.&quot; &quot;Michigamea.&quot; &quot;Satuskhdin.&quot; &quot;Adai.&quot; &quot;Mdewakanton.&quot; &quot;Noquet.&quot; &quot;Kilatika.&quot; &quot;Mengkonkia.&quot; &quot;Okouara.&quot; &quot;Mascouten.&quot; &quot;Piankeshaw.&quot; &quot;Wabash.&quot; &quot;Chillicothe.&quot; &quot;Shatteras.&quot; &quot;Chickamauga.&quot; &quot;Yazoo.&quot; &quot;Natchez.&quot; &quot;Biloxi.&quot; &quot;Napochi.&quot; &quot;Tohome.&quot; &quot;Chatot.&quot; &quot;Yustaga.&quot; &quot;Calusa.&quot; &quot;Mayaimi.&quot; &quot;Hitchiti.&quot; &quot;Yamasee.&quot; &quot;Mocama.&quot; &quot;Coweta.&quot; &quot;Saluda.&quot; &quot;Cusabo.&quot; &quot;Waccamaw.&quot; &quot;Yadkin.&quot; &quot;Waxhaw.&quot; &quot;Chicora.&quot; &quot;Roanoke.&quot; &quot;Tutelo.&quot; &quot;Moratok.&quot; &quot;Doeg.&quot; &quot;Monongahela.&quot; &quot;Manahoac.&quot; &quot;Potomac.&quot; &quot;Nanticoke.&quot; &quot;Honniasont.&quot; &quot;Juniata.&quot; &quot;Atrakwaye.&quot; &quot;Espachomy.&quot; &quot;Adirondack.&quot; &quot;Quinnipiac.&quot; &quot;Wampanoag.&quot; &quot;Pennacook.&quot; &quot;Missisquoi.&quot; &quot;Sokoki.&quot; &quot;Kennebec.&quot; &quot;Passamaquoddy.&quot; &quot;Aroostook.&quot; &quot;Kespukwitk.&quot; &quot;Eskikewakik.&quot; &quot;Wolystoq.&quot; &quot;Madawaska.&quot; &quot;Siknikt.&quot; &quot;Placentia.&quot; &quot;Sikumiut.&quot; &quot;Naskapi.&quot; &quot;Mingan.&quot; &quot;Manicouagan.&quot; &quot;Anticosti.&quot; &quot;Piekouagami.&quot; &quot;Atikamekw.&quot; &quot;Timiskaming.&quot; &quot;Maliseet.&quot; &quot;Etchemins.&quot; &quot;Loup.&quot; &quot;Kichesipi.&quot; &quot;Tionontate.&quot; &quot;Odawa.&quot; &quot;Piscatang.&quot; &quot;Kesagami.&quot; &quot;Shaggami.&quot; &quot;Outoulibi.&quot; &quot;Omushkego.&quot; &quot;Wappus.&quot; &quot;Quennebigon.&quot; &quot;Kesyehotinne.&quot; &quot;Mahmikiwiniyak.&quot; &quot;Sipiwininiwak.&quot; &quot;Hebina.&quot; &quot;Athabasca.&quot; &quot;Nihithawak.&quot; &quot;Danezaa.&quot; &quot;Siksikawa.&quot; &quot;Sekani.&quot; &quot;Dakelh.&quot; &quot;Secwepemc.&quot; &quot;Tsilhoqotin.&quot; &quot;Okanagan.&quot; &quot;Rocky Mountains.&quot; &quot;Nisga\&apos;a.&quot; &quot;Heiltsuk.&quot; &quot;Kodiak.&quot; &quot;Eyak.&quot; &quot;Sitka.&quot; &quot;Cotoname.&quot; &quot;Guamares.&quot; &quot;Seri.&quot; &quot;Huichol.&quot; &quot;Toboso.&quot; &quot;Laguneros.&quot; &quot;Nakipa.&quot; &quot;Tizapan.&quot; &quot;Cuitzeo.&quot; &quot;Cutzamala.&quot; &quot;Patzcuaro.&quot; &quot;Hinonoeino.&quot; &quot;Tullucan.&quot; &quot;Cihuatlan.&quot; &quot;Tepeacac.&quot; &quot;Coyolapan.&quot; &quot;Tochtepec.&quot; &quot;Mixe.&quot; &quot;Xicallanco.&quot; &quot;Mani.&quot; &quot;Uaymil.&quot; &quot;Chiapas.&quot; &quot;Chacujal.&quot; &quot;Chortli.&quot; &quot;Xocnochco.&quot; &quot;Raritan.&quot; &quot;Lenca.&quot; &quot;Tziccoac.&quot; &quot;Metztitlan.&quot; &quot;Apatzingan.&quot; &quot;Cholula.&quot; &quot;Teloloapan.&quot; &quot;Coixtlahuacan.&quot; &quot;Cuetlaxtlan.&quot; &quot;Yopitzinco.&quot; &quot;Tehuantepec.&quot; &quot;Champutun.&quot; &quot;Ah Canul.&quot; &quot;Ecab.&quot; &quot;Iximch&#x00E9;.&quot; &quot;Baracoa.&quot; &quot;Bayamo.&quot; &quot;Camaguey.&quot; &quot;Colima.&quot; &quot;Maguana.&quot; &quot;Magua.&quot; &quot;Managua.&quot; &quot;Uluas.&quot; &quot;Olancho.&quot; &quot;Nicoya.&quot; &quot;Veraguas.&quot; &quot;Eyeish.&quot; &quot;Tuintsund&#x00E9;.&quot; &quot;Cacaxtes.&quot; &quot;Borrado.&quot; &quot;Hasinai.&quot; &quot;Tkaronto.&quot; &quot;Missisage.&quot; &quot;Kitkehaki.&quot; &quot;Pasai.&quot; &quot;Peureulak.&quot; &quot;Rokan.&quot; &quot;Indragiri.&quot; &quot;Jambi.&quot; &quot;Bangka.&quot; &quot;Belitung.&quot; &quot;Muko-Muko.&quot; &quot;Pagarruyung.&quot; &quot;Pariaman.&quot; &quot;Mentawai.&quot; &quot;Nias.&quot; &quot;Gayo.&quot; &quot;Bintan.&quot; &quot;Pakuan.&quot; &quot;Cirebon.&quot; &quot;Kendal.&quot; &quot;Pajang.&quot; &quot;Kediri.&quot; &quot;Madura.&quot; &quot;Lombok.&quot; &quot;Gangneung.&quot; &quot;East Timor.&quot; &quot;Yamdena.&quot; &quot;Tondo.&quot; &quot;Pangasinan.&quot; &quot;Bikol.&quot; &quot;Panay.&quot; &quot;Tagloc.&quot; &quot;Butuan.&quot; &quot;Lehad Datu.&quot; &quot;Sibu.&quot; &quot;Kuching.&quot; &quot;Katapang.&quot; &quot;Barito.&quot; &quot;Sampit.&quot; &quot;Tarakan.&quot; &quot;Berau.&quot; &quot;Bulungan.&quot; &quot;Samarinda.&quot; &quot;Gorontalo.&quot; &quot;Palu.&quot; &quot;Palopo.&quot; &quot;Buton.&quot; &quot;Sula.&quot; &quot;Fak-Fak.&quot; &quot;Madang.&quot; &quot;Lae.&quot; &quot;Kerema.&quot; &quot;Daru.&quot; &quot;Yos Sudarso.&quot; &quot;Asmat.&quot; &quot;Aru.&quot; &quot;Malgana.&quot; &quot;Minang.&quot; &quot;Tiwi.&quot; &quot;Yolngu.&quot; &quot;Awngthim.&quot; &quot;Guugu Yimithirr.&quot; &quot;Wulgurukaba.&quot; &quot;Baiali.&quot; &quot;Yuin.&quot; &quot;Gunditjmara.&quot; &quot;Nukunu.&quot; &quot;Ahuriri.&quot; &quot;Waitaha.&quot; &quot;Kirikiriroa.&quot; &quot;Borneo.&quot; &quot;Jeju.&quot; &quot;Yukjin.&quot; &quot;Gyeongseong.&quot; &quot;Nyeongbyeon.&quot; &quot;Gyeongju.&quot; &quot;Vidin.&quot; &quot;Khara Narin Ula.&quot; &quot;Jianchang.&quot; &quot;Tikhvin.&quot; &quot;Plovdiv.&quot; &quot;Cuenca.&quot; &quot;Romsdal.&quot; &quot;Narbonne.&quot; &quot;La Mancha.&quot; &quot;Soria.&quot; &quot;Welayta.&quot; &quot;Kaffa.&quot; &quot;Illubabor.&quot; &quot;Gambela.&quot; &quot;Hadiya.&quot; &quot;Arsi.&quot; &quot;Damot.&quot; &quot;Asosa.&quot; &quot;Ausa.&quot; &quot;Assab.&quot; &quot;Mendefera.&quot; &quot;Enderta.&quot; &quot;Angot.&quot; &quot;Lasta.&quot; &quot;Agew.&quot; &quot;Semien.&quot; &quot;Dembiya.&quot; &quot;Mora.&quot; &quot;Kismayo.&quot; &quot;Merca.&quot; &quot;Afgooye.&quot; &quot;Bardera.&quot; &quot;Werder.&quot; &quot;Afder.&quot; &quot;Beledweyne.&quot; &quot;Gedo.&quot; &quot;Warsheikh.&quot; &quot;Hobyo.&quot; &quot;Galkayo.&quot; &quot;El Buur.&quot; &quot;Bosaso.&quot; &quot;Hamasien.&quot; &quot;Hafun.&quot; &quot;Las Khorey.&quot; &quot;Sanaag.&quot; &quot;Ankober.&quot; &quot;Togdheer.&quot; &quot;Hargeisa.&quot; &quot;Barawa.&quot; &quot;Meregh.&quot; &quot;Pate.&quot; &quot;Shendy.&quot; &quot;Soba.&quot; &quot;Sennar.&quot; &quot;Kosti.&quot; &quot;Medwa.&quot; &quot;Kobbe.&quot; &quot;Orinoco Delta.&quot; &quot;Guasipati.&quot; &quot;Uyapari.&quot; &quot;Guajira.&quot; &quot;Altagracia.&quot; &quot;Coro.&quot; &quot;Llanos.&quot; &quot;Apure.&quot; &quot;Atabapo.&quot; &quot;Pore.&quot; &quot;Merida.&quot; &quot;Meta.&quot; &quot;Puerto Carreno.&quot; &quot;Guaviare.&quot; &quot;Neiva.&quot; &quot;Popayan.&quot; &quot;Darien.&quot; &quot;Esmeraldas.&quot; &quot;Piwra.&quot; &quot;Tucume.&quot; &quot;Moyobamba.&quot; &quot;Wankapampa.&quot; &quot;Pisqupampa.&quot; &quot;Chimbote.&quot; &quot;Huaraz.&quot; &quot;Camana.&quot; &quot;Ayaviri.&quot; &quot;Quero.&quot; &quot;Tiahuanaco.&quot; &quot;San Joaquin.&quot; &quot;Madre de Dios.&quot; &quot;Santa Cruz de la Sierra.&quot; &quot;Sucre.&quot; &quot;Tucuman.&quot; &quot;Santa Catalina.&quot; &quot;Tarija.&quot; &quot;Puna de Atacama.&quot; &quot;Calama.&quot; &quot;Antofagasta.&quot; &quot;Santiago del Estero.&quot; &quot;La Rioja.&quot; &quot;Chepes.&quot; &quot;San Juan.&quot; &quot;Quisquisacate.&quot; &quot;San Luis.&quot; &quot;Santa Fe.&quot; &quot;Rosario.&quot; &quot;Montevideo.&quot; &quot;Colonia.&quot; &quot;Salto.&quot; &quot;Yareyu.&quot; &quot;Chaco Central.&quot; &quot;Misiones.&quot; &quot;Highveld.&quot; &quot;Rio Grande do Sul.&quot; &quot;Santiago.&quot; &quot;Itap&#x00FA;a.&quot; &quot;Querandi.&quot; &quot;Sauce.&quot; &quot;Coquimbo.&quot; &quot;Rio Negro.&quot; &quot;Senqu.&quot; &quot;Puelches.&quot; &quot;Olavarria.&quot; &quot;Chanar.&quot; &quot;San Antonio.&quot; &quot;Florida Blanca.&quot; &quot;Tehuelmapu.&quot; &quot;Poya.&quot; &quot;Chiquiyami.&quot; &quot;Chiloe.&quot; &quot;Aysen.&quot; &quot;Chubut.&quot; &quot;Teush.&quot; &quot;Mendoza.&quot; &quot;Matara.&quot; &quot;Santa Tecla.&quot; &quot;Griqualand.&quot; &quot;Corumba.&quot; &quot;Fuerte Borbon.&quot; &quot;Melodia.&quot; &quot;Povos das Missoes.&quot; &quot;Barra.&quot; &quot;Parnaiba.&quot; &quot;Santa Catarina.&quot; &quot;Cuiaba.&quot; &quot;Rio Branco.&quot; &quot;Maraj&#x00F3;.&quot; &quot;Santo Antonio da Manga.&quot; &quot;Araxas.&quot; &quot;Ofaie.&quot; &quot;Sao Joao del Rei.&quot; &quot;Castro.&quot; &quot;Campinas.&quot; &quot;Araraquara.&quot; &quot;Serro.&quot; &quot;Vila Rica.&quot; &quot;Guapore.&quot; &quot;Cerejeiras.&quot; &quot;Vila Bela.&quot; &quot;Caceres.&quot; &quot;Diamantino.&quot; &quot;Rio Das Mortes.&quot; &quot;Ipora.&quot; &quot;Vila Boa.&quot; &quot;Arrial dos Couros.&quot; &quot;Conceicao.&quot; &quot;Pontal.&quot; &quot;Natividad.&quot; &quot;Sergipe.&quot; &quot;Jeremoabo.&quot; &quot;Inhambupe.&quot; &quot;Pambu.&quot; &quot;Rio Contas.&quot; &quot;Paratinga.&quot; &quot;Campo Largo.&quot; &quot;Luziana.&quot; &quot;Coxim.&quot; &quot;Alagoas.&quot; &quot;Borborema.&quot; &quot;Pastos Bons.&quot; &quot;Timon.&quot; &quot;Parnagua.&quot; &quot;Grajau.&quot; &quot;Alcantara.&quot; &quot;Tucurui.&quot; &quot;Para.&quot; &quot;Santarem.&quot; &quot;Pirara.&quot; &quot;Waddai.&quot; &quot;Barcelos.&quot; &quot;Manaus.&quot; &quot;Muturu.&quot; &quot;Guyana.&quot; &quot;Suriname.&quot; &quot;Oiapoque.&quot; &quot;Zaraza.&quot; &quot;Chichas.&quot; &quot;Choquechaca.&quot; &quot;Charcas.&quot; &quot;Chachapoyas.&quot; &quot;Ucayali.&quot; &quot;Yurimaguas.&quot; &quot;Quillacas.&quot; &quot;Macaya.&quot; &quot;Matamba.&quot; &quot;Mbata.&quot; &quot;Buhera.&quot; &quot;Manikya.&quot; &quot;Madanda.&quot; &quot;Hj&#x00E4;lmaren.&quot; &quot;Djerba.&quot; &quot;Ingolstadt.&quot; &quot;Straubing.&quot; &quot;Regensburg.&quot; &quot;Osterode.&quot; &quot;Tarnow.&quot; &quot;Nowy Sacz.&quot; &quot;Lwow.&quot; &quot;Rowne.&quot; &quot;Notec.&quot; &quot;Altmark.&quot; &quot;Vogtland.&quot; &quot;Glogau.&quot; &quot;Eger.&quot; &quot;Budejovice.&quot; &quot;Sternberg.&quot; &quot;Hradecko.&quot; &quot;Hoya.&quot; &quot;Paderborn.&quot; &quot;Meppen.&quot; &quot;Loon.&quot; &quot;Kleves.&quot; &quot;Umbria.&quot; &quot;Urbino.&quot; &quot;Arezzo.&quot; &quot;Novara.&quot; &quot;Lucca.&quot; &quot;Montferrat.&quot; &quot;Syracuse.&quot; &quot;Salerno.&quot; &quot;Cosenza.&quot; &quot;Capitanata.&quot; &quot;Cagliari.&quot; &quot;Urgell.&quot; &quot;Tarragona.&quot; &quot;Rioja.&quot; &quot;Teruel.&quot; &quot;Forcalquier.&quot; &quot;Albenga.&quot; &quot;Uckermark.&quot; &quot;Greifswald.&quot; &quot;Stolp.&quot; &quot;Wismar.&quot; &quot;Tuchola.&quot; &quot;Buzau.&quot; &quot;Hormuz.&quot; &quot;Nis.&quot; &quot;Skopje.&quot; &quot;Visoki.&quot; &quot;Euboea.&quot; &quot;Comoros.&quot; &quot;Antankara.&quot; &quot;Iboina.&quot; &quot;Tsimihety.&quot; &quot;Maroantsetra.&quot; &quot;Vatomandry.&quot; &quot;Antemoro.&quot; &quot;Betsileo.&quot; &quot;Mahafaly.&quot; &quot;Antanosy.&quot; &quot;Bara.&quot; &quot;Antsalova.&quot; &quot;Fiherana.&quot; &quot;Al Qadarif.&quot; &quot;Makua.&quot; &quot;Ngindo.&quot; &quot;Wayao.&quot; &quot;Katsekera.&quot; &quot;Lolo.&quot; &quot;Lundu.&quot; &quot;Kalonga.&quot; &quot;Kinga.&quot; &quot;Makonde.&quot; &quot;Phangwa.&quot; &quot;Ngonde.&quot; &quot;Tumbuka.&quot; &quot;Lala.&quot; &quot;Nsenga.&quot; &quot;Lomwe.&quot; &quot;Ibo.&quot; &quot;Luangwa.&quot; &quot;Ewaso Ngiro.&quot; &quot;Dawa.&quot; &quot;Turkana.&quot; &quot;Kuria.&quot; &quot;Shamba.&quot; &quot;Gogo.&quot; &quot;Nyatura.&quot; &quot;Zigua.&quot; &quot;Shaga.&quot; &quot;Kikuyu.&quot; &quot;Buzinza.&quot; &quot;Busoga.&quot; &quot;Karagwe.&quot; &quot;Buganda.&quot; &quot;Bunyoro.&quot; &quot;Nkore.&quot; &quot;Nduga.&quot; &quot;Bafuriru.&quot; &quot;Bushubi.&quot; &quot;Nkoma.&quot; &quot;Buyogoma.&quot; &quot;Ruguru.&quot; &quot;Hehe.&quot; &quot;Pubungo.&quot; &quot;Lango.&quot; &quot;Muhambwe.&quot; &quot;Rukwa.&quot; &quot;Mayumba.&quot; &quot;Ngoyo.&quot; &quot;Soyo.&quot; &quot;Songo.&quot; &quot;Kasanje.&quot; &quot;Shinje.&quot; &quot;Malem.&quot; &quot;Yaka.&quot; &quot;Nunu.&quot; &quot;Kumbana.&quot; &quot;Munene.&quot; &quot;Kuba.&quot; &quot;Songye.&quot; &quot;Mpasu.&quot; &quot;Rund.&quot; &quot;Lwena.&quot; &quot;Chokwe.&quot; &quot;Ishindi.&quot; &quot;Kalundwe.&quot; &quot;Luba.&quot; &quot;Upemba.&quot; &quot;Hemba.&quot; &quot;Luapula.&quot; &quot;Lualaba.&quot; &quot;Bemba.&quot; &quot;Tabwa.&quot; &quot;Lamba.&quot; &quot;Kusu.&quot; &quot;Lenje.&quot; &quot;Kanongesha.&quot; &quot;Kaonde.&quot; &quot;Lega.&quot; &quot;Sutherland.&quot; &quot;Saintonge.&quot; &quot;Quercy.&quot; &quot;Rovaniemi.&quot; &quot;Jokkmokk.&quot; &quot;Mazyr.&quot; &quot;Oka.&quot; &quot;Bezhetsk.&quot; &quot;Cork.&quot; &quot;Sligo.&quot; &quot;Kildare.&quot; &quot;Ulster.&quot; &quot;Shenkursk.&quot; &quot;Pirkanmaa.&quot; &quot;Karelia.&quot; &quot;Szolnok.&quot; &quot;Bacs.&quot; &quot;Turda.&quot; &quot;Kir&#x00E1;lyf&#x00F6;ld.&quot; &quot;Ust-Vym.&quot; &quot;Somerset.&quot; &quot;Mutsu.&quot; &quot;Mweru.&quot; &quot;Kivu.&quot; &quot;Rutanzige.&quot; &quot;Lake Albert.&quot; &quot;Zaysan.&quot; &quot;Alakol.&quot; &quot;Issyk-Kul.&quot; &quot;Ouluj&#x00E4;rvi.&quot; &quot;Saimaa.&quot; &quot;Dithmarschen.&quot; &quot;&#x00D8;stjylland.&quot; &quot;Sm&#x00E5;lenene.&quot; &quot;Bratsberg.&quot; &quot;Agdesiden.&quot; &quot;Langfjella.&quot; &quot;Rostov.&quot; &quot;Luki.&quot; &quot;Kolding.&quot; &quot;&#x00C9;vora.&quot; &quot;Enare.&quot; &quot;Kainuu.&quot; &quot;The Scandes.&quot; &quot;The Pyrenees.&quot; &quot;The Carpathians.&quot; &quot;The Caucasus.&quot; &quot;The Alps.&quot; &quot;Janjiro.&quot; &quot;The Alps.&quot; &quot;The Alps.&quot; &quot;The Alps.&quot; &quot;The Alps.&quot; &quot;Elfsborg.&quot; &quot;Dal.&quot; &quot;G&#x00F6;inge.&quot; &quot;Tioh&#x00E4;rad.&quot; &quot;High Atlas.&quot; &quot;High Atlas.&quot; &quot;Aures.&quot; &quot;Zagros.&quot; &quot;Abarquh.&quot; &quot;Zagros.&quot; &quot;Syrmia.&quot; &quot;Durr&#x00EB;s.&quot; &quot;Lezh&#x00EB;.&quot; &quot;Branicevo.&quot; &quot;Alborz.&quot; &quot;Pontic Mountains.&quot; &quot;Hakkari Mountains.&quot; &quot;Hyuga.&quot; &quot;Higo.&quot; &quot;Hizen.&quot; &quot;Iwami.&quot; &quot;Bizen.&quot; &quot;Tango.&quot; &quot;Iyo.&quot; &quot;Kii.&quot; &quot;Shinano.&quot; &quot;Sagami.&quot; &quot;Shimousa.&quot; &quot;Shimotsuke.&quot; &quot;Ugo.&quot; &quot;Oshima.&quot; &quot;Yongping.&quot; &quot;Zhending.&quot; &quot;Haizhou.&quot; &quot;Huangzhou.&quot; &quot;Fengxiang.&quot; &quot;Tongren.&quot; &quot;Hulan.&quot; &quot;Jianzhou.&quot; &quot;Taining.&quot; &quot;Ju Ud.&quot; &quot;Anding.&quot; &quot;Nagchu.&quot; &quot;Balikul.&quot; &quot;Turpan.&quot; &quot;Qurqara-usu.&quot; &quot;Maralbexi.&quot; &quot;Yangi Hissar.&quot; &quot;Dazhou.&quot; &quot;Jiazhou.&quot; &quot;Luzhou.&quot; &quot;Kalar.&quot; &quot;Fudali.&quot; &quot;Ulch.&quot; &quot;Pijin.&quot; &quot;Buteha.&quot; &quot;Bayan Tumen.&quot; &quot;Khiagt.&quot; &quot;Dundgovi.&quot; &quot;Ulaangom.&quot; &quot;Hetao.&quot; &quot;Tokai Sea.&quot; &quot;Hokkaido Coast.&quot; &quot;Japan Basin.&quot; &quot;Jinju.&quot; &quot;Naju.&quot; &quot;Chungju.&quot; &quot;Suwon.&quot; &quot;Haeju.&quot; &quot;Ganggye.&quot; &quot;Bohai Sea.&quot; &quot;Western Yellow Sea.&quot; &quot;Vistula Lagoon.&quot; &quot;Trencin.&quot; &quot;Olomouc.&quot; &quot;Liegnitz.&quot; &quot;Belgrade.&quot; &quot;Fej&#x00E9;r.&quot; &quot;Wenden.&quot; &quot;Ula.&quot; &quot;Toropets.&quot; &quot;Trubchevsk.&quot; &quot;Vyazma.&quot; &quot;Mstislav.&quot; &quot;Owrucz.&quot; &quot;Kashin.&quot; &quot;Zubtsov.&quot; &quot;Mologa.&quot; &quot;Mozhaisk.&quot; &quot;Kolomna.&quot; &quot;Yuriev.&quot; &quot;Starodub.&quot; &quot;Pronsk.&quot; &quot;Solvychegodsk.&quot; &quot;Mezen.&quot; &quot;Onega.&quot; &quot;Velsk.&quot; &quot;Vyshny Volochyok.&quot; &quot;Ustyuzhna.&quot; &quot;Totma.&quot; &quot;Sol Galitskaya.&quot; &quot;Tetyushi.&quot; &quot;Ar-Chally.&quot; &quot;Izhkar.&quot; &quot;Bolgar.&quot; &quot;Aqabah.&quot; &quot;Al Wajh.&quot; &quot;Azraq.&quot; &quot;Suwayda.&quot; &quot;Al Jawf.&quot; &quot;Al-Kariatan.&quot; &quot;Sudayr.&quot; &quot;Al-Yamamah.&quot; &quot;Jabal Tubaiq.&quot; &quot;Taif.&quot; &quot;Qunfudhah.&quot; &quot;Zabid.&quot; &quot;Taiz.&quot; &quot;Dhamar.&quot; &quot;Sahda.&quot; &quot;Shihr.&quot; &quot;Al Ghaydah.&quot; &quot;Baraimi.&quot; &quot;Ash Sharqiyah.&quot; &quot;Ibra.&quot; &quot;Shatt.&quot; &quot;Shushtar.&quot; &quot;Hoveyzeh.&quot; &quot;Qazaniya.&quot; &quot;Mardin.&quot; &quot;Arbil.&quot; &quot;Sulimaniyeh.&quot; &quot;Hisn Kayfa.&quot; &quot;Bitlis.&quot; &quot;Homs.&quot; &quot;Ayntab.&quot; &quot;Shamakhi.&quot; &quot;Mianeh.&quot; &quot;Kartli.&quot; &quot;Bayazid.&quot; &quot;Oltu.&quot; &quot;Khoy.&quot; &quot;Shaki.&quot; &quot;Lakia.&quot; &quot;Aksaray.&quot; &quot;Denizli.&quot; &quot;Aydin.&quot; &quot;Divrigi.&quot; &quot;Karahisar.&quot; &quot;Sultan&#x00F6;n&#x00FC;.&quot; &quot;Kangiri.&quot; &quot;Kirshehir.&quot; &quot;Tokat.&quot; &quot;Sharqiya.&quot; &quot;Buhaira.&quot; &quot;Atfih.&quot; &quot;Isna.&quot; &quot;Girga.&quot; &quot;Egyptian Desert.&quot; &quot;Egyptian Desert.&quot; &quot;Farafreh.&quot; &quot;Ghuriyan.&quot; &quot;Sarakhs.&quot; &quot;Nishapur.&quot; &quot;Jask.&quot; &quot;Chagai.&quot; &quot;Fasa.&quot; &quot;Darab.&quot; &quot;Kazerun.&quot; &quot;Siraf.&quot; &quot;Dahlak Archipelago.&quot; &quot;Tabas.&quot; &quot;Kashan.&quot; &quot;Tun.&quot; &quot;Savah.&quot; &quot;Soltanieh.&quot; &quot;Rasht.&quot; &quot;Astara.&quot; &quot;Sari.&quot; &quot;Malamir.&quot; &quot;Termez.&quot; &quot;Kish.&quot; &quot;Saidabad.&quot; &quot;Qamr Bay.&quot; &quot;Pirate Coast.&quot; &quot;Ifugao.&quot; &quot;Laguna.&quot; &quot;Mindoro.&quot; &quot;Buglas.&quot; &quot;Cebu.&quot; &quot;Leyte.&quot; &quot;Zamboanga.&quot; &quot;Caraga.&quot; &quot;Taytay.&quot; &quot;Cuyo Archipelago.&quot; &quot;Philippine Trench.&quot; &quot;Ise.&quot; &quot;Mikawa.&quot; &quot;East March.&quot; &quot;West March.&quot; &quot;Argyll.&quot; &quot;Inner Hebrides.&quot; &quot;Mann.&quot; &quot;Montgomery.&quot; &quot;Hull.&quot; &quot;Scarborough.&quot; &quot;Carmarthen.&quot; &quot;Cambridge.&quot; &quot;Sussex.&quot; &quot;Coventry.&quot; &quot;Devon.&quot; &quot;Dorset.&quot; &quot;Chester.&quot; &quot;Leicester.&quot; &quot;Ormond.&quot; &quot;Desmond.&quot; &quot;Midlands.&quot; &quot;Donegal.&quot; &quot;Oversticht.&quot; &quot;Groningen.&quot; &quot;Den Haag.&quot; &quot;Rennais.&quot; &quot;Cotentin.&quot; &quot;Bas-Poitou.&quot; &quot;Angoumois.&quot; &quot;Chartres.&quot; &quot;Touraine.&quot; &quot;Troyes.&quot; &quot;Vivarais.&quot; &quot;Auxerrois.&quot;</Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Keywords8"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Delimiters">00Event: 01 02((EOL)) 03 03Decision: 04 05((EOL)) 06[messagehandler 07 08] 09EVE: 10 11((EOL)) 12Error 13 14((EOL)) 15 16 17 18 19 20 21 22 23</Keywords>
        </KeywordLists>
        <Styles>
            <WordsStyle name="DEFAULT" fgColor="000000" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="0" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="COMMENTS" fgColor="000000" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="0" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="LINE COMMENTS" fgColor="6A6A6A" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="0" nesting="261120" />
            <WordsStyle name="NUMBERS" fgColor="000000" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="0" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="KEYWORDS1" fgColor="000087" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="0" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="KEYWORDS2" fgColor="000087" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="0" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="KEYWORDS3" fgColor="008000" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="0" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="KEYWORDS4" fgColor="008040" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="0" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="KEYWORDS5" fgColor="C86400" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="0" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="KEYWORDS6" fgColor="C86400" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="0" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="KEYWORDS7" fgColor="C86400" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="0" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="KEYWORDS8" fgColor="000000" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="0" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="OPERATORS" fgColor="A40000" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="0" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="FOLDER IN CODE1" fgColor="000000" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="0" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="FOLDER IN CODE2" fgColor="000000" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="0" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="FOLDER IN COMMENT" fgColor="000000" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="0" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="DELIMITERS1" fgColor="005900" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="0" nesting="261120" />
            <WordsStyle name="DELIMITERS2" fgColor="005900" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="0" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="DELIMITERS3" fgColor="000000" bgColor="DDDDDD" fontName="" fontStyle="0" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="DELIMITERS4" fgColor="0080C0" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="1" nesting="16" />
            <WordsStyle name="DELIMITERS5" fgColor="000000" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="0" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="DELIMITERS6" fgColor="000000" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="0" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="DELIMITERS7" fgColor="000000" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="0" nesting="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="DELIMITERS8" fgColor="000000" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="0" nesting="0" />
        </Styles>
    </UserLang>
</NotepadPlus>
